<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-23T19:52:18+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing personality 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/23/writing-personality-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing personality 1" /><published>2023-05-23T00:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-23T00:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/23/writing%20personality%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/23/writing-personality-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people fail in school but end up sucessful in life
why do you think that is the case?
&lt;br /&gt;
what is the most important thing to succeed in life?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
generally people believe successful in school should be prerequisite of successful in life. However there were always some who was not successful in school but in life. i will write my inference of the reason of this situation further in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Generally, people believe that success in school is a prerequisite for success in life. However, there have always been individuals who were not successful in school but still managed to achieve success in life. In the following paragraph, I will provide my inference on the reasons behind this situation.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;prerequisite of -&amp;gt; prerequisite for
&lt;br /&gt;
were always -&amp;gt; have always been
&lt;br /&gt;
write my inference of -&amp;gt; provide my inference on
&lt;br /&gt;
reason of this situation -&amp;gt; reason behind this situation
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the regular education of school is stands for keep the human species from unnesscerly excessive explore by providing guideline. but as time progresses, world’s gaining diversity resulting in making lots of way to live. as we can’t cover and guide every case by regular education there are occer some cases who success with their own way didn’t following the regular course.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The regular education system in schools aims to prevent unnecessary and excessive exploration by providing guidelines. However, as the world progresses, it becomes increasingly diverse, giving rise to various paths in life. Since the regular education system cannot cover and guide every individual case, there are instances where individuals find success by following their own unique paths, deviating from the conventional course.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;resulting in -&amp;gt; giving rise to
&lt;br /&gt;
lots of way -&amp;gt; various path
&lt;br /&gt;
there are occur -&amp;gt; there are instances
&lt;br /&gt;
didn’t following the regular course -&amp;gt; deviating from the conventional course
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;now we can come up with one question about what is important to be successful. i believe the most important thing is becoming confident. since we live in different environment, we are getting our own strength in our life. every our behavior has personal significant in their pursuit of happiness moreover If someone focuses on one skill, we can identify the area in which they are optimized using the maximum principle of convex optimization theory. If you come across someone who is optimized in a particular area, you can ascertain their focus on one skill through the strong separation theorem of convex optimization theory. but we can only become extreme to one area through stop comparing ourselves with another because we can easily loose our confidence by that behavior.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Now, we can raise a question about what is important for success. I believe that the most crucial factor is developing confidence. As we live in diverse environments, we cultivate our own strengths in life. Each of our behaviors holds personal significance in our pursuit of happiness. Furthermore, If someone focuses on one skill, we can identify the area in which they are optimized using the maximum principle of convex optimization theory. If you come across someone who is optimized in a particular area, you can ascertain their focus on one skill through the strong separation theorem of convex optimization theory. However, we can only become truly exceptional in one area by refraining from comparing ourselves to others, as such comparisons can easily undermine our confidence.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;come up with -&amp;gt; raise
&lt;br /&gt;
becomming confident -&amp;gt; developing confident
&lt;br /&gt;
getting our own strength -&amp;gt; cultivate our own strengh
&lt;br /&gt;
every our -&amp;gt; each of our bahaviors hold
&lt;br /&gt;
extreme -&amp;gt; focus on 
&lt;br /&gt;
by ~ theory -&amp;gt; using ~ theory
&lt;br /&gt;
encounter -&amp;gt; come across (encounter은 의도적인 만남)
&lt;br /&gt;
extreme -&amp;gt; exceptional
&lt;br /&gt;
stop -&amp;gt; by refraining
&lt;br /&gt;
loose the confidence -&amp;gt; undermine our confidence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q some people fail in school but end up sucessful in life why do you think that is the case? what is the most important thing to succeed in life? A generally people believe successful in school should be prerequisite of successful in life. However there were always some who was not successful in school but in life. i will write my inference of the reason of this situation further in the following paragraph. revise</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing education 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/22/writing-education-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing education 3" /><published>2023-05-22T09:53:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-22T09:53:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/22/writing%20education%203</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/22/writing-education-3.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
the government should allocate more funding to teaching sciences rather than subjects in order for a country to develop and progress
&lt;br /&gt;
to what extent do you agree?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
as the time progresses, the world is becomming globalize due to the advancement of transportation system and online platform. but most crucial factor behind all this change is improvement of techonology over time. some advocate goverment to fund more in techonology through weighting more in teaching in regular education. i will provide detailed explaination of my perspective on this matter further in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
As time progresses, the world is becoming more globalized due to advancements in transportation systems and online platforms. However, the most crucial factor driving these changes is the continuous improvement of technology. Some argue that the government should invest more in technology by giving it greater importance in regular education. In the following paragraph, I will provide a detailed explanation of my perspective on this matter.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;advancement of -&amp;gt; advancements in 
&lt;br /&gt;
factor behind -&amp;gt; factor driving
&lt;br /&gt;
improvement of techonology over time -&amp;gt; continuous improvement of technology
&lt;br /&gt;
weighting more in -&amp;gt; giving it greater importance
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;even though every imporvement is due to techonological advancement, that doesn’t bring hapiness of human species. as difference between wealthy and poverty getting worse, persentage of homeless is rather getting more than before which phenomenon is occered from loophole of policy.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Even though every improvement is due to technological advancement, that doesn’t necessarily bring happiness to the human species. As the difference between wealth and poverty worsens, the percentage of homelessness is increasing rather than decreasing, which is a phenomenon occurring due to policy loopholes.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;getting worse -&amp;gt; worsen
&lt;br /&gt;
which phenomenon occered from-&amp;gt; which is a phenomenon occering due to
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;government’s excessive influence to some area is potentially problematic. for instance, in korea, government’s excessively support in medical science brings lots of medical accident because there are lots of people who wanna practice surgery even though they are not qualified or not interested in help people sincerely and even worse, government makes lots of loophole in the law in the medical field with the reason of assitance of medical field.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Government’s excessive influence in certain areas can pose potential problems. For instance, in Korea, the government’s excessive support in the field of medical science has resulted in numerous medical accidents. This is due to the presence of individuals who are eager to perform surgeries without proper qualifications or genuine dedication to helping people. Furthermore, the government’s creation of loopholes in medical laws, under the guise of assisting the medical field, exacerbates the situation.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;some -&amp;gt; certain
&lt;br /&gt;
imply -&amp;gt; pose
&lt;br /&gt;
lots of -&amp;gt; numerous
&lt;br /&gt;
interested in help sincerily -&amp;gt; genuine dedication
&lt;br /&gt;
with the reason of -&amp;gt; under the guise of, under the pretense of
&lt;br /&gt;
worsen -&amp;gt; exacerbates
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;so i believe the most important thing is, government have to assist people to crave out their own way through balance the investment on each field not invest excessively on the just few field as happiness is achieved through preventing metthew effect regardless of advancement of techonology.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
So I believe the most important thing is that the government assists people in carving out their own path by balancing investments in each field, rather than investing excessively in just a few areas. Happiness is achieved through preventing the Matthew effect, regardless of technological advancements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;assist people to crave out -&amp;gt; assist people in craving out (people who are carving out)
&lt;br /&gt;
way -&amp;gt; path
&lt;br /&gt;
invest on -&amp;gt; invest in
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q the government should allocate more funding to teaching sciences rather than subjects in order for a country to develop and progress to what extent do you agree? A as the time progresses, the world is becomming globalize due to the advancement of transportation system and online platform. but most crucial factor behind all this change is improvement of techonology over time. some advocate goverment to fund more in techonology through weighting more in teaching in regular education. i will provide detailed explaination of my perspective on this matter further in the following paragraph. revise</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing education 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/22/writing-education-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing education 2" /><published>2023-05-22T03:53:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-22T03:53:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/22/writing%20education%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/22/writing-education-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
for centuries, importat parts of education have remained such as reading, writing and maths. with the advent of computers, some people think that computer skill be made as fourth skill to be added to the list
&lt;br /&gt;
to what extent do you agree?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
world is becoming more globalized over time. not only for the development of transport system, the online system which enabling us to exchange information more easily is becomming more important. some argu we have to include computer education in school regular education system according to this development. i will elaborate on my perspective on this view in the following paragraph further.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;review&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The world is becoming increasingly globalized, and this is evident not only in the advancement of transportation systems but also in the growing significance of online platforms that facilitate the exchange of information. Some argue that computer education should be included in the regular education system in response to this trend. In the following paragraph, I will provide a detailed explanation of my perspective on this matter.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;world -&amp;gt; the world
&lt;br /&gt;
more -&amp;gt; increasingly
&lt;br /&gt;
development of transport -&amp;gt; advancement of transportation
&lt;br /&gt;
transport system -&amp;gt; transportation system
&lt;br /&gt;
enabling more easily -&amp;gt; facilitate
&lt;br /&gt;
online system -&amp;gt; online flatform
&lt;br /&gt;
according to this development -&amp;gt; in response to this trend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
respecting individual’s choice is important as every one’s choice has their own meaning in aspect of chasing the happiness. even though we have to keep that kinds of attitude, sometimes we have to compel some extent of guideline to prevent human species from falling in sub optimization because sometimes we choose difficult way because we purely don’t know any better. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Respecting individuals’ choices is crucial, as each person’s choice holds personal significance in their pursuit of happiness. However, there are instances where it becomes necessary to impose certain guidelines to prevent the human species from falling into sub-optimization, as sometimes we choose difficult paths simply because we lack better alternatives.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;important -&amp;gt; crucial
&lt;br /&gt;
every one’s -&amp;gt; each person’s
&lt;br /&gt;
choice has -&amp;gt; choice holds
&lt;br /&gt;
their own meaning -&amp;gt; personal significance
&lt;br /&gt;
in aspect of chasing -&amp;gt; in their pursuit of
&lt;br /&gt;
falling in -&amp;gt; falling into
&lt;br /&gt;
sometimes -&amp;gt; there is instances
&lt;br /&gt;
compel -&amp;gt; impose
&lt;br /&gt;
sub optimization -&amp;gt; sub-optimization
&lt;br /&gt;
don’t know any better -&amp;gt; lack better alternatives
&lt;br /&gt;
way -&amp;gt; path
&lt;br /&gt;
purely -&amp;gt; simply
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;computer science help us to relieve the problem which is like “falling in sub optimization” or “make hasty disition” by learning another people’s life through internet flatform like another regular subjects. in instance, ability associated with math enabling us to think more logically and sensible, literacy and computer science facilitate us to communicate.which is why regular education stands for us.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Computer science plays a vital role in addressing such challenges, as it allows us to learn from the lives of others through online platforms, much like any other regular subject. For example, proficiency in mathematics fosters logical and rational thinking, while literacy and computer science skills enhance communication abilities. These are the reasons why computer education is an essential component of a well-rounded education system.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;relieve the problem -&amp;gt; address such challenges
&lt;br /&gt;
like another ~ -&amp;gt; much like any other ~
&lt;br /&gt;
internet flatform -&amp;gt; online platform
&lt;br /&gt;
enabling = 없는걸 줘서 가능하게
&lt;br /&gt;
foster = 그냥 강화시키는거
&lt;br /&gt;
why -&amp;gt; the reasons why&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q for centuries, importat parts of education have remained such as reading, writing and maths. with the advent of computers, some people think that computer skill be made as fourth skill to be added to the list to what extent do you agree? A world is becoming more globalized over time. not only for the development of transport system, the online system which enabling us to exchange information more easily is becomming more important. some argu we have to include computer education in school regular education system according to this development. i will elaborate on my perspective on this view in the following paragraph further. review</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing education 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-education-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing education 1" /><published>2023-05-21T15:53:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-21T15:53:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing%20education%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-education-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some educationalists think that international exchange visits will benefit teenagers at the school. to what extent do the advantages outweigh the disadvantages?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
As time progress, world is becomming globalized enabling us to visit and communicate another country more and more easier. different from past, we can compare our country with different countries such things resulting in us be able to revise our own culture and learn better things from another culture. I will elaborate my perspective of internationl exchange visits in the following paragraph further.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
As time progresses, the world is becoming more globalized, making it easier for us to visit and communicate with other countries. Unlike in the past, we now have the opportunity to compare our own culture with that of different countries, allowing us to revise and improve our own cultural practices. Through international exchange visits, we can gain a deeper understanding of other cultures and learn valuable lessons from them. I will elaborate on my perspective on international exchange visits in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;communicate -&amp;gt; communicate with
&lt;br /&gt;
enabling ~~ more easier -&amp;gt; making it easier
&lt;br /&gt;
different from past -&amp;gt; unlike in the past
&lt;br /&gt;
such things -&amp;gt; ,
&lt;br /&gt;
resulting us ~ be able to -&amp;gt; allowing us
&lt;br /&gt;
learn better things -&amp;gt; learn valuable lessons
&lt;br /&gt;
elaborate my perspective of -&amp;gt; elaborate on my perspective on
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if you to live in another country, it can be cost you need to find house to stay, you need to find airplain ticket and also if you are going to wealthy country, food will be also more expensive than your own country. you have to learn about another countries transport system and you have to buy and connect your data. and it can be also difficult to make friends because you or your friends are not accustomed to rase diversity. if at least one of them or you are not good at english, it also must play the crutial point to making you hard to make friennds
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
If you choose to live in another country, there will be associated costs such as finding a place to stay, purchasing airplane tickets, and potentially dealing with higher food prices in wealthier countries. You will also need to familiarize yourself with the transportation system and arrange for internet connectivity. Additionally, making friends might be challenging due to differences in cultural background and racial diversity. Language proficiency, particularly in English, can also be a crucial factor in establishing social connections even if either you or your friends are not fluent in it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;it will be cost ~~ -&amp;gt; there will be associated costs
&lt;br /&gt;
will be ~~ if -&amp;gt; potentially ~~ in
&lt;br /&gt;
food will be expensive -&amp;gt; dealing with higher food prices
&lt;br /&gt;
accostomed to -&amp;gt; just used to it
&lt;br /&gt;
familiarize with -&amp;gt; acquire new knowledge
&lt;br /&gt;
buy and connect your data -&amp;gt; arrange for internet connectivity
&lt;br /&gt;
rase diversity -&amp;gt; racial diversity
&lt;br /&gt;
good at language -&amp;gt; language proficiency
&lt;br /&gt;
play a crutial point -&amp;gt; crucial factor
&lt;br /&gt;
make friends -&amp;gt; establishing social connections
&lt;br /&gt;
if at least one of them or you are not good at english
&lt;br /&gt;
-&amp;gt; even if either you or your friends are not fluent in it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
even though every disadvantage arise from living in another country, advantages are still seems to cover every disadvantages. maybe it can be hard to study in that situation due to busy of making yourself familierize to that environment. but most of all, you can learn plenty of another cultures through that processes. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the disadvantages that may arise from living in another country, the advantages seem to outweigh them. It can be challenging to study in such a situation due to the busyness of familiarizing yourself with the new environment. However, this process presents an opportunity to learn about other cultures instead.
&lt;br /&gt;
cover them -&amp;gt; outweigh them
&lt;br /&gt;
hard -&amp;gt; challenging
&lt;br /&gt;
that situation -&amp;gt; such situation
&lt;br /&gt;
busy of -&amp;gt; busyness of
&lt;br /&gt;
근데 오히려 -&amp;gt; however ~ instead
&lt;br /&gt;
can do through this process -&amp;gt; this process presents an opportunity&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q some educationalists think that international exchange visits will benefit teenagers at the school. to what extent do the advantages outweigh the disadvantages? A As time progress, world is becomming globalized enabling us to visit and communicate another country more and more easier. different from past, we can compare our country with different countries such things resulting in us be able to revise our own culture and learn better things from another culture. I will elaborate my perspective of internationl exchange visits in the following paragraph further. revise</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing language 4</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-language-4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing language 4" /><published>2023-05-21T15:00:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-21T15:00:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing%20language%204</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-language-4.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people think that you can never become fluent in a language unless you have spent time living or working in that country.
&lt;br /&gt;
to what extent do you agree?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q some people think that you can never become fluent in a language unless you have spent time living or working in that country. to what extent do you agree? A</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing language 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-language-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing language 3" /><published>2023-05-21T11:00:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-21T11:00:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing%20language%203</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-language-3.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people think that a person can never understand the culture of a country unless they speak the language.
&lt;br /&gt;
do you agree with this opinion?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
we sometimes can see the argument that says languages have only few origins.however, with the time progression, human species have gained the diversity in language to meet each other’s needs of expression which varies across the country. this development bring languages to be interwined with culture. someone argue we can’t learn another culture unless learning language. i will elaborate my perspective of view with this argument in the following paragraph further.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
We sometimes encounter the argument that languages have only a few origins. However, as time has progressed, the human species has gained linguistic diversity to fulfill the varied needs of expression across different countries. This development has resulted in languages becoming intertwined with culture. Some argue that we cannot truly understand another culture without learning its language. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;can see -&amp;gt; encounter
&lt;br /&gt;
argument that says -&amp;gt; argument that
&lt;br /&gt;
with the time progression -&amp;gt; as time has progressed
&lt;br /&gt;
diversity of language -&amp;gt; linguistic diversity
&lt;br /&gt;
across the country -&amp;gt; across different countries
&lt;br /&gt;
someone -&amp;gt; some
&lt;br /&gt;
elaborate -&amp;gt; elaborate on
&lt;br /&gt;
with this argument -&amp;gt; regarding this argument
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it can be difficult to learn another countries culture without learning their language because we can see their priority from way to talk. when their country is surrounded by sea, they are used to use the term about ship, fish. when their country is located in the north part of earth, they are used to use language about snow, blizzard. their language is probably developed to that way so as to express details about their important things.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
It can be difficult to understand another country’s culture without learning their language, as their language reveals their priorities and preferences. For instance, if a country is surrounded by sea, their language may incorporate terms specific to ships and fish. Similarly, if a country is located in the northern part of the Earth, their language may include words specific to snow and blizzards. These linguistic nuances are likely developed to express the important aspects of their environment and daily life
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;the way to talk -&amp;gt; linguistic practices
&lt;br /&gt;
include = just add
&lt;br /&gt;
incorporate = mix together
&lt;br /&gt;
north part of the earth -&amp;gt; northern part of the earth
&lt;br /&gt;
linguistic practices, linguistic nuances
&lt;br /&gt;
developed to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
but we can also learn their culture from their food, clothes, building eventhough they can not express everything about it.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
But we can also learn about their culture through their food, clothing, and architecture, even though they may not be able to fully express everything about it through language.
&lt;br /&gt;
learn from -&amp;gt; learn through
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;express everything -&amp;gt; fully express everything
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;eventhough -&amp;gt; even though
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q some people think that a person can never understand the culture of a country unless they speak the language. do you agree with this opinion? A we sometimes can see the argument that says languages have only few origins.however, with the time progression, human species have gained the diversity in language to meet each other’s needs of expression which varies across the country. this development bring languages to be interwined with culture. someone argue we can’t learn another culture unless learning language. i will elaborate my perspective of view with this argument in the following paragraph further. revise</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing language 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-language-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing language 2" /><published>2023-05-21T06:53:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-21T06:53:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing%20language%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/21/writing-language-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
scientist predict that all people will choose to take the same global language in the future
&lt;br /&gt;
do you think this is a positive or negative development?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
even though languages are developed from common origins, they have been shaped by different countries in order to meet human needs. since england conquar the substantial numbers of countries, making them as colony under control, huge number of countries have been using english as mother toung. in contemporary world, this thing at that time resulting in making english as global language around the world. some sientists argue that all people will use english eventually and i will explain my perspective in the following paragraph further.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Even though languages have common origins, they have been shaped by different countries to meet human needs. Due to England’s conquest of numerous countries and their colonization, a significant number of nations have adopted English as their mother tongue. In the contemporary world, this historical development has led to English becoming a global language. Some scientists argue that eventually, everyone will use English. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this viewpoint.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;developed from common origins -&amp;gt; have common origins
&lt;br /&gt;
substantial number of -&amp;gt; numerous
&lt;br /&gt;
have been using ~ as mother toung -&amp;gt; adopted ~ as their mother toung
&lt;br /&gt;
this thing at that time -&amp;gt; historical development
&lt;br /&gt;
explain -&amp;gt; elaborate on
&lt;br /&gt;
about this -&amp;gt; regarding this viewpoint
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;using same language as mother toung around the world can make us to communicate more easily which enabling us to enhance techonology more fastely. however this can be problem since that development doesn’t necessarily resulting in language becomming optimized to our needs to expression. if we loose variety by choosing one language, when are in situation which we needs of express something which can’t accomplished by english, we have no way to express that due to eradicate another languages. this phenomenon is called model collapse in ai terms.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Using the same language as a mother tongue around the world can make communication easier, enabling faster technological advancements. However, this can also be problematic as such development does not necessarily lead to the language becoming optimized for our expressive needs. If we lose linguistic diversity by adopting a single language, we may find ourselves in situations where we need to express something that cannot be adequately conveyed in English. In such cases, we would have no means to express those ideas because we have already eradicated other languages. This phenomenon is referred to as “model collapse” in AI terms.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;be problem -&amp;gt; be problematic
&lt;br /&gt;
that development -&amp;gt; such development
&lt;br /&gt;
optimized to our needs to expression -&amp;gt; optimized for our expressive needs
&lt;br /&gt;
variety -&amp;gt; linguistic diversity
&lt;br /&gt;
choose -&amp;gt; adopt
&lt;br /&gt;
one -&amp;gt; single
&lt;br /&gt;
when are in situation -&amp;gt; we may find ourselves in situations where
&lt;br /&gt;
express something accomplished by -&amp;gt; express something cannot conveyed in
&lt;br /&gt;
then -&amp;gt; in such cases
&lt;br /&gt;
is called -&amp;gt; is referred to as&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q scientist predict that all people will choose to take the same global language in the future do you think this is a positive or negative development? A even though languages are developed from common origins, they have been shaped by different countries in order to meet human needs. since england conquar the substantial numbers of countries, making them as colony under control, huge number of countries have been using english as mother toung. in contemporary world, this thing at that time resulting in making english as global language around the world. some sientists argue that all people will use english eventually and i will explain my perspective in the following paragraph further. revise</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing language 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/20/writing-language-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing language 1" /><published>2023-05-20T15:53:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-20T15:53:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/20/writing%20language%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/20/writing-language-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As computer translate quickly and accurately, learning fireign languages is a waste of time?
&lt;br /&gt;
to what extend do you agree or disagree
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
throughout human’s history, we struggle to learn another language to communicate with another country to fulfill each other’s needs. as computer science have grown up especially artificial intelligence, computer start learning multiple language together resulting in becoming capable of translating. today, some people even say our need to learn foreign language becomming deminishing. i’m not agree with them and will explain the reason in the following paragraph further.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Throughout human history, we have strived to learn different languages in order to communicate with people from other countries and fulfill each other’s needs. With the advancement of computer science, particularly in the field of artificial intelligence, computers have started to learn multiple languages simultaneously, enabling them to perform translation tasks. Today, some people argue that our need to learn foreign languages is diminishing. However, I disagree with this perspective and will further explain the reasons in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;human’s history -&amp;gt; human history
&lt;br /&gt;
struggle -&amp;gt; strive (struggle = solve difficulty, strive = for goal)
&lt;br /&gt;
to -&amp;gt; in order to
&lt;br /&gt;
learn another language -&amp;gt; learn different languages
&lt;br /&gt;
communicate with country -&amp;gt; communicate people in another country
&lt;br /&gt;
as~ growing up -&amp;gt; with advancement
&lt;br /&gt;
especially ai -&amp;gt; particularilly in the fielf of ai
&lt;br /&gt;
start ing -&amp;gt; have started to
&lt;br /&gt;
at the same time -&amp;gt; simultaneously
&lt;br /&gt;
resulting in becomeing -&amp;gt; enabling them to perform
&lt;br /&gt;
say -&amp;gt; argue
&lt;br /&gt;
don’t agree with them -&amp;gt; disagree with this perspective
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Eventhough languages came from just few common origin, as Language is used as one of means of life of human, it is improved over the time according to human needs. today’s language varies depend on the country and they also reflect their culture. we can understand another’s culture by learning language not only make us to commmunicate easily.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Even though languages have common origins, they have evolved over time to meet the diverse needs of human life. Language serves as a fundamental tool for communication and has been shaped by different countries and cultures. By learning a language, we not only gain the ability to communicate more easily but also develop a deeper understanding of another culture.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;from few origins -&amp;gt; have common origins
&lt;br /&gt;
language is improved -&amp;gt; language have evolved
&lt;br /&gt;
improved according to human needs -&amp;gt; evolved to meet diverse needs
&lt;br /&gt;
one of means of human life -&amp;gt; fundamental tool for communication
&lt;br /&gt;
varies depend on country -&amp;gt; shaped by different countries
&lt;br /&gt;
make us communicate easily -&amp;gt; gain ability to communicate easily
&lt;br /&gt;
can understand -&amp;gt; develop deeper understanding&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and also there is big problem when we don’t learn language anymore and fully resort at translater. we can’t supervise whether ai translate language properly or not which will arise or incurring misunderstanding across the country.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
And also, there is a significant problem when we no longer learn languages and solely rely on translators. We are unable to supervise whether AI translates languages accurately, which can lead to misunderstandings across countries.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;big -&amp;gt; significant
&lt;br /&gt;
don’t anymore -&amp;gt; no longer
&lt;br /&gt;
fully -&amp;gt; solely
&lt;br /&gt;
can’t -&amp;gt; unable
&lt;br /&gt;
properly -&amp;gt; accurately
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in conclution, we have necessairly to learn foreign language because of disadvantages occered from not learning them and advantages which are unable to be accomplished from simply using translater.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, it is necessary for us to learn foreign languages due to the disadvantages that arise from not learning them and the advantages that cannot be achieved by simply relying on translators.
&lt;br /&gt;
because of -&amp;gt; due to
&lt;br /&gt;
occered from -&amp;gt; arise from
&lt;br /&gt;
accomplish -&amp;gt; are achieved&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q As computer translate quickly and accurately, learning fireign languages is a waste of time? to what extend do you agree or disagree A throughout human’s history, we struggle to learn another language to communicate with another country to fulfill each other’s needs. as computer science have grown up especially artificial intelligence, computer start learning multiple language together resulting in becoming capable of translating. today, some people even say our need to learn foreign language becomming deminishing. i’m not agree with them and will explain the reason in the following paragraph further. revise</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing art 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing-art-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing art 3" /><published>2023-05-19T09:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-19T09:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing%20art%203</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing-art-3.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people think that art is an essential subject for children at school while others think it is waste of time
&lt;br /&gt;
discuss both sides and give your opinion
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
through history, art always goes together with human species. maybe it was someday just one part of prey, or it could be one of tools for communicate. regardless of no one clearly know when it is started and how they came from, it is still play the some role in these days society. there is contraversal over the meaning of art and i will explain my aspect of these contraversal in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Throughout history, art has always been intertwined with the human species. It may have been used for prayers to deities or as a means of communication between individuals. Despite the lack of clarity regarding its origins and beginnings, it continues to play a significant role in today’s society. There is controversy surrounding the meaning of art, and in the following paragraph, I will explain my perspective on this controversy.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;through -&amp;gt; throughout
&lt;br /&gt;
goes together with -&amp;gt; interwined with
&lt;br /&gt;
maybe it was somedays -&amp;gt; it may have been past (!= have been past)
&lt;br /&gt;
god -&amp;gt; deities (god = only one)
&lt;br /&gt;
tools for ~ -&amp;gt; means of ~
&lt;br /&gt;
when it was started, how come -&amp;gt; beginning origin
&lt;br /&gt;
still -&amp;gt; continues to
&lt;br /&gt;
these days -&amp;gt; todays
&lt;br /&gt;
contraversal -&amp;gt; controversy
&lt;br /&gt;
my aspect of -&amp;gt; my perspective on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i firstly wanna say art education is not meaningless. every human behavior has their own meaning at the aspect of pursuing the happier life. we earn to eat more edible food and live in more livable house and more which things giving us preasure. if we can get presure without earning, it is also another plausable way to live. eventhough there is less people to demand your art so you can’t earn plenty of money, you still satisfy of your job also even resulting in less consumption of money for another things to gain happiness. as educating art result in peoples to be more skillful, their work becoming more demandable eventually resulting in they to live more happily.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I firstly want to say that art education is not meaningless. Every human behavior has its own meaning in terms of pursuing a happier life. We earn to have more edible food, live in a more livable house, and acquire things that bring us pleasure. However, if we can find fulfillment without solely focusing on earning, it is also a plausible way to live. Even if there are fewer people demanding your art and you can’t earn a substantial amount of money, you can still find satisfaction in your job. This can even lead to reduced consumption of money on other things, as you prioritize the pursuit of happiness. As art education equips people with skills, their work becomes more in demand, eventually resulting in a happier life for them.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;every ~ their -&amp;gt; every ~ its (singular)
&lt;br /&gt;
at the aspect of -&amp;gt; in terms of
&lt;br /&gt;
acquire
&lt;br /&gt;
things giving us pleasure -&amp;gt;things bring us pleasure
&lt;br /&gt;
get pleasure -&amp;gt; find fulfillment
&lt;br /&gt;
there is less people -&amp;gt; there are fewer people
&lt;br /&gt;
plenty -&amp;gt; substantial amount of
&lt;br /&gt;
satisfy of job -&amp;gt; find satisfaction in
&lt;br /&gt;
consumption of money for food-&amp;gt; consumption of money on food
&lt;br /&gt;
become more demanding -&amp;gt; become more sought after, becomes more in demand&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
but it doesn’t means art education should be essentional. we can’t repel someone to learn another things that does not helpful for his life. if we learn everything like this way, we can’t be professional at any subject. someone want to learn art but someone doesn’t. as i said before, we should respect every single person’s inclination.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
However, this does not imply that art education should be deemed essential for everyone. We cannot impose upon individuals to learn something that may not be directly beneficial to their lives. If we attempt to learn everything in this manner, we would be unable to specialize and become experts in any particular field. It is important to recognize that while some individuals may have a passion for art and choose to pursue it, others may not share the same inclination. As mentioned earlier, it is crucial to respect and honor each person’s unique interests and inclinations.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;means -&amp;gt; imply
&lt;br /&gt;
subject should be essential -&amp;gt; subject should be deemed essential 
&lt;br /&gt;
repel -&amp;gt; impose
&lt;br /&gt;
helpful -&amp;gt; beneficial
&lt;br /&gt;
like this way -&amp;gt; in this manner
&lt;br /&gt;
at any subject -&amp;gt; in any particular field
&lt;br /&gt;
as i mentioned before -&amp;gt; as mentioned earlier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
in conclution, as our every bahavior aim to live happier whether that behavior guarantee to make us happier or not, we pursuing our own way to getting happier. studing art is one of the way of getting happier but at the same time not the only to be happier therefore we have to give option to students if they will learn art or not but we just should not compel everyone to learn samely
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, since every individual’s behavior aims to live a happier life, whether that behavior guarantees happiness or not, we each pursue our own path to happiness. Studying art is one way to find happiness, but it is not the only way. Therefore, we should provide students with the option to choose whether or not to learn art, and we should not force everyone to learn the same thing.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;we pursuing -&amp;gt; we each pursue
&lt;br /&gt;
one of the way to -&amp;gt; one way of
&lt;br /&gt;
give -&amp;gt; provide
&lt;br /&gt;
option to students if or not -&amp;gt; option to choose whether or not
&lt;br /&gt;
learn samely -&amp;gt; learn the same thing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q some people think that art is an essential subject for children at school while others think it is waste of time discuss both sides and give your opinion A through history, art always goes together with human species. maybe it was someday just one part of prey, or it could be one of tools for communicate. regardless of no one clearly know when it is started and how they came from, it is still play the some role in these days society. there is contraversal over the meaning of art and i will explain my aspect of these contraversal in the following paragraph. revised</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing art 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing-art-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing art 2" /><published>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing%20art%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing-art-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
art is considered an essential part of all cultures throughout the world. however, these days fewer and fewer people appreciate art and turn their focus to science, technology and business.
&lt;br /&gt;
why do you think that is?
&lt;br /&gt;
what could be done to encourage more people to take inerest in the arts?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
cultures over the world has their own color which is usually expressed in the form of art which has taken diverse form and appears in wall engraving, sound or dance and so on. as times going on, the lives of people getting lake of leasure which incurring the lessening interest on the art which doesn’t directly influence on their lives. I will explain my perspective of the reasion of this phenomenon and the solution in the furture paragraph
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Cultures around the world possess their own unique colors, often expressed through diverse forms of art such as wall engravings, music, dance, and more. However, as time progresses, people’s lives have become increasingly devoid of leisure, resulting in a diminished interest in art that does not directly impact their daily lives. In the following paragraphs, I will explain my perspective on the reasons behind this phenomenon and propose potential solutions for the future.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;over the world -&amp;gt; around the world
&lt;br /&gt;
expressed in -&amp;gt; expressed through
&lt;br /&gt;
and so on -&amp;gt; and more
&lt;br /&gt;
as times going on -&amp;gt; as time progresses + have pp
&lt;br /&gt;
getting lake of leasure -&amp;gt; become increasingly devoid of leasure
&lt;br /&gt;
incurring in -&amp;gt; resulting in
&lt;br /&gt;
lessening -&amp;gt; deminished
&lt;br /&gt;
lives -&amp;gt; daily lives
&lt;br /&gt;
reason of this phenonmoon -&amp;gt; reason behind this phenonmon
&lt;br /&gt;
solution in the future -&amp;gt; solution for the future&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The main reason of people to getting devoid of leasure is their lives are becomming hard to fulfill even their basic needs. which phenomenon arised from unsensible policy which are only made for wealthy people, resulting in increasing disparity between poverty and wealthy. The issue is wealthy occupy only small portion of all population and else occupy the most part of it. so this phenomenon leads to conclution of people to prioritize other one than art.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The main reason people are becoming devoid of leisure is the increasing difficulty in fulfilling their basic needs. This phenomenon arises from unjust policies that predominantly benefit the wealthy, consequently widening the gap between poverty and wealth. The issue lies in the fact that a smaller and smaller portion of the population possesses wealth, while more and more people face economic challenges over time. As a result, people are inclined to prioritize other aspects of life over art.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;becoming hard to -&amp;gt; increasing difficulty in
&lt;br /&gt;
unsensible -&amp;gt; unjust
&lt;br /&gt;
policy that made for wealthy -&amp;gt; policy that banefit the wealthy
&lt;br /&gt;
increasing disparity -&amp;gt; widening
&lt;br /&gt;
people to -&amp;gt; people are inclined to
&lt;br /&gt;
priortize other one than art -&amp;gt; priortize other aspects of life over art&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
i believe we cannot solve this problem by just increasing the quality of art because the criteria of art also changing while quality of art increase. i think the most sensible solution in this situation is making people to be relized of this phenomen and making sound to government to increasing tex for just wealthy who is top earning of the world. regardless of their power, we can achieve the happy world if we don’t fight next person and aim to common end.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I believe we cannot solve this problem by simply increasing the quality of art because the criteria for art also change as the quality of art improves. I think the most sensible solution in this situation is to raise people’s awareness of this phenomenon and advocate for the government to increase taxes for the wealthy, who are the top earners in the world. Regardless of their power, we can achieve a happier world if we refrain from fighting against one another and strive towards a common goal.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;just -&amp;gt; simply
&lt;br /&gt;
criteria of art -&amp;gt; criteria for art
&lt;br /&gt;
quality of art increase -&amp;gt; quality of art improves
&lt;br /&gt;
make sound to -&amp;gt; advocate
&lt;br /&gt;
make people to be realized -&amp;gt; raise people’s awareness
&lt;br /&gt;
top earning of the world -&amp;gt; top earners in the world
&lt;br /&gt;
don’t -&amp;gt; refrain from
&lt;br /&gt;
fight next person -&amp;gt; fighting against one another
&lt;br /&gt;
aim to -&amp;gt; strive towards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclution, the phenomenon people to increasingly devoid art arises from disparity of wealth and poverty, not from innate problem of art or from people’s low comprehensive in terms of art. we can solve this problem by gathering together and advocate government to texing higher on the wealthy.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, the phenomenon of people becoming increasingly deprived of art arises from the disparity between wealth and poverty, rather than from an inherent problem with art or from people’s lack of understanding of art. We can address this issue by coming together and advocating for higher taxes on the wealthy from the government.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;the phenomenon people to -&amp;gt; the phenomenon of people ing
&lt;br /&gt;
disparity of -&amp;gt; disparity between
&lt;br /&gt;
not -&amp;gt; rather than
&lt;br /&gt;
innate problem of art -&amp;gt; inherent problem with art
&lt;br /&gt;
solve this problem -&amp;gt; address this issue
&lt;br /&gt;
gathering together -&amp;gt; comming together
&lt;br /&gt;
advocate government to -&amp;gt; advocate for (context) from government
&lt;br /&gt;
tex to the wealthy -&amp;gt; tex on the wealthy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q art is considered an essential part of all cultures throughout the world. however, these days fewer and fewer people appreciate art and turn their focus to science, technology and business. why do you think that is? what could be done to encourage more people to take inerest in the arts? A cultures over the world has their own color which is usually expressed in the form of art which has taken diverse form and appears in wall engraving, sound or dance and so on. as times going on, the lives of people getting lake of leasure which incurring the lessening interest on the art which doesn’t directly influence on their lives. I will explain my perspective of the reasion of this phenomenon and the solution in the furture paragraph revised</summary></entry></feed>