<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-07-15T20:21:24+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing food 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/15/writing-food-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing food 2" /><published>2023-07-15T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-15T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/15/writing%20food%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/15/writing-food-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
with a fast pace of modern life more and more people are turning towards fast food for their main meals.
&lt;br /&gt;
do you think the advantages outweigh the disadvantages?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
With modernization over the world, people are becomming more and more busy. According to this situation, consumption of fast food increasing. some argue that we should restrict consumption of fast food. in the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument through explaining about pros and cons of consumption of fast food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With modernization taking place worldwide, people are becoming increasingly busy. As a result, the consumption of fast food is also increasing. Some argue that we should restrict the consumption of fast food. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument by discussing the pros and cons of consuming fast food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;through explaining -&amp;gt; by discussing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As diversity of job increase over time, propertion of people who serve in first industry such like present decreasing. which undoubtedly result in increasing food miles so make us hard to consume various food. Nowadays we come to choose fast food which doesn’t need lots of time or resource. According to research conducted in California, United States, in 2017, on twenties, the rate of daily consumption of fastfood on average on upper 20% wealthy is 30% less than opposite group which means people who can afford healthy food don’t choose fast food because that is unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the diversity of job opportunities increases over time, the proportion of people serving in traditional industries, such as the present, is decreasing. This undoubtedly results in an increase in food miles, making it harder for us to consume a variety of foods. Nowadays, we tend to choose fast food because it requires less time and resources. According to research conducted in California, United States, in 2017, among individuals in their twenties, the average daily consumption rate of fast food in the upper 20% wealthier group was 30% lower than the opposite group. This suggests that people who can afford healthy food often avoid fast food due to its unhealthy nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;first industry -&amp;gt; primary industry
serve -&amp;gt; working
on twenties -&amp;gt; among individuals in their twenties&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However consuming fast food doesn’t absolutely result in losing our health condition. As increasing number of people who worry about their health, lots of healty food company borned which make suppliment for a cheap price which is useful for modern people who spend hard time to consuming necessary nutrition. even though we normaly consume limited and cheap nutrition through fast food, we can consume another essentional nutrition by simply consuming cheap and small suppliment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, consuming fast food doesn’t necessarily lead to a decline in our health condition. With an increasing number of people concerned about their health, numerous healthy food companies have emerged, offering affordable supplements that are beneficial for modern individuals who struggle to obtain necessary nutrition. Even though fast food often provides limited and inexpensive nutrition, we can easily supplement our diet with essential nutrients by incorporating affordable and compact supplements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;losing health condition -&amp;gt; decline health condition
회사가 생겨났다 born -&amp;gt; emerged
suppliment -&amp;gt; supplement&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclution, even though it is hard to consume healthy food and someone have to consume fast food to fit their economic situation, they also can consume important nutrition which they don’t have chance to consume in normal days through consuming suppliment. given these facts, i believe that advantage of leverage fast food overweight the disadvantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, despite the challenges of consuming healthy food and the necessity for some individuals to rely on fast food due to their economic circumstances, they can still obtain essential nutrients they might not have access to on a regular basis through the use of supplements. Considering these factors, I believe that the advantages of leveraging fast food outweigh the disadvantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;because of -&amp;gt; due to
economic situation -&amp;gt; economic circumstances
given these facts -&amp;gt; considering these factors
평소에 on a regular basis
활용하다 leveraging&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q with a fast pace of modern life more and more people are turning towards fast food for their main meals. do you think the advantages outweigh the disadvantages? A With modernization over the world, people are becomming more and more busy. According to this situation, consumption of fast food increasing. some argue that we should restrict consumption of fast food. in the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument through explaining about pros and cons of consumption of fast food.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing food 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing-food-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing food 1" /><published>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing%20food%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing-food-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
with a growing world population one of the most pressing issues is that of feeding such a large number of people. some people think that gm foods offer a viable solution to this problem to what extent do you agree
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As population over the world increase, Some argue that genetic modified foods will be good alternative of real food to sort out depletion of food problem. In the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As the global population continues to increase, some argue that genetically modified foods could be a viable alternative to address the issue of food depletion. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
sort out -&amp;gt; address
&lt;br /&gt;
The development of gene over the time was based on “proper survive” principle which means they should provide good nutrition for animal to survive and also they should be optimized to prospering. But if they don’t have to worry about breed, there is no point to modify their behavior to prospering by decreasing efficiency of providing nutrition. so there are still many ways to make plant improve in our favor without any side effect. Additionally,According to the investigation conducted in California, United States, on the residents about cancer rate between who continue to consuming genetic modified food regularly and who didn’t, surprisingly the ratio of occurence of cancer in formar group was rather more lower than later group by 0.0003%. even though they didn’t account for another varience to rule out such as wealthyness, gender, workplace, at least we don’t have any proper reason to deduce GM food are harm for our health. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The development of genes over time has been based on the principle of ‘proper survival,’ which means they should provide good nutrition for animals to survive and optimize their chances of prospering. However, if there is no concern about breeding, there is no point in modifying their behavior to prioritize prospering at the expense of decreased nutritional efficiency. Therefore, there are still many ways to improve plants in our favor without any adverse side effects. Additionally, according to an investigation conducted in California, United States, comparing the cancer rates between residents who regularly consume genetically modified food and those who don’t, the occurrence of cancer in the former group was surprisingly lower by 0.0003% compared to the latter group. Although this study did not account for other variables such as wealth, gender, or workplace, it provides no substantial reason to deduce that GM foods are harmful to our health.
&lt;br /&gt;
survival of the fittest
at the cost of
later -&amp;gt; latter
&lt;br /&gt;
However, we have to think about if GM foods are only one solution to takle with deplation of food problem. Some people just grown their own plant or animal to eat so it doesn’t seems make sense that food depletion can be problem. i think the root of problem is inconsistent density of population which brings city side people to feel the price of food as expensive which is result of additional transportation and maintainence fee. so if we just make food more, this can simply suffocate local farmar without solving root problem.
&lt;br /&gt;
However, we must consider whether GM foods are the only solution to tackle the issue of food depletion. Some people choose to grow their own plants or raise animals for consumption, making the concept of food depletion seem less relevant. I believe the root problem lies in the uneven distribution of population density, which leads urban dwellers to perceive food prices as expensive due to additional transportation and maintenance costs. Simply increasing food production could potentially suffocate local farmers without addressing the underlying problem.”
&lt;br /&gt;
if -&amp;gt; whether
inconsistent -&amp;gt; uneven
root problem -&amp;gt; underlying problem
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, we can conclude GM is good way to make food because development process of food is not optimized to good for human so it can be improved more without any side effect. However the problem with the food can be not necessairy came from food depletation so it is possible that we cannot solve that problem by making more food easily.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, we can conclude that genetic modification is a good approach to improving food production as the development process of food is not optimized solely for human benefit. It can be further improved without significant side effects. However, it is important to note that the problem with food may not necessarily arise solely from food depletion. Therefore, simply increasing food production may not be the easy solution to address the underlying problem.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
way -&amp;gt; approach
came from -&amp;gt; arise from
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q with a growing world population one of the most pressing issues is that of feeding such a large number of people. some people think that gm foods offer a viable solution to this problem to what extent do you agree A As population over the world increase, Some argue that genetic modified foods will be good alternative of real food to sort out depletion of food problem. In the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. As the global population continues to increase, some argue that genetically modified foods could be a viable alternative to address the issue of food depletion. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. sort out -&amp;gt; address The development of gene over the time was based on “proper survive” principle which means they should provide good nutrition for animal to survive and also they should be optimized to prospering. But if they don’t have to worry about breed, there is no point to modify their behavior to prospering by decreasing efficiency of providing nutrition. so there are still many ways to make plant improve in our favor without any side effect. Additionally,According to the investigation conducted in California, United States, on the residents about cancer rate between who continue to consuming genetic modified food regularly and who didn’t, surprisingly the ratio of occurence of cancer in formar group was rather more lower than later group by 0.0003%. even though they didn’t account for another varience to rule out such as wealthyness, gender, workplace, at least we don’t have any proper reason to deduce GM food are harm for our health. The development of genes over time has been based on the principle of ‘proper survival,’ which means they should provide good nutrition for animals to survive and optimize their chances of prospering. However, if there is no concern about breeding, there is no point in modifying their behavior to prioritize prospering at the expense of decreased nutritional efficiency. Therefore, there are still many ways to improve plants in our favor without any adverse side effects. Additionally, according to an investigation conducted in California, United States, comparing the cancer rates between residents who regularly consume genetically modified food and those who don’t, the occurrence of cancer in the former group was surprisingly lower by 0.0003% compared to the latter group. Although this study did not account for other variables such as wealth, gender, or workplace, it provides no substantial reason to deduce that GM foods are harmful to our health. survival of the fittest at the cost of later -&amp;gt; latter However, we have to think about if GM foods are only one solution to takle with deplation of food problem. Some people just grown their own plant or animal to eat so it doesn’t seems make sense that food depletion can be problem. i think the root of problem is inconsistent density of population which brings city side people to feel the price of food as expensive which is result of additional transportation and maintainence fee. so if we just make food more, this can simply suffocate local farmar without solving root problem. However, we must consider whether GM foods are the only solution to tackle the issue of food depletion. Some people choose to grow their own plants or raise animals for consumption, making the concept of food depletion seem less relevant. I believe the root problem lies in the uneven distribution of population density, which leads urban dwellers to perceive food prices as expensive due to additional transportation and maintenance costs. Simply increasing food production could potentially suffocate local farmers without addressing the underlying problem.” if -&amp;gt; whether inconsistent -&amp;gt; uneven root problem -&amp;gt; underlying problem In summary, we can conclude GM is good way to make food because development process of food is not optimized to good for human so it can be improved more without any side effect. However the problem with the food can be not necessairy came from food depletation so it is possible that we cannot solve that problem by making more food easily. In summary, we can conclude that genetic modification is a good approach to improving food production as the development process of food is not optimized solely for human benefit. It can be further improved without significant side effects. However, it is important to note that the problem with food may not necessarily arise solely from food depletion. Therefore, simply increasing food production may not be the easy solution to address the underlying problem. way -&amp;gt; approach came from -&amp;gt; arise from</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing tourism 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing-tourism-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing tourism 1" /><published>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing%20tourism%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing-tourism-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
tourism is evergrowing industry
what benefits do you think tourism brings to individual and industry?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
With the globalization over the world, which includes modernization of transportation system, it becomes increasingly easy to travel across the countries. traveling another countries is probably great experience for travelers but we want to know the effect on local society and citizens of travel industry. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding pros and cons of these phenomenon.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With globalization affecting the entire world, including the modernization of transportation systems, it has become increasingly easy to travel across countries. Traveling to other countries is undoubtedly a great experience for travelers, but it is important to consider the effects on local societies and citizens within the travel industry. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding the pros and cons of this phenomenon
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
becomes -&amp;gt; has become
travel -&amp;gt; travel to
obviously -&amp;gt; undoubtedly
local society -&amp;gt; local societies
effect on ~ of -&amp;gt; effect on ~ within&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To discuss with the aspect of local society, because tourists use lots of money in the excuse of experience even to the normal stuff which is not worth that money, common people can easily get in the black. government can set small market to make tourist experience another culture easily and common people can pay them for trade their stuff at the crowded environment. morever, if goverment architect some museum or art gallary, they can earn money permemently by simply selling ticket with minimal conservative process .they can earn great amount of profit like that way so they take the risk of posibility of another crime and destruction of environment on the certain extent.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To discuss the impact on local society, it is important to note that tourists often spend a significant amount of money, even on ordinary items that may not warrant such expenses. This can lead to a negative influence on the local community, as common people can easily become involved in illicit activities. To address this, the government can establish small markets that allow tourists to experience different cultures while providing opportunities for locals to engage in trade within a bustling environment. Furthermore, if the government constructs museums or art galleries, they can generate consistent revenue by selling tickets with minimal administrative processes. Although this approach can yield substantial profits, it also carries risks such as potential crime and environmental damage, albeit to a certain extent.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
discussing with -&amp;gt; to discuss
normal stuff -&amp;gt; ordinary item
worth that money -&amp;gt; warrant such expenses
get in the black
trade in -&amp;gt; trade within
leave the profit -&amp;gt; generate revenue, yield profit
maintenance cost
dispite of -&amp;gt; albeit to
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
On the other hand, tourist can serve the role of sharing the culture so individuals have more opportunity to learn other culture, especially their habitat, so they can evaluate their own culture from one step back and they can revolute by burden old and bad habitat and accept new habitat. additionally they also have apportunity to learn another language and start relationship with another countries people. even though they are always inherit the risk since we didn’t fully understand how they are, but we always need some challenge to change.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
On the other hand, tourists can play a crucial role in sharing cultures, providing individuals with more opportunities to learn about other cultures, particularly the local customs and ways of life. This exposure allows them to evaluate their own culture from a different perspective and potentially bring about positive changes by shedding old and negative practices while embracing new ones. Additionally, tourists have the chance to learn new languages and establish relationships with people from other countries. Although there is always an inherent risk in encountering the unfamiliar, it is through such challenges that we can foster growth and transformation.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
role of -&amp;gt; role in
habitat -&amp;gt; customs
burden -&amp;gt; shedding
custom -&amp;gt; practice
start relationship -&amp;gt; establish relationship
foster growth
change -&amp;gt; transformation
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
in summary, i discussed about advantage and disadvantage of tourist industry so far. tourism is highly profitable for local industry by share our cultrue through market, museum, gallary and more. Moreover that is also beneficial to individual at the aspect of habitat, education, relationship and so on. therefore i believe improve tourism must be rewarding for everyone.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, I have discussed the advantages and disadvantages of the tourism industry thus far. Tourism proves to be highly profitable for local industries as it allows for the sharing of our culture through markets, museums, galleries, and more. Furthermore, it benefits individuals in terms of their understanding of different habitats, educational opportunities, and the establishment of relationships, among other aspects. Therefore, I firmly believe that the improvement and development of tourism can be rewarding for everyone involved.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
so far -&amp;gt; thus far
and so on -&amp;gt; among other aspects
everyone -&amp;gt; everyone involved&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q tourism is evergrowing industry what benefits do you think tourism brings to individual and industry? A With the globalization over the world, which includes modernization of transportation system, it becomes increasingly easy to travel across the countries. traveling another countries is probably great experience for travelers but we want to know the effect on local society and citizens of travel industry. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding pros and cons of these phenomenon. With globalization affecting the entire world, including the modernization of transportation systems, it has become increasingly easy to travel across countries. Traveling to other countries is undoubtedly a great experience for travelers, but it is important to consider the effects on local societies and citizens within the travel industry. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding the pros and cons of this phenomenon becomes -&amp;gt; has become travel -&amp;gt; travel to obviously -&amp;gt; undoubtedly local society -&amp;gt; local societies effect on ~ of -&amp;gt; effect on ~ within</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing sports 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/13/writing-sports-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing sports 1" /><published>2023-07-13T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-13T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/13/writing%20sports%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/13/writing-sports-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people think dangerous sports should be banned while others think people should be free to choose.
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
with modernization of the world, the techonology used to support sports improved, so enabling us to challenge more and more dangerous sports. Some argue we should forbid dangerous sports so as to prevent occerance of decreased. I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With the modernization of the world, the technology used to support sports has improved, enabling us to engage in increasingly challenging and potentially dangerous activities. Some argue that we should prohibit dangerous sports to prevent occurrences of harm. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
more and more -&amp;gt; increasingly
forbid -&amp;gt; prohibit
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
sports have plenty of beneficial aspect. we can improve our socialization skill by communicate each other in multi player sports, we can relieve stress and improve our health by enjoying physical activity, we even improve our motor skill by e-sports which doesn’t require stemina. But i belive the most rewarding aspect of sports is experience. as our equipment are enhanced over the time, we can try many kinds of activitys didn’t abled to before. nowadays we eventually learn various skills through mordanized sports which situation allow us to improve ability dealing with many different problems by different skills.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sports have plenty of beneficial aspects. We can improve our socialization skills by communicating with each other in multiplayer sports. We can relieve stress and enhance our health by engaging in physical activities. Additionally, even in e-sports, which do not require stamina, we can improve our motor skills. However, I believe the most rewarding aspect of sports is the experience itself. As our equipment continues to advance over time, we can explore and participate in various activities that were previously inaccessible. Nowadays, modernized sports allow us to learn a wide range of skills, enabling us to enhance our ability to tackle different problems using different approaches.
&lt;br /&gt;
try -&amp;gt; explore participate
deal -&amp;gt; tackle
different approaches
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
According to one investigation conducted at california states of US on twenty generation, the decreased by sports are decreasing as their proficiency increasing. For example, the people dead rate while scuba diving is totally 0.01% but 80% of that portion was occupied by people who’s experience of diving is less than 50times even though average experience time of diving was 200times. the lesson we can learn with this experience is dangerous sports itself doesn’t affect the possibility of critical injury but insufficient understanding of sports itself.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, spanning twenty generations, the occurrence of accidents in sports is decreasing as proficiency levels increase. For instance, the fatality rate while scuba diving is only 0.01%. However, 80% of these incidents involve individuals with less than 50 diving experiences, despite the average diving experience being 200 times. The lesson we can learn from this is that the inherent danger in sports does not necessarily determine the likelihood of critical injuries; rather, it is often attributed to a lack of understanding and knowledge about the sport itself
&lt;br /&gt;
California, United States,
twenties
proficiency level
fatality
inherent
attributed to
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, what i would like to state is the riskness of sports are not based on defficulty but understanding of that sports. moreover, since benefit of experiencing new sports are invaluable we can’t restrict the range of available sports. In conclution, I think we have to be care of education of security than just ban the sports. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, what I would like to emphasize is that the level of risk in sports is not solely determined by their difficulty but rather by our understanding of those sports. Furthermore, considering the invaluable benefits of experiencing new sports, we should not restrict the range of available activities. In conclusion, I believe it is essential to prioritize education on safety measures rather than simply banning certain sports.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
based on -&amp;gt; solely determined by
education on safety measure
just -&amp;gt; simply
then
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q some people think dangerous sports should be banned while others think people should be free to choose. A with modernization of the world, the techonology used to support sports improved, so enabling us to challenge more and more dangerous sports. Some argue we should forbid dangerous sports so as to prevent occerance of decreased. I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument in the following paragraph. With the modernization of the world, the technology used to support sports has improved, enabling us to engage in increasingly challenging and potentially dangerous activities. Some argue that we should prohibit dangerous sports to prevent occurrences of harm. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. more and more -&amp;gt; increasingly forbid -&amp;gt; prohibit sports have plenty of beneficial aspect. we can improve our socialization skill by communicate each other in multi player sports, we can relieve stress and improve our health by enjoying physical activity, we even improve our motor skill by e-sports which doesn’t require stemina. But i belive the most rewarding aspect of sports is experience. as our equipment are enhanced over the time, we can try many kinds of activitys didn’t abled to before. nowadays we eventually learn various skills through mordanized sports which situation allow us to improve ability dealing with many different problems by different skills. Sports have plenty of beneficial aspects. We can improve our socialization skills by communicating with each other in multiplayer sports. We can relieve stress and enhance our health by engaging in physical activities. Additionally, even in e-sports, which do not require stamina, we can improve our motor skills. However, I believe the most rewarding aspect of sports is the experience itself. As our equipment continues to advance over time, we can explore and participate in various activities that were previously inaccessible. Nowadays, modernized sports allow us to learn a wide range of skills, enabling us to enhance our ability to tackle different problems using different approaches. try -&amp;gt; explore participate deal -&amp;gt; tackle different approaches According to one investigation conducted at california states of US on twenty generation, the decreased by sports are decreasing as their proficiency increasing. For example, the people dead rate while scuba diving is totally 0.01% but 80% of that portion was occupied by people who’s experience of diving is less than 50times even though average experience time of diving was 200times. the lesson we can learn with this experience is dangerous sports itself doesn’t affect the possibility of critical injury but insufficient understanding of sports itself. According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, spanning twenty generations, the occurrence of accidents in sports is decreasing as proficiency levels increase. For instance, the fatality rate while scuba diving is only 0.01%. However, 80% of these incidents involve individuals with less than 50 diving experiences, despite the average diving experience being 200 times. The lesson we can learn from this is that the inherent danger in sports does not necessarily determine the likelihood of critical injuries; rather, it is often attributed to a lack of understanding and knowledge about the sport itself California, United States, twenties proficiency level fatality inherent attributed to In summary, what i would like to state is the riskness of sports are not based on defficulty but understanding of that sports. moreover, since benefit of experiencing new sports are invaluable we can’t restrict the range of available sports. In conclution, I think we have to be care of education of security than just ban the sports. In summary, what I would like to emphasize is that the level of risk in sports is not solely determined by their difficulty but rather by our understanding of those sports. Furthermore, considering the invaluable benefits of experiencing new sports, we should not restrict the range of available activities. In conclusion, I believe it is essential to prioritize education on safety measures rather than simply banning certain sports. based on -&amp;gt; solely determined by education on safety measure just -&amp;gt; simply then</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing reading 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/12/writing-reading-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing reading 1" /><published>2023-07-12T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-12T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/12/writing%20reading%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/12/writing-reading-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
Some people think books are losing importance as a source of information and entertainment. to what extent do you agree?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
with globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to get the information on the internet. some argue books are not important anymore as online website have cumulated immornouse information. i will elaborate on my perspective of this argument further in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With the globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to access information on the internet. Some argue that books are no longer important since online websites have accumulated enormous amounts of information. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
when we read the book with paper, we can protect our eyesight from various dexitorious lights such as microwave and bluelight. morever, we can utilize our aother sensory motor system to appreciate reading mood entirely which eventually award us on some extent of satisfaction and enjoyness.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
When we read a book on paper, we can protect our eyesight from various detrimental lights, such as microwaves and blue light. Moreover, we can engage our other sensory and motor systems to fully appreciate the reading experience, which ultimately rewards us with a certain level of satisfaction and enjoyment.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
however, when it comes to learning, according to one of artificial intelligence researches conducted on agent simulated in the computer from MIT university, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately when we learn following curiousity by maximizing information gain. but when we learn with the book, the information they produce to be obsorved restricted in some aspect besides hard to find which aspect hinder us to learn actively with having curiousity. but when we learn something on the internet, we can search what we used to want to know whenever we want enabling us to learn actively resulting our knowledge optimized.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
However, when it comes to learning, according to one of the artificial intelligence research studies conducted at MIT University on computer-simulated agents, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately by following curiosity and maximizing information gain. On the other hand, learning with books may restrict the information they provide in some aspects, making it difficult to identify the specific areas that hinder active learning and curiosity. In contrast, learning something on the internet allows us to search for the information we want to know whenever we want, enabling us to learn actively and resulting in optimized knowledge
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summerize, I believe the significance of reading the book stay still at the aspect of giving us the sufficient opportunity of feeling fulfillment and enjoy. But they are not most useful means anymore as internet come to us as secondary unlimited and handy resourse of information.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, I believe that the significance of reading books remains in providing us with ample opportunities for fulfillment and enjoyment. However, they are no longer the most useful means, as the internet has emerged as a primary, limitless, and convenient resource of information.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q Some people think books are losing importance as a source of information and entertainment. to what extent do you agree? A with globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to get the information on the internet. some argue books are not important anymore as online website have cumulated immornouse information. i will elaborate on my perspective of this argument further in the following paragraph. With the globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to access information on the internet. Some argue that books are no longer important since online websites have accumulated enormous amounts of information. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument when we read the book with paper, we can protect our eyesight from various dexitorious lights such as microwave and bluelight. morever, we can utilize our aother sensory motor system to appreciate reading mood entirely which eventually award us on some extent of satisfaction and enjoyness. When we read a book on paper, we can protect our eyesight from various detrimental lights, such as microwaves and blue light. Moreover, we can engage our other sensory and motor systems to fully appreciate the reading experience, which ultimately rewards us with a certain level of satisfaction and enjoyment. however, when it comes to learning, according to one of artificial intelligence researches conducted on agent simulated in the computer from MIT university, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately when we learn following curiousity by maximizing information gain. but when we learn with the book, the information they produce to be obsorved restricted in some aspect besides hard to find which aspect hinder us to learn actively with having curiousity. but when we learn something on the internet, we can search what we used to want to know whenever we want enabling us to learn actively resulting our knowledge optimized. However, when it comes to learning, according to one of the artificial intelligence research studies conducted at MIT University on computer-simulated agents, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately by following curiosity and maximizing information gain. On the other hand, learning with books may restrict the information they provide in some aspects, making it difficult to identify the specific areas that hinder active learning and curiosity. In contrast, learning something on the internet allows us to search for the information we want to know whenever we want, enabling us to learn actively and resulting in optimized knowledge In summerize, I believe the significance of reading the book stay still at the aspect of giving us the sufficient opportunity of feeling fulfillment and enjoy. But they are not most useful means anymore as internet come to us as secondary unlimited and handy resourse of information. In summary, I believe that the significance of reading books remains in providing us with ample opportunities for fulfillment and enjoyment. However, they are no longer the most useful means, as the internet has emerged as a primary, limitless, and convenient resource of information.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (variation)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(variation).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (variation)" /><published>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca%20(variation)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(variation).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; variation &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">variation</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (colloqual, words)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(colloqual,-words).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (colloqual, words)" /><published>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca%20(colloqual,%20words)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(colloqual,-words).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; colloqual &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a mass of
&lt;br /&gt;
dozens of
&lt;br /&gt;
tons of
&lt;br /&gt;
umpteen
&lt;br /&gt;
a scrap of
&lt;br /&gt;
I gather
&lt;br /&gt;
Incidentally
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
in excess of
&lt;br /&gt;
somewhere in the region of 
&lt;br /&gt;
or so
&lt;br /&gt;
dash
&lt;br /&gt;
stacks of
&lt;br /&gt;
or whatever
&lt;br /&gt;
and things like that / and that kind of thing.
&lt;br /&gt;
something along those lines
&lt;br /&gt;
or words to that effect
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Mumble
&lt;br /&gt;
mutter
&lt;br /&gt;
slagging off
&lt;br /&gt;
whining
&lt;br /&gt;
chatting away
&lt;br /&gt;
winding him up
&lt;br /&gt;
get tongue-tied
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; words &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;86
&lt;br /&gt;
overhang
&lt;br /&gt;
overshadowed
&lt;br /&gt;
undermine
&lt;br /&gt;
proliferate
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
guilt-ridden
&lt;br /&gt;
crime-ridden
&lt;br /&gt;
bedridden
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
upend
&lt;br /&gt;
end up
&lt;br /&gt;
uphold
&lt;br /&gt;
hold up
&lt;br /&gt;
outdo
&lt;br /&gt;
do out
&lt;br /&gt;
outrun
&lt;br /&gt;
run out
&lt;br /&gt;
upset
&lt;br /&gt;
set up&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">colloqual a mass of dozens of tons of umpteen a scrap of I gather Incidentally in excess of somewhere in the region of or so dash stacks of or whatever and things like that / and that kind of thing. something along those lines or words to that effect Mumble mutter slagging off whining chatting away winding him up get tongue-tied words 86 overhang overshadowed undermine proliferate guilt-ridden crime-ridden bedridden upend end up uphold hold up outdo do out outrun run out upset set up</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (metaphore)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(metaphore).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (metaphore)" /><published>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca%20(metaphore)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(metaphore).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; metaphore &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;formidable
&lt;br /&gt;
dismal
&lt;br /&gt;
ludicrous
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
be on the ball
&lt;br /&gt;
rule of thumb
&lt;br /&gt;
dim
&lt;br /&gt;
trickling
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
threw me completely
&lt;br /&gt;
got our wires crossed
&lt;br /&gt;
I’m not with you. / You’ve lost me there
&lt;br /&gt;
to be fed up to the back teeth
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Come over
&lt;br /&gt;
put forward
&lt;br /&gt;
come off
&lt;br /&gt;
come under
&lt;br /&gt;
stay on
&lt;br /&gt;
dwell on
&lt;br /&gt;
catch on
&lt;br /&gt;
going on
&lt;br /&gt;
brush up on
&lt;br /&gt;
laid off 
&lt;br /&gt;
thrown himself into&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">metaphore formidable dismal ludicrous be on the ball rule of thumb dim trickling threw me completely got our wires crossed I’m not with you. / You’ve lost me there to be fed up to the back teeth Come over put forward come off come under stay on dwell on catch on going on brush up on laid off thrown himself into</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (communication)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(communication).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (communication)" /><published>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca%20(communication)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(communication).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; agree &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;assent
countenance
endorse
clamp down
veto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; complain &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve just about had enough of
this is just not on
I’m not at all satisfied with
I wish to complain about
I take great exception to
I really must object to
grouse *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; apology &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;phoney *
alibi
flimsy pretext
remorse
acquitted
armistice
accord
ceasefire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; compliment &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;back-handed compliment
double-edged compliment
pay tribute to
ovation
extol
plaudit
laud&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; promise &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;promise someone the earth/moon
oath / to swear
swears by
pledge
vowed
wager&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">agree assent countenance endorse clamp down veto</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (regret, academy, agree)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(regret,-academy,-agree).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (regret, academy, agree)" /><published>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca%20(regret,%20academy,%20agree)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(regret,-academy,-agree).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; regret &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;out of touch
&lt;br /&gt;
what became of
&lt;br /&gt;
if I recall
&lt;br /&gt;
think back
&lt;br /&gt;
hear anything of
&lt;br /&gt;
what stands out in my mind
&lt;br /&gt;
reminiscing about
&lt;br /&gt;
through rose-tinted spectacles
&lt;br /&gt;
pangs
&lt;br /&gt;
rue
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; agree &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tally
&lt;br /&gt;
dissent
&lt;br /&gt;
concessions
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; academy &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;authoritative
&lt;br /&gt;
incidence
&lt;br /&gt;
negate
&lt;br /&gt;
thereby
&lt;br /&gt;
whereby
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;expounded
&lt;br /&gt;
posited
&lt;br /&gt;
subsumed
&lt;br /&gt;
allude
&lt;br /&gt;
touch upon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
scribble
&lt;br /&gt;
jot down
&lt;br /&gt;
doodling
&lt;br /&gt;
writing up
&lt;br /&gt;
touch-type
&lt;br /&gt;
run you off&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">regret out of touch what became of if I recall think back hear anything of what stands out in my mind reminiscing about through rose-tinted spectacles pangs rue</summary></entry></feed>