<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-20T23:52:57+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing art 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing art 3" /><published>2023-05-19T09:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-19T09:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing3.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people think that art is an essential subject for children at school while others think it is waste of time
&lt;br /&gt;
discuss both sides and give your opinion
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
through history, art always goes together with human species. maybe it was someday just one part of prey, or it could be one of tools for communicate. regardless of no one clearly know when it is started and how they came from, it is still play the some role in these days society. there is contraversal over the meaning of art and i will explain my aspect of these contraversal in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Throughout history, art has always been intertwined with the human species. It may have been used for prayers to deities or as a means of communication between individuals. Despite the lack of clarity regarding its origins and beginnings, it continues to play a significant role in today’s society. There is controversy surrounding the meaning of art, and in the following paragraph, I will explain my perspective on this controversy.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;through -&amp;gt; throughout
&lt;br /&gt;
goes together with -&amp;gt; interwined with
&lt;br /&gt;
maybe it was somedays -&amp;gt; it may have been past (!= have been past)
&lt;br /&gt;
god -&amp;gt; deities (god = only one)
&lt;br /&gt;
tools for ~ -&amp;gt; means of ~
&lt;br /&gt;
when it was started, how come -&amp;gt; beginning origin
&lt;br /&gt;
still -&amp;gt; continues to
&lt;br /&gt;
these days -&amp;gt; todays
&lt;br /&gt;
contraversal -&amp;gt; controversy
&lt;br /&gt;
my aspect of -&amp;gt; my perspective on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i firstly wanna say art education is not meaningless. every human behavior has their own meaning at the aspect of pursuing the happier life. we earn to eat more edible food and live in more livable house and more which things giving us preasure. if we can get presure without earning, it is also another plausable way to live. eventhough there is less people to demand your art so you can’t earn plenty of money, you still satisfy of your job also even resulting in less consumption of money for another things to gain happiness. as educating art result in peoples to be more skillful, their work becoming more demandable eventually resulting in they to live more happily.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I firstly want to say that art education is not meaningless. Every human behavior has its own meaning in terms of pursuing a happier life. We earn to have more edible food, live in a more livable house, and acquire things that bring us pleasure. However, if we can find fulfillment without solely focusing on earning, it is also a plausible way to live. Even if there are fewer people demanding your art and you can’t earn a substantial amount of money, you can still find satisfaction in your job. This can even lead to reduced consumption of money on other things, as you prioritize the pursuit of happiness. As art education equips people with skills, their work becomes more in demand, eventually resulting in a happier life for them.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;every ~ their -&amp;gt; every ~ its (singular)
&lt;br /&gt;
at the aspect of -&amp;gt; in terms of
&lt;br /&gt;
acquire
&lt;br /&gt;
things giving us pleasure -&amp;gt;things bring us pleasure
&lt;br /&gt;
get pleasure -&amp;gt; find fulfillment
&lt;br /&gt;
there is less people -&amp;gt; there are fewer people
&lt;br /&gt;
plenty -&amp;gt; substantial amount of
&lt;br /&gt;
satisfy of job -&amp;gt; find satisfaction in
&lt;br /&gt;
consumption of money for food-&amp;gt; consumption of money on food
&lt;br /&gt;
become more demanding -&amp;gt; become more sought after, becomes more in demand&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
but it doesn’t means art education should be essentional. we can’t repel someone to learn another things that does not helpful for his life. if we learn everything like this way, we can’t be professional at any subject. someone want to learn art but someone doesn’t. as i said before, we should respect every single person’s inclination.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
However, this does not imply that art education should be deemed essential for everyone. We cannot impose upon individuals to learn something that may not be directly beneficial to their lives. If we attempt to learn everything in this manner, we would be unable to specialize and become experts in any particular field. It is important to recognize that while some individuals may have a passion for art and choose to pursue it, others may not share the same inclination. As mentioned earlier, it is crucial to respect and honor each person’s unique interests and inclinations.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;means -&amp;gt; imply
&lt;br /&gt;
subject should be essential -&amp;gt; subject should be deemed essential 
&lt;br /&gt;
repel -&amp;gt; impose
&lt;br /&gt;
helpful -&amp;gt; beneficial
&lt;br /&gt;
like this way -&amp;gt; in this manner
&lt;br /&gt;
at any subject -&amp;gt; in any particular field
&lt;br /&gt;
as i mentioned before -&amp;gt; as mentioned earlier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
in conclution, as our every bahavior aim to live happier whether that behavior guarantee to make us happier or not, we pursuing our own way to getting happier. studing art is one of the way of getting happier but at the same time not the only to be happier therefore we have to give option to students if they will learn art or not but we just should not compel everyone to learn samely
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, since every individual’s behavior aims to live a happier life, whether that behavior guarantees happiness or not, we each pursue our own path to happiness. Studying art is one way to find happiness, but it is not the only way. Therefore, we should provide students with the option to choose whether or not to learn art, and we should not force everyone to learn the same thing.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;we pursuing -&amp;gt; we each pursue
&lt;br /&gt;
one of the way to -&amp;gt; one way of
&lt;br /&gt;
give -&amp;gt; provide
&lt;br /&gt;
option to students if or not -&amp;gt; option to choose whether or not
&lt;br /&gt;
learn samely -&amp;gt; learn the same thing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q some people think that art is an essential subject for children at school while others think it is waste of time discuss both sides and give your opinion A through history, art always goes together with human species. maybe it was someday just one part of prey, or it could be one of tools for communicate. regardless of no one clearly know when it is started and how they came from, it is still play the some role in these days society. there is contraversal over the meaning of art and i will explain my aspect of these contraversal in the following paragraph. revised</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing art 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing art 1" /><published>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
Some people think that government is wasting money on the arts and that this money could be better spent elsewhere
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To what extent do you agree with this view?
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
Art seems to take up our unconsciousness part which art we were used to express our emotion which cannot expressed in language so it is revealed in various way since the ancient, some is in griving on the wall, some is form of sounds. some people assert art is waste of money and i agree with them on some level and will explain with the following parpgraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Art seems to tap into the unconscious part of ourselves that we struggle to express through language, enabling us to convey our emotions in various ways. Throughout history, art has taken diverse forms, including wall engravings and auditory compositions. While some individuals argue that art is a waste of money, I partially agree with them and will explain my perspective further in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;seems like -&amp;gt; seems to
&lt;br /&gt;
since the ancient -&amp;gt; Throughout history
&lt;br /&gt;
revealed in various way -&amp;gt; has taken diverse forms
&lt;br /&gt;
on some level -&amp;gt; partially
&lt;br /&gt;
with the following paragraph -&amp;gt; in the following paragraph
&lt;br /&gt;
will explain -&amp;gt; will explain my perspective further&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Art has been served as important role in our mental stability. No matter how much we are rich or poor, we like to see beautiful scence and music which seems console and empathy ourselves. so government’s investment to art can improve our lives on some way largly or smally
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Art plays an important role in maintaining our mental stability. Regardless of our wealth or poverty, we all have an innate inclination to appreciate beautiful scenery and music, as they offer solace and evoke empathy within us. Therefore, government investment in art can significantly enhance our lives, whether in significant or subtle ways.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;has been served -&amp;gt; plays
&lt;br /&gt;
mental stability -&amp;gt; maintaining mental stability
&lt;br /&gt;
no matter how -&amp;gt; regardless of 
&lt;br /&gt;
rich or poor -&amp;gt; wealth or poverty
&lt;br /&gt;
like to see -&amp;gt; have an innate inclination to appreciate
&lt;br /&gt;
console -&amp;gt; solace
&lt;br /&gt;
invest to -&amp;gt; invest in
&lt;br /&gt;
largly or smally -&amp;gt; whether in significant or subtle ways&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
but there is some people who are hard to serve even just themselves so they priority basic tools of life over the art which situation comes from increasing difference between wealth and poverty because of matthew effect but that doesn’t come to conclution that art is lake of meaning
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
However, there are people who struggle to fulfill even their basic needs, prioritizing survival over art. This situation arises from the growing wealth and poverty disparity, known as the Matthew effect. Nevertheless, this does not lead to the conclusion that art lacks meaning.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;there is some people -&amp;gt; there are people
&lt;br /&gt;
serve even just themselves -&amp;gt; fulfill even their basic needs
&lt;br /&gt;
basic tools of life -&amp;gt; survival
&lt;br /&gt;
comes from -&amp;gt; arises from
&lt;br /&gt;
difference -&amp;gt; disparity(greater level)
&lt;br /&gt;
because of -&amp;gt; known as
&lt;br /&gt;
come to conclution -&amp;gt; lead to the conclution&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
in the conclution, government doesn’t waste money on the art because art plays inreplaceable rule in society, but government should invest in warefare more to guarantee basic needs of survival resulting in make people can feel pleasure from the art.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, the government should not perceive investment in art as a waste of money, given its irreplaceable role in society. However, the government should prioritize investing more in ensuring basic survival needs, such as welfare, by imposing higher taxes on the wealthy. This approach would ultimately enable people to derive pleasure from art.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;in the conclution -&amp;gt; in conclution
&lt;br /&gt;
view = perceive = consider
&lt;br /&gt;
some behavior is not like that -&amp;gt; should not consider
&lt;br /&gt;
tex more wealthy-&amp;gt; imposing higher taxes on the wealthy
&lt;br /&gt;
to feel pleasure from art -&amp;gt; to derive pleasure from art&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q Some people think that government is wasting money on the arts and that this money could be better spent elsewhere To what extent do you agree with this view? A Art seems to take up our unconsciousness part which art we were used to express our emotion which cannot expressed in language so it is revealed in various way since the ancient, some is in griving on the wall, some is form of sounds. some people assert art is waste of money and i agree with them on some level and will explain with the following parpgraph. revised</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing art 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing art 2" /><published>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
art is considered an essential part of all cultures throughout the world. however, these days fewer and fewer people appreciate art and turn their focus to science, technology and business.
&lt;br /&gt;
why do you think that is?
&lt;br /&gt;
what could be done to encourage more people to take inerest in the arts?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
cultures over the world has their own color which is usually expressed in the form of art which has taken diverse form and appears in wall engraving, sound or dance and so on. as times going on, the lives of people getting lake of leasure which incurring the lessening interest on the art which doesn’t directly influence on their lives. I will explain my perspective of the reasion of this phenomenon and the solution in the furture paragraph
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Cultures around the world possess their own unique colors, often expressed through diverse forms of art such as wall engravings, music, dance, and more. However, as time progresses, people’s lives have become increasingly devoid of leisure, resulting in a diminished interest in art that does not directly impact their daily lives. In the following paragraphs, I will explain my perspective on the reasons behind this phenomenon and propose potential solutions for the future.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;over the world -&amp;gt; around the world
&lt;br /&gt;
expressed in -&amp;gt; expressed through
&lt;br /&gt;
and so on -&amp;gt; and more
&lt;br /&gt;
as times going on -&amp;gt; as time progresses + have pp
&lt;br /&gt;
getting lake of leasure -&amp;gt; become increasingly devoid of leasure
&lt;br /&gt;
incurring in -&amp;gt; resulting in
&lt;br /&gt;
lessening -&amp;gt; deminished
&lt;br /&gt;
lives -&amp;gt; daily lives
&lt;br /&gt;
reason of this phenonmoon -&amp;gt; reason behind this phenonmon
&lt;br /&gt;
solution in the future -&amp;gt; solution for the future&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The main reason of people to getting devoid of leasure is their lives are becomming hard to fulfill even their basic needs. which phenomenon arised from unsensible policy which are only made for wealthy people, resulting in increasing disparity between poverty and wealthy. The issue is wealthy occupy only small portion of all population and else occupy the most part of it. so this phenomenon leads to conclution of people to prioritize other one than art.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The main reason people are becoming devoid of leisure is the increasing difficulty in fulfilling their basic needs. This phenomenon arises from unjust policies that predominantly benefit the wealthy, consequently widening the gap between poverty and wealth. The issue lies in the fact that a smaller and smaller portion of the population possesses wealth, while more and more people face economic challenges over time. As a result, people are inclined to prioritize other aspects of life over art.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;becoming hard to -&amp;gt; increasing difficulty in
&lt;br /&gt;
unsensible -&amp;gt; unjust
&lt;br /&gt;
policy that made for wealthy -&amp;gt; policy that banefit the wealthy
&lt;br /&gt;
increasing disparity -&amp;gt; widening
&lt;br /&gt;
people to -&amp;gt; people are inclined to
&lt;br /&gt;
priortize other one than art -&amp;gt; priortize other aspects of life over art&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
i believe we cannot solve this problem by just increasing the quality of art because the criteria of art also changing while quality of art increase. i think the most sensible solution in this situation is making people to be relized of this phenomen and making sound to government to increasing tex for just wealthy who is top earning of the world. regardless of their power, we can achieve the happy world if we don’t fight next person and aim to common end.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I believe we cannot solve this problem by simply increasing the quality of art because the criteria for art also change as the quality of art improves. I think the most sensible solution in this situation is to raise people’s awareness of this phenomenon and advocate for the government to increase taxes for the wealthy, who are the top earners in the world. Regardless of their power, we can achieve a happier world if we refrain from fighting against one another and strive towards a common goal.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;just -&amp;gt; simply
&lt;br /&gt;
criteria of art -&amp;gt; criteria for art
&lt;br /&gt;
quality of art increase -&amp;gt; quality of art improves
&lt;br /&gt;
make sound to -&amp;gt; advocate
&lt;br /&gt;
make people to be realized -&amp;gt; raise people’s awareness
&lt;br /&gt;
top earning of the world -&amp;gt; top earners in the world
&lt;br /&gt;
don’t -&amp;gt; refrain from
&lt;br /&gt;
fight next person -&amp;gt; fighting against one another
&lt;br /&gt;
aim to -&amp;gt; strive towards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclution, the phenomenon people to increasingly devoid art arises from disparity of wealth and poverty, not from innate problem of art or from people’s low comprehensive in terms of art. we can solve this problem by gathering together and advocate government to texing higher on the wealthy.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, the phenomenon of people becoming increasingly deprived of art arises from the disparity between wealth and poverty, rather than from an inherent problem with art or from people’s lack of understanding of art. We can address this issue by coming together and advocating for higher taxes on the wealthy from the government.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;the phenomenon people to -&amp;gt; the phenomenon of people ing
&lt;br /&gt;
disparity of -&amp;gt; disparity between
&lt;br /&gt;
not -&amp;gt; rather than
&lt;br /&gt;
innate problem of art -&amp;gt; inherent problem with art
&lt;br /&gt;
solve this problem -&amp;gt; address this issue
&lt;br /&gt;
gathering together -&amp;gt; comming together
&lt;br /&gt;
advocate government to -&amp;gt; advocate for (context) from government
&lt;br /&gt;
tex to the wealthy -&amp;gt; tex on the wealthy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q art is considered an essential part of all cultures throughout the world. however, these days fewer and fewer people appreciate art and turn their focus to science, technology and business. why do you think that is? what could be done to encourage more people to take inerest in the arts? A cultures over the world has their own color which is usually expressed in the form of art which has taken diverse form and appears in wall engraving, sound or dance and so on. as times going on, the lives of people getting lake of leasure which incurring the lessening interest on the art which doesn’t directly influence on their lives. I will explain my perspective of the reasion of this phenomenon and the solution in the furture paragraph revised</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Use chatgpt for free on mac</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/chatgpt.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Use chatgpt for free on mac" /><published>2023-05-17T13:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-17T13:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/chatgpt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/chatgpt.html">&lt;p&gt;Join the membership at openai.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Download chatgpt from the following link.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
https://github.com/vincelwt/chatgpt-mac
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Use.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="tool" /><summary type="html">Join the membership at openai. Download chatgpt from the following link. https://github.com/vincelwt/chatgpt-mac Use.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to create and maintain gitblog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/gitblog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to create and maintain gitblog" /><published>2023-05-17T11:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-17T11:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/gitblog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/gitblog.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;create&quot;&gt;create&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First you should install homebrew.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If you type ruby -v in your own terminal, it will display 2.6.8.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I recommand you to download 2.7.8 because jekyll need &amp;gt;2.7 and there are often many issues after big update. as 2.7.8 is just before version 3.0.0, it provides a more stable option.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Homebrew always download the lastest version which is unstable. by RBM, you can install ruby 2.7.8. i don’t recommand downloading rbenv due to some tricky issues with it in this situation.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Afterward, you should clone a theme from here http://jekyllthemes.org
and type following command in the terminal within the folder where you downloaded theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bundler&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;install&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;gem&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;install&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bundler&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you can see the basic theme running on your local server.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;maintain&quot;&gt;maintain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
To put it simply, you can make your own blog by just typing following command in your terminal after modify your files.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bundle&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;exec&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;serve&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you can modify your 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;_posts
&lt;br /&gt;
_includes (arrange section on your own homepage)
&lt;br /&gt;
README.md (introduction of homepage)
&lt;br /&gt;
_config.yml (basic information)
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is meaningless to modify _site as it is included in gitignore.
&lt;br /&gt;
Because it will be changed each time by running the command “bundle exec jekyll serve”.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="tool" /><summary type="html">create First you should install homebrew. If you type ruby -v in your own terminal, it will display 2.6.8. I recommand you to download 2.7.8 because jekyll need &amp;gt;2.7 and there are often many issues after big update. as 2.7.8 is just before version 3.0.0, it provides a more stable option. Homebrew always download the lastest version which is unstable. by RBM, you can install ruby 2.7.8. i don’t recommand downloading rbenv due to some tricky issues with it in this situation. Afterward, you should clone a theme from here http://jekyllthemes.org and type following command in the terminal within the folder where you downloaded theme. ```ruby bundler install</summary></entry></feed>