<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-02T17:05:04+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing2.html">&lt;p&gt;the depicted map outlines the transformation of region around certain house from 1990 to 2010. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The map provided illustrates the changes in the vicinity of a particular house over a 20-year period, from 1990 to 2010.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
region around -&amp;gt; in the vicinity of
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the garden is located at the upper part of the house. at 1990 and it is later appeared more at the right below part of map, adjacent and above the main road. there was cottage at the left part of road which is changed to the cafe
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In 1990, a garden was situated to the north of the house. Over time, this garden expanded towards the southeastern part of the map, adjacent to and north of the main road. Initially, there was a cottage to the west of the road, which was later transformed into a cafe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the enterance is open to the right part of house and shop is extent to the connected room while mergiing these rooms.
the store room is located at the left right part.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The entrance to the house opened to the east, and over the years, a shop was extended into an adjoining room, effectively merging these spaces. Additionally, a storeroom was located to the northeast of the house.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
right  -&amp;gt; east
extended to the connected room -&amp;gt; extended into adjoining room&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the depicted map outlines the transformation of region around certain house from 1990 to 2010. The map provided illustrates the changes in the vicinity of a particular house over a 20-year period, from 1990 to 2010. region around -&amp;gt; in the vicinity of the garden is located at the upper part of the house. at 1990 and it is later appeared more at the right below part of map, adjacent and above the main road. there was cottage at the left part of road which is changed to the cafe In 1990, a garden was situated to the north of the house. Over time, this garden expanded towards the southeastern part of the map, adjacent to and north of the main road. Initially, there was a cottage to the west of the road, which was later transformed into a cafe.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the provided map illustrate the changes of the park over the 40years from 1980 until now. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided map delineates the transformations that have occurred within a park over a span of 40 years, from 1980 to the present day.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
changes -&amp;gt; occered within 
over the -&amp;gt; over a span of
now -&amp;gt; present day
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there was few trees situated at the northen eastern corner triangle part of park. which is transformed into rectangular part, added chairs and desks and barbecue zone.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In 1980, a small cluster of trees was positioned in the northeastern corner of the park, forming a triangular area. This space has since evolved into a rectangular section, now featuring added chairs, tables, and a designated barbecue zone.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;few -&amp;gt; cluster of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;northestern.
part -&amp;gt; section
(바베큐존이 되었다)designated barbecue zone
featuring 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was no road at the northen and estern part of park starts from center. but it appears nowadays. the deployment of bench in the vicinity of pond changed and number increased by 1, 3 to 4. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally, there were no pathways in the northern and eastern sections of the park, starting from the center. However, these have been constructed in recent years. The arrangement and quantity of benches near the pond have also changed, with the number increasing from three to four.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
road -&amp;gt; pathways 인도
appears nowadays -&amp;gt; constructed in recent years
deployment -&amp;gt; arrangment
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was flowers around the southen gate but the left side of it changed to the bush and right side of it changed as play ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Around the southern entrance, there were initially flower beds. These have undergone changes as well; the area to the left has been converted into a bushy zone, while the right side has been transformed into a playground.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
it changed -&amp;gt; it have undergone changes
꽃밭 -&amp;gt; flower beds
—&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the provided map illustrate the changes of the park over the 40years from 1980 until now. The provided map delineates the transformations that have occurred within a park over a span of 40 years, from 1980 to the present day. changes -&amp;gt; occered within over the -&amp;gt; over a span of now -&amp;gt; present day</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;depicted map outlines the process of processing olive beginning with harvesting culmulating with storage tank or delivery to the factory for post processing.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The illustrated map vividly depicts the intricate journey of olives, starting from their harvesting and culminating in their eventual storage in tanks or transportation to a factory for further processing.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;복잡한(작은 서로 얽힌) intricate
process -&amp;gt; journey&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
first olive is collected from the tree via collection vat.
once it is collected, it is gone through leafting and washing process before get in olive mill to be crushing.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Initially, olives are meticulously gathered from trees using collection vats. Once harvested, they undergo a thorough cleaning process which includes leaf removal and washing. This prepares them for the next crucial step.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;섬세하게 meticulously
gone through -&amp;gt; undergo through&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
after crushing process, it is pasted through malaxer with -27 degree celcious and send to the centrifugal press machine. the pomace is send to the another factory as aforementioned. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The cleaned olives are then transported to an olive mill, where they are crushed. Following this, the crushed olives are mixed in a malaxer at a controlled temperature of -27 degrees Celsius. This process is essential for enhancing oil extraction.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
after crushing process -&amp;gt; Following this
with -27 degree celcious -&amp;gt; at a controlled temperature of -27 degrees Celsius&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the virgin oils post processed again which is seperation or decantation before store.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Afterwards, the olive paste is directed to a centrifugal press machine. Here, the oil is extracted while the remaining solid residue, known as pomace, is sent to a separate facility for further use.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The extracted virgin oil undergoes additional refinement. This involves processes like separation or decantation to ensure purity and quality. Finally, the refined oil is either carefully stored in tanks or dispatched to factories for additional post-processing stages.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;delivered to -&amp;gt; dispatched to
post-processing stages
—&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">depicted map outlines the process of processing olive beginning with harvesting culmulating with storage tank or delivery to the factory for post processing. The illustrated map vividly depicts the intricate journey of olives, starting from their harvesting and culminating in their eventual storage in tanks or transportation to a factory for further processing.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the depicted picture shows the delivery process of fish starting with fishing culmulating with fishshop sell.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided diagram illustrates the stages involved in the delivery process of fish, from the initial catch to the final sale at a fish shop.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
first we catch fish with net on the sea and deliver that to the port. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process begins at sea, where fish are caught using nets. Once caught, the fish are transported to a port. Upon arrival, they are immediately stored in a freezing environment to preserve their freshness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
we store them freezing and over time, we thaw them in fresh water and cut open.
and then we coloring them as yellow in the saltwater, smoking.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
After some time, these frozen fish are thawed in fresh water and then gutted. The next step involves coloring the fish yellow by immersing them in saltwater and subjecting them to a smoking process. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
and over time -&amp;gt; after some time
손질하다 gutted 
매우 실망하다 gutted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;then we freeze them at the 0 celcius temperature 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Once this is completed, the fish are frozen again, this time at a temperature of 0 degrees Celsius, ensuring they remain in a preserved state. They are then stored accordingly until they are ready for distribution.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
then -&amp;gt; once ~~
remain at ~state -&amp;gt; remain in ~state
and then -&amp;gt; then ~ accordingly
until ready for distribution&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and store them and distribute them to the fish shop sell
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The final step in the process involves delivering these preserved fish to fish shops, where they are ultimately sold to customers. This comprehensive journey from the sea to the shop ensures that the fish remain fresh and high in quality for the end consumer.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
comprehensive journey
remain high in quality
for the end consumer&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the depicted picture shows the delivery process of fish starting with fishing culmulating with fishshop sell. The provided diagram illustrates the stages involved in the delivery process of fish, from the initial catch to the final sale at a fish shop.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing2.html">&lt;p&gt;depicted map shows the development plan of river basin. 
there is no bridge cross the river but they plan to build that house above the river with constructing the connected bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The illustrated map outlines a development plan for a river basin area. Presently, there is no bridge crossing the river, but there are plans to build one along with houses situated above the river, connected by the proposed bridge.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
shows -&amp;gt; outlines
river basin -&amp;gt; river basin area
now -&amp;gt; presently&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was initially the raod featured roundabout and few factories are located around that roundabout and located along the load streached right side of roundabout. 
they are planning to vanish every factory and replace that as housing along the load streach to the right side. 
and construct them adjacent to the road between bridge and roundabout aforementioned. and they will build additional road at the upper left side of roundabout and two housing accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Initially, the area features a road with a roundabout. Several factories are situated around this roundabout and along the road extending from its right side. The plan involves demolishing these factories and replacing them with housing units along the road stretching to the right of the roundabout. These houses will be constructed adjacent to the road, situated between the proposed bridge and the existing roundabout. Additionally, a new road is planned to be built on the upper left side of the roundabout, flanked by two housing units.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
vanishing -&amp;gt; demolishing
replace as -&amp;gt; replace with
flanked by two housing units.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
they are planning to construct few amenities like shops and medical centre located near the roundabout. playground located above the housing which is located at the right side of roundabout. and at the end of that road, there will be school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The development plan also includes the construction of various amenities. Shops and a medical center are planned to be located near the roundabout. Above the housing on the right side of the roundabout, there will be a playground. At the end of this road, a school is proposed to be built.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
and they planning to make new roundabout at the below part of aforementioned roundabout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, there are plans to create a new roundabout below the existing one, enhancing the overall connectivity and accessibility of the area.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">depicted map shows the development plan of river basin. there is no bridge cross the river but they plan to build that house above the river with constructing the connected bridge.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/25/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-25T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/25/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/25/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the illustrated map depict the transformation of river basin over the three time zone from 1780, 1860 to 2000.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The illustrated map showcases the dynamic changes in a river basin over three distinct periods: 1780, 1860, and 2000.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
depict -&amp;gt; showcasees 
three time zone -&amp;gt; three distinct periods
transformation of -&amp;gt; dynamic changes in
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was large farm region adjacent to the river at the 1780 but the area of it decreases over the time and finally dissappeared at 2000. also same thing happened for the woods located at the right southen part of the map.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In 1780, a vast farming region flanked the river, but this area progressively shrank and had completely vanished by 2000. A similar fate befell the woods located in the southern part of the map, which also diminished over time.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
flanked adjacent랑 비슷한 뜻이지만 둘러싸인느낌
면적이 줄어들다 shrank 
dissappeared at -&amp;gt; vanished by
similar things happened to A-&amp;gt; simialr fate befell the A&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
and there was not bridge over the river but it constructed at 1860 and still maintained at 2000. in addition, few shop appeared along the river. there was only small resident which is composed of 100homes but it increases over time, becoming 200homes at 1860s and finally 500homes at 2000s. when 1860, load appeared to connect between homes and river and it expanded to connect schools and sport field which appeared at the location which wood has been to.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Initially, there was no bridge crossing the river. However, one was constructed in 1860 and remained in use by 2000. Alongside this, a few shops began to appear near the riverbank. The residential area, initially a small community of around 100 homes in 1780, experienced substantial growth. By the 1860s, it had doubled to 200 homes and by 2000, it had expanded to 500 homes. In 1860, a road was introduced to connect the homes with the river, and over time, this road extended to newly established schools and a sports field. These new developments occupied the space where the woods once stood.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there was not bridge -&amp;gt; there was no bridge
over the river -&amp;gt; crossing the river
still maintained -&amp;gt; remained in use by 2000
next to the river -&amp;gt; alongside river
resident -&amp;gt; residental area
area is community of around 100 homes
expanded -&amp;gt; experienced substantial growth
doubled to
location which wood has been to -&amp;gt; where the woods once stood&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the illustrated map depict the transformation of river basin over the three time zone from 1780, 1860 to 2000. The illustrated map showcases the dynamic changes in a river basin over three distinct periods: 1780, 1860, and 2000. depict -&amp;gt; showcasees three time zone -&amp;gt; three distinct periods transformation of -&amp;gt; dynamic changes in there was large farm region adjacent to the river at the 1780 but the area of it decreases over the time and finally dissappeared at 2000. also same thing happened for the woods located at the right southen part of the map.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/22/writing-1-4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-22T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/22/writing%201-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/22/writing-1-4.html">&lt;p&gt;the depicted picture show the making process of raw tea and ripe tea.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
The provided illustration outlines the production process of both raw and ripe tea.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
making process -&amp;gt; production process
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
both type of tea share the process of pan frying , which is for inactivation of tnzymes, followed by rolling. and after then, they both are dried under the sun and loose raw tea.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
Both types of tea undergo similar initial steps. They are first pan-fried, a step crucial for the inactivation of enzymes. This is followed by rolling. Subsequently, the teas are sun-dried, resulting in loose raw tea.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
both type -&amp;gt; both types
share process -&amp;gt; undergo initial steps
which is for -&amp;gt; a step crucial for
dried under the sun -&amp;gt; sun-dried
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
to make vintage pu-erh raw tea, it should be compressed to pu-erh raw tea and store for a long time. to make pu-erh ripe tea, they are fermentated by mold and compressed.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
For the creation of vintage Pu-erh raw tea, the loose tea is compressed into Pu-erh raw tea cakes and then stored for an extended period. On the other hand, to produce Pu-erh ripe tea, the tea undergoes fermentation using mold before being compressed.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
to make -&amp;gt; for the creation
for a long time -&amp;gt; for an extended period
undergo&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the depicted picture show the making process of raw tea and ripe tea. &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; The provided illustration outlines the production process of both raw and ripe tea. &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; making process -&amp;gt; production process &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; both type of tea share the process of pan frying , which is for inactivation of tnzymes, followed by rolling. and after then, they both are dried under the sun and loose raw tea. &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; Both types of tea undergo similar initial steps. They are first pan-fried, a step crucial for the inactivation of enzymes. This is followed by rolling. Subsequently, the teas are sun-dried, resulting in loose raw tea. &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; both type -&amp;gt; both types share process -&amp;gt; undergo initial steps which is for -&amp;gt; a step crucial for dried under the sun -&amp;gt; sun-dried &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; to make vintage pu-erh raw tea, it should be compressed to pu-erh raw tea and store for a long time. to make pu-erh ripe tea, they are fermentated by mold and compressed. &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; For the creation of vintage Pu-erh raw tea, the loose tea is compressed into Pu-erh raw tea cakes and then stored for an extended period. On the other hand, to produce Pu-erh ripe tea, the tea undergoes fermentation using mold before being compressed. &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/br&amp;gt; to make -&amp;gt; for the creation for a long time -&amp;gt; for an extended period undergo</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/20/writing-ground.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/20/writing%20ground</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/20/writing-ground.html">&lt;p&gt;illustrated map below is changing history of ground floor of apartment. they devide three section. first one is used as office 1958-1984 , second one is used as apartment 1985-2000 and third one is used as flower shop 2001-present. entrance is located at the bottom of that building.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The transformation of the ground floor of a certain apartment building over the years is vividly depicted in the provided map. This space has been repurposed through three distinct eras, each with its unique utilization and design.
&lt;br /&gt;
changing history -&amp;gt; transformation
&lt;br /&gt;
illustrated -&amp;gt; vividly depicted
&lt;br /&gt;
repurposed (원래 하려고한 쓰임새랑 다르게 쓰게끔 만듬)
&lt;br /&gt;
each with its unique utilization
&lt;br /&gt;
every timeline, map is bisected by the alley. left uppermost area was used as meeting room for the first. and another section at the left is used as assistent’s office and secretary’s office and toilet from the up to the down sequence. right uppermost area is used as kitchen until now, rest area was devided as two area, upper one is manager office and down one is reception area.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
From 1958 to 1984, the primary function of the ground floor was to serve as an office. During this period, the layout was distinctively bisected by an alley. On the left, the uppermost area was designated as a meeting room. Below this, The left side was partitioned into three distinct areas: an assistant’s office, a secretary’s office, and, at the very bottom, a toilet. The right-hand side saw the topmost section serving as a kitchen, which has intriguingly remained unchanged over the decades. The remainder of this side was split, with a manager’s office positioned above and a reception area located below.
&lt;br /&gt;
primary function 원래 의도했던 작동방식
&lt;br /&gt;
another section -&amp;gt; below this
&lt;br /&gt;
very bottom, furthest bottom
&lt;br /&gt;
right side -&amp;gt; right-hand side
&lt;br /&gt;
uppermost -&amp;gt; topmost
&lt;br /&gt;
rest area was devided as
-&amp;gt; remainder of this side was split
&lt;br /&gt;
situated -&amp;gt; poistioned
&lt;br /&gt;
when it is used as apartment, leftside was devided as two part. upper area is used as living room and down area is used as bathroom and shower. the leftover space of right side is used as connected 2 bedrooms.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Following this office era, from 1985 to 2000, the ground floor was revamped into a residential space. The left side was bifurcated into a living room above and a bathroom, complete with a shower, below. On the right, the available area was optimized to accommodate two interconnected bedrooms, making it a comfortable living space.
&lt;br /&gt;
revamped into (repurposed 랑 비슷한데 업그레이드한다는 개념)
&lt;br /&gt;
bisected -&amp;gt; bifurcated
&lt;br /&gt;
complete with a shower(샤워시설이 구비된)
&lt;br /&gt;
and now, the left uppermost area is used as gift cards and bottommost area is used as play area. 
when you get in that apartment, you can see flower right away at the right side and left senter area. you don’t need to get in the room because they left that area as open. and they situated office at the right center region.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The most recent transformation, starting from 2001 up to the present, has seen the ground floor become a bustling flower shop. An interesting design choice is evident in the left uppermost corner, which now displays gift cards. Below this, a playful touch has been added with a designated play area for visitors. Upon entering the building, which has its entrance situated at the bottom, one is immediately welcomed by a visual treat. Flowers greet visitors both to their immediate right and slightly towards the left center. This display area remains open, allowing for an immersive experience without the need to enter a separate room. Additionally, an office space has been strategically placed in the central right section.
&lt;br /&gt;
bustling 붐비는
&lt;br /&gt;
immediate right and slightly towards the left center
&lt;br /&gt;
remains open
&lt;br /&gt;
without the need to enter a separate room
&lt;br /&gt;
placed in the central right section.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the illustrated map provides a captivating insight into the dynamic nature of space utilization. The ground floor of this apartment building is a testament to the changing needs and innovative design choices made over the years.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">illustrated map below is changing history of ground floor of apartment. they devide three section. first one is used as office 1958-1984 , second one is used as apartment 1985-2000 and third one is used as flower shop 2001-present. entrance is located at the bottom of that building. The transformation of the ground floor of a certain apartment building over the years is vividly depicted in the provided map. This space has been repurposed through three distinct eras, each with its unique utilization and design. changing history -&amp;gt; transformation illustrated -&amp;gt; vividly depicted repurposed (원래 하려고한 쓰임새랑 다르게 쓰게끔 만듬) each with its unique utilization every timeline, map is bisected by the alley. left uppermost area was used as meeting room for the first. and another section at the left is used as assistent’s office and secretary’s office and toilet from the up to the down sequence. right uppermost area is used as kitchen until now, rest area was devided as two area, upper one is manager office and down one is reception area. From 1958 to 1984, the primary function of the ground floor was to serve as an office. During this period, the layout was distinctively bisected by an alley. On the left, the uppermost area was designated as a meeting room. Below this, The left side was partitioned into three distinct areas: an assistant’s office, a secretary’s office, and, at the very bottom, a toilet. The right-hand side saw the topmost section serving as a kitchen, which has intriguingly remained unchanged over the decades. The remainder of this side was split, with a manager’s office positioned above and a reception area located below. primary function 원래 의도했던 작동방식 another section -&amp;gt; below this very bottom, furthest bottom right side -&amp;gt; right-hand side uppermost -&amp;gt; topmost rest area was devided as -&amp;gt; remainder of this side was split situated -&amp;gt; poistioned when it is used as apartment, leftside was devided as two part. upper area is used as living room and down area is used as bathroom and shower. the leftover space of right side is used as connected 2 bedrooms. Following this office era, from 1985 to 2000, the ground floor was revamped into a residential space. The left side was bifurcated into a living room above and a bathroom, complete with a shower, below. On the right, the available area was optimized to accommodate two interconnected bedrooms, making it a comfortable living space. revamped into (repurposed 랑 비슷한데 업그레이드한다는 개념) bisected -&amp;gt; bifurcated complete with a shower(샤워시설이 구비된) and now, the left uppermost area is used as gift cards and bottommost area is used as play area. when you get in that apartment, you can see flower right away at the right side and left senter area. you don’t need to get in the room because they left that area as open. and they situated office at the right center region. The most recent transformation, starting from 2001 up to the present, has seen the ground floor become a bustling flower shop. An interesting design choice is evident in the left uppermost corner, which now displays gift cards. Below this, a playful touch has been added with a designated play area for visitors. Upon entering the building, which has its entrance situated at the bottom, one is immediately welcomed by a visual treat. Flowers greet visitors both to their immediate right and slightly towards the left center. This display area remains open, allowing for an immersive experience without the need to enter a separate room. Additionally, an office space has been strategically placed in the central right section. bustling 붐비는 immediate right and slightly towards the left center remains open without the need to enter a separate room placed in the central right section.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing1-1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing1-1" /><published>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
that diagram illustrates making and delivery process of rock. 
there are totally 7 process starting with digging cumulating with delivery
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The diagram illustrates the creation and delivery process of bricks.
In total, there are seven processes, beginning with digging and culminating in delivery.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;make -&amp;gt; create
start from -&amp;gt; beginning with
&lt;br /&gt;
first digger is employed for dig the clay and digged clay is put on the metal grid, filtering to smaller one on the roller.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
First, a digger is employed to excavate the clay. The excavated clay is then placed on a metal grid, where it is filtered into smaller pieces via a roller.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;be employed for -&amp;gt; be employed to
smaller one -&amp;gt; smaller pieces
on the roller -&amp;gt; via a roller
&lt;br /&gt;
then sand and water is added to that smaller one. that is formed as brick by cutting them or moulding.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Next, sand and water are added to these smaller pieces. These are then formed into bricks either by cutting or molding.
&lt;br /&gt;
formed as  -&amp;gt; formed into
or -&amp;gt; either or
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;after formed as brick, they are dried for more than 24 hours and then heated in the kiln, first heated in moderate temperature and high temperature and finally cooled for 2 to 3days. following packaging and delivery
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Once shaped into bricks, they are dried for more than 24 hours. Subsequently, they are heated in a kiln, initially at a moderate temperature, followed by a high temperature. They are then cooled for 2 to 3 days. The process concludes with packaging and delivery.
&lt;br /&gt;
formed as -&amp;gt; shaped into
followed by -&amp;gt; concludes with&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">that diagram illustrates making and delivery process of rock. there are totally 7 process starting with digging cumulating with delivery The diagram illustrates the creation and delivery process of bricks. In total, there are seven processes, beginning with digging and culminating in delivery.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing-map.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing-map</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing-map.html">&lt;p&gt;the illustrated map is reconstruct plan of region.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided map illustrates the redevelopment plan for the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
illustrated map -&amp;gt; provided map
reconstruct -&amp;gt; redevelopment
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
they are airfield located to north west part of the map and planning to substitute that as industrial estate with connecting railway&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There’s an airfield in the northwest part of the map, which is slated to be replaced with an industrial estate, and there are plans to connect it with a railway.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
planning to -&amp;gt; be slated to
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A2 road is situated next to the air field including roundabout and they propose the build A4 road at the bottom of the A2, also connecting railway
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The A2 road lies adjacent to the airfield and features a roundabout. A proposal is in place to construct the A4 road below the A2, which will also be connected to the railway.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
situated next to -&amp;gt; lies adjacent to
including roundabout -&amp;gt; features a roundabout
build -&amp;gt; construce
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
they are planning to make another roundabout above to the gas station which is next to the railway
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, there are plans to construct another roundabout just above the gas station, which is situated near the railway.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the illustrated map is reconstruct plan of region. The provided map illustrates the redevelopment plan for the region.</summary></entry></feed>