<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-12-22T12:26:23+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing 22</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w22.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 22" /><published>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w22</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w22.html">&lt;p&gt;the line graph delineates the change in number of participants in each different areas. From a comprehensive analysis, the number of people engaged in Table tennis and Musical performances increased over period, meanwhile the number of people participating in Amateur dramatics diminished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of participancts in Film club, commenced with takes first place in all different kinds of art, which is about 63, steadly maintained its number until the 2020. The number of participants in Martial arts get second place in total area, begin with around 36 does not changed till the end analogues to Film club. The participants in Amateur dramatics starts around 26, marginally increased at 2005 but after Musical performances occered in 2005, the number of participants decreased as number of Musical performances increased. the number of Table tennis slightly increased until 2010 but it surged after 2010 until 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The line graph illustrates the changes in the number of participants across various activities. A detailed analysis reveals that the number of individuals involved in table tennis and musical performances increased over time, whereas participation in amateur dramatics decreased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the category of film clubs, which initially recorded the highest participation with approximately 63 attendees, the numbers remained stable through 2020. Martial arts secured the second highest overall participation, starting with around 36 participants and maintaining that figure consistently, similar to the trend observed in the film club. Participation in amateur dramatics began with about 26 individuals, saw a slight increase in 2005, but subsequently declined as musical performances, which began in the same year, attracted more participants. The number of table tennis players exhibited a modest rise until 2010, followed by a significant surge through to 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the line graph delineates the change in number of participants in each different areas. From a comprehensive analysis, the number of people engaged in Table tennis and Musical performances increased over period, meanwhile the number of people participating in Amateur dramatics diminished.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 19</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w19.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 19" /><published>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w19</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w19.html">&lt;p&gt;there is a debate considering weather history should be studied. i will examine the merits and drawbacks in terms of studying a series of past events and will further elaborate on my opinion in the following paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to begin with, lets consider the disadvantages of studying history. over time, we increasingly face with complex problems with the advent of internet. critics argue that as we need to deal different problems, we need to manage social problems with different avenues such as methamatics and statics which were not existed in the past. For example, we can not address hacking or scammer with traditional approach but cyber security and network flow management skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the opposing view points, dispite our society represent different aspect from the past, studying history is still beneficial to improve our knack to deal with modern challanges. even though the gap in scientific advancement between past and nowadays are extremely large, our inheretant habits which is established over 10 thousands years have not changed. in conclusion, they believe studying about the past will somehow help our social matuality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i am inclined to partially agree with the opintion that supports the studying history. our neural network system in the brain have not changed yet. moreover since we already aware of we are in different situation from that of privious era, we can modify the privious means and adept that for current situations. However, sicne we are all have different individual strength, it would be preferrable to study history for people who want to study about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a debate concerning whether history should be studied. I will examine the merits and drawbacks of studying a series of past events and will further elaborate on my opinion in the following paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin with, let us consider the disadvantages of studying history. Over time, as we face increasingly complex problems with the advent of the internet, critics argue that we need to address different problems using diverse avenues such as mathematics and statistics, which did not exist in the past. For example, traditional approaches are inadequate for addressing issues like hacking or scams; instead, skills in cybersecurity and network flow management are required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the opposing viewpoint, despite our society representing different aspects from the past, studying history is still beneficial for improving our ability to deal with modern challenges. Although the gap in scientific advancement between the past and present is vast, our inherent habits, established over tens of thousands of years, have not changed. In conclusion, proponents believe that studying the past can somehow aid our social maturity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am inclined to partially agree with the opinion supporting the study of history. Our neural network systems in the brain have not yet changed. Moreover, since we are already aware that our situation differs from that of previous eras, we can modify previous methods and adapt them to current situations. However, since individuals possess different strengths, it would be preferable for those interested in history to pursue its study.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">there is a debate considering weather history should be studied. i will examine the merits and drawbacks in terms of studying a series of past events and will further elaborate on my opinion in the following paragraph.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 17</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/wexp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 17" /><published>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/wexp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/wexp.html">&lt;p&gt;aid
address
diverse
inadequate
vast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;debate concerning whether
examine
inadvertently
Proponents
critics
Students are able to engage
merits and drawbacks 
subsequent
makes it challenging
the absence of surveillance
which amounts to
the ease of monitoring 
offer more advantages
some degree of
schools lack control&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to be conscientious
driving under the influence
stemming from 
I contend
those identified as potential risks.
government should intervene between 
unscrupulous companies
counterfeit 
it is preferable to
not always function
conceal their wrongdoings
This same dynamic 
reportedly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;mental maturity can be learned through other means
actualize
how to concede
certain jobs are valued less
some people excel in
integral part&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;inclined to partially agree that
advancement of technology may exert negative
erosion of civic values
maintain regular contact
prosperous and enriched life&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;art’s role in modern society is multifaceted
imperative
Inadvertently
shape social norms
pragmatic value of art may seem diminished in the face of
intrinsic benefits
With the advent of
taps into the human subconscious&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">aid address diverse inadequate vast</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 17</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w17.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 17" /><published>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w17</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w17.html">&lt;p&gt;there is debate about wether having a class by online have more advantage over having a class by offline. i examine the advantage and disadvantage of this argument and will further elaborate on my opinion in the following paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a debate concerning whether online classes offer more advantages than offline ones. I will examine the merits and drawbacks of this argument and will further elaborate on my opinion in the subsequent paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to begin with, let us consider the merits of having offline class. they argue that there is something children can not learn through online class. they are not only can learn academical subject but also learn some humanity. For example, they can play traditional game together and as physical environment is susceptable to violence and easily hurt each other, they can learn how to respect each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin with, let us consider the merits of offline classes. Proponents argue that there are certain lessons that cannot be learned through online classes. Students are able to engage not only in academic subjects but also in lessons of humanity. For example, they can participate in traditional games together, and because the physical environment may expose them to potential conflicts, it provides opportunities to learn respect for one another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for the opposite perspective, some people argue that online class is more effective than offline class. the main reason beings online class save the time for commute and easy to sulvillance the behavior. students need to wear the uniform to get the school and it takes around 1hour, so it totally takes about 2hours for commute every day. moreover there are no cctv in the school in some country, so it is hard to monitering student’s behavior in the offline class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the opposite perspective, some individuals argue that online classes are more effective than offline classes. The primary reasons include the time saved on commuting and the ease of monitoring behavior. Students typically need to wear uniforms and spend about an hour traveling to school, which amounts to approximately two hours of commuting daily. Moreover, the absence of surveillance cameras in schools in some countries makes it challenging to monitor students’ behavior in offline classes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m partially agree with that online class is more advantaged than face to face class. it can be true that students can learn some extent of cooperation and socializing while clowning around together. but if schools are lake of control over students and irresponsible, that brings the school violence problem and demaging the socialization rather than improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I partially agree that online classes offer more advantages than face-to-face classes. It is true that students can learn some degree of cooperation and socialization while engaging in playful activities together. However, if schools lack control over students and are irresponsible, this can lead to issues such as school violence, ultimately damaging socialization rather than enhancing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;feel awake&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;후천적으로&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;acceptable 권장할만하다&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">there is debate about wether having a class by online have more advantage over having a class by offline. i examine the advantage and disadvantage of this argument and will further elaborate on my opinion in the following paragraph.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 21</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 21" /><published>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-28T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/28/w.html">&lt;p&gt;The bar graph delineates the difference between winter and summer in term of the number of servings. From a comprehensive analysis, it is evident that the daily sales in summer is similar in every category whereas that of winter fluctuate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of sold Hot coffee in winter secured biggest part in overall graph, around 75, contrastly The number of sold Iced coffee record lowest in the same season which is almost 0 . the number of sold Soup in winter is 50 which is twice bigger than that in summer. The number of sold salad steadly remained in both seasons and same dynamic also applied in ice cream which only experienced marginally increasing in summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bar graph illustrates the seasonal variation in the number of servings, comparing winter and summer. A thorough analysis clearly shows that daily sales in summer remain consistent across all categories, while those in winter exhibit fluctuations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In winter, hot coffee sales dominate the chart, approximately 75 servings, in stark contrast to iced coffee, which nearly disappears with almost zero servings. Soup sales in winter reach 50 servings, doubling the figure observed in summer. The sales of salad remain stable in both seasons, a trend also observed in ice cream, which only shows a slight increase during the summer months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;trend also observed
doubling the figure
in stark contrast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pie chart delineates percentage of reason for the immigration and emigration in UK. From a comprehensive analysis, It is evident that career issue is staple for moving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ratio of deficite job occupied the largest part across all reasons for both immigration and emigration. the reason of formal study recoreded secondly largest part in immigration, contrastly occupying least part in emigration. the percentage of accompany is less than half of definite job and formal study in immigration but almost same as definite job in emigration. the percentage of immigrated to the uk with without any reason occupied least part of all category which is third of that in emigration. the reason of accompany occupied similar as both immigration and emigration which is 13 percent and 15 percent each.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
The pie chart provides a detailed breakdown of the reasons for immigration to and emigration from the UK. An in-depth analysis reveals that career-related issues are a primary motivator for relocation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lack of job opportunities constitutes the predominant reason for both immigrating to and emigrating from the UK, accounting for the largest proportion in each case. Educational pursuits are the second most common reason for immigration, yet they represent the least common reason for emigration. The proportion of individuals who immigrate for the purpose of accompanying someone is less than half that of those relocating for definite job opportunities or formal study, but this reason aligns closely with job-related moves in terms of emigration. The percentage of individuals who immigrate to the UK without any specific reason forms the smallest portion of all categories, amounting to a third of the corresponding figure for emigration. The motive of accompanying another accounts for similar proportions in both immigration and emigration, at 13 percent and 15 percent, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
the pie charts provides detailed breakdown of change in diverse source for energy production from 1995 to 2005. From the comprehensive analysis, it is evident that predominant source of energy is from coal and gas for both era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the energy from the coal in 1995 recorded largest among the all sources, amounting approximately 30 percent, directly followed by the gas in 1995 which is also approximately accounting for 30 percent, at 29.80 and 29.63 percent, respectively. these source are marginally increased at 2005, to 30.93 and 30.31 percent each. the proportion of petro also secured similar as gas and coal in 1995, 29.27 percent but decreased to 19.55 percent, approximately third of twice of previous. the ratio of nuclear was 6.40 percent but increased to 10.10 percent which is half of third of previous one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
The pie charts provide a detailed breakdown of the changes in various energy sources for production from 1995 to 2005. A comprehensive analysis clearly shows that coal and gas were the predominant sources of energy in both periods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1995, energy derived from coal was the largest among all sources, approximately amounting to 30 percent, closely followed by gas, which also accounted for about 30 percent, at 29.80 and 29.63 percent, respectively. These sources saw marginal increases by 2005, reaching 30.93 and 30.31 percent each. The proportion of petroleum was comparable to gas and coal in 1995, at 29.27 percent, but decreased to 19.55 percent by 2005, which is roughly two-thirds of its previous amount. The share of nuclear energy was 6.40 percent in 1995 and increased to 10.10 percent by 2005, representing one and a half times its earlier figure.
&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;
The pie charts provide an analysis of the distribution of various energy sources within a specific country for the years 1995 and 2005. From a general overview, it is clear that the production of the two primary energy sources, coal and gas, increased slightly, whereas petrol saw a significant decline. Both ‘Other’ energy forms and nuclear energy experienced considerable growth, although they remained less predominant than the main sources in both years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1995, coal, gas, and petrol each constituted slightly more than 29% of total energy production, indicating a relatively balanced distribution among these sources. By 2005, the percentages for coal and gas had moderately increased to 30.93% and 30.31%, respectively, while the share of petrol fell sharply to only 19.55%. The statistics for the other categories started off significantly lower, with ‘Other’ representing 4.9% and nuclear at 6.4% at the beginning of the period. By 2005, ‘Other’ had nearly doubled to 9.1%, reducing the gap significantly, whereas nuclear energy’s growth was more gradual, reaching 10.1%.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">The bar graph delineates the difference between winter and summer in term of the number of servings. From a comprehensive analysis, it is evident that the daily sales in summer is similar in every category whereas that of winter fluctuate.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 16</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w16.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 16" /><published>2024-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w16</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w16.html">&lt;p&gt;The map delineates a beachfront location in Australia as it was in 1950 and the changes that have occurred up to the present day. From a comprehensive perspective, it is evident that there has been an expansion in leisure facilities and motor vehicle access to the beach. The beach itself remains unaltered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1950, the area, which was less developed, featured a road positioned above the beach, terminating at a car park. In the contemporary setting, both the road and the car park persist; however, the car park has been enlarged and the road extended. The current road extends to a lighthouse, which was also present in 1950, and leads to a newly constructed surf club adjacent to the beach. A small 25-meter pool is still situated near the lighthouse. Beneath the road in 1950, there existed a playground, a dining area, and a pavilion, which remain largely unchanged today, except for the replacement of the children’s playground with an additional car park. Closer to the beach, what was once a 25-meter pool has been expanded to 50 meters, and presently there is a restaurant and another surf club located to the left of the beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the map deliniates the transformation between 1950 and now in terms of sea shore. from the comprehensive perspective, they are more industrialized than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map delineates the transformation of the sea shore from 1950 to the present, illustrating significant changes. From a comprehensive perspective, the area has become more industrialized than it was previously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the play ground, which was initially located at the north east part of the map, gives way to car park. and road extends from the northen car park to the big road a the north part. the another car park which was initially occupying the northen east was extended. moreover the northen raod was initially only cumulated to the carpark was now extended to the light house at the south. surf clubs were now situated alinging with the pool and at the left side, restaurant take place right behind eht surf club and pool is extended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The playground, initially located in the northeastern part of the map, gives way to a car park. A road extends from the northern car park to the main road in the northern area. Another car park, which initially occupied the northeastern area, has been expanded. Furthermore, the northern road, which originally led only to the car park, now extends to the lighthouse to the south. Surf clubs are now located adjacent to the pool, while a restaurant is situated directly behind the surf club, and the pool area has been expanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map delineates the changes within the town of Pentland from 1980 to 2007. From a comprehensive perspective, it is evident that there has been extensive residential and commercial development over the years, including the construction of a marina for yachts, shops, houses, and entertainment facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1980, Pentland primarily featured grasslands to the south, two main intersecting roads, a car park to the east, an industrial area to the west, and the sea to the north. By 2007, every area had undergone transformation or relocation. A new road was constructed along the coast, where a yacht marina now exists, flanked by a park in the northwest and seaside apartments on the opposite side. The roads are now lined with shops, and the car park, which has expanded vertically, was relocated from the eastern to the western end of town, adjacent to a newly constructed swimming pool. In the south, what were once grasslands have been replaced by a cinema to the west and rows of houses along a newly established avenue stretching eastward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the above map delinates the alternation of shore of the sea from 1980 to 2007. from the comprehensive perspective, this place become more village area from indistral area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map above delineates the alteration of the sea shore from 1980 to 2007. From a comprehensive perspective, this area has transitioned from an industrial zone to a more village-like environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the sea, occupying the northen part of map is named as yacht marina in present, surrounded by the road which is extended from the main roads. park and apartments are situated alongside to the newly constructed raod. the industrial area, located at the above of western part of roads gives way to commercial amennity. many shops are newly situated alongside main raods, the car park which was initially located at the east part of roads is now located at the westmost northen part of map.
swimming pool is adjacent to the multi storay car park. houses are take place of grassland which was occupying the southen west part of map.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea, occupying the northern part of the map, is now designated as a yacht marina and is surrounded by an extended road from the main thoroughfares. Parks and apartments are situated alongside this newly constructed road. The industrial area, previously located in the upper western part of the roads, has been replaced by commercial amenities. Numerous shops have been newly established along the main roads. The car park, which was initially situated in the eastern part of the roads, is now located in the westernmost northern part of the map. A swimming pool is adjacent to the multi-story car park. Houses have replaced the grasslands that once occupied the southwestern part of the map.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above floor plan delineates a theater in 2010 and in 2012 following renovations. From an overall perspective, it is evident that there was a significant expansion of facilities, enhancing both customer-oriented services and staff operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2010, the theater featured a large auditorium at its center, which remained unchanged by 2012, with expansive dressing room space behind it and a storage area located in the top right corner. By 2012, the storage room was relocated to the bottom left corner to make room for an administration office, while the dressing room was moved to a smaller room in a newly added wing on the left side, which also includes a shower room. The former dressing room area was repurposed into a coordination area.
Near the entrance, a large restaurant now occupies what was previously an empty space, necessitating the relocation of the administrative and ticket offices. The former is now positioned to the right of the entrance, displacing a café. The main door has remained unchanged, with no further alterations since 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the above map delinates the plan for transition of theatre from 2010 to 2012. From the comprehensive perspective, they are extended with additional ammenities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the Dressing Room, situated at the northen most part of theatre was replaced by the coordination room. and moved to the west part of theatre. the storage which was located at the northen east part of thearte gives way to the admin office which was initially located at the beneath of auditorium. storage is now situated at directly west side of the adjectant of restaurant which is beneath of autitorium. ticket office take place of cafe, which is now located at the east side of restaurtnat. the stage enlarged vertically and shower room is newly established at the left of stage. autitorium persisted unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map above delineates the plan for the transition of the theater from 2010 to 2012. From a comprehensive perspective, the theater was expanded with additional amenities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dressing Room, originally situated in the northernmost part of the theater, was replaced by a coordination room and relocated to the western part of the theater. The storage area, previously located in the northeastern part of the theater, made way for the administrative office, which was initially situated beneath the auditorium. The storage is now located directly west of the restaurant, which is beneath the auditorium. The ticket office has taken the place of the café and is now located on the east side of the restaurant. The stage was enlarged vertically, and a shower room has been newly established to the left of the stage. The auditorium remained unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">The map delineates a beachfront location in Australia as it was in 1950 and the changes that have occurred up to the present day. From a comprehensive perspective, it is evident that there has been an expansion in leisure facilities and motor vehicle access to the beach. The beach itself remains unaltered.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 14</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w14.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 14" /><published>2024-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w14</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w14.html">&lt;p&gt;The maps above depict the current layout of Norbiton and the proposed future developments. 
From a broad perspective, it is evident that the town is set to transition from an industrial focus to a more residential one, with the addition of housing, educational, commercial, and medical facilities. 
This development will primarily take place in the western and northern parts of Norbiton, leaving only a small section of farmland untouched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At present, the town features a central roundabout, surrounded by factories, and a road that runs from west to east through Norbiton. 
In the future, while the roundabout will remain, the surrounding factories will be replaced by shops. 
A new residential area will line a road to the northwest, and a hospital will be constructed to the southeast. 
Additionally, the original road leading east will be flanked by housing on both sides, with a large playground to the north and a school at the town’s eastern boundary. 
Beyond the town center, a smaller roundabout will be introduced to the south, bisecting an existing street. 
In the north, a bridge will be constructed over the river, and a portion of the farmland will give way to housing, although the area to the east will remain unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map illustrates the transformations that took place in the town of Willington during the years 1780, 1860, and 2000. 
From a broad perspective, it is evident that the town shifted towards a more residential and commercial character, with the introduction of new homes, roads, a bridge, shops, and recreational facilities, 
while natural areas such as forests and farmlands were diminished. Notably, the river remained unchanged throughout this period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1780, Willington was home to only 100 residences, and large portions of land to the east and south were covered by farms and woods. 
The river flowed from north to south, a geographical feature that persisted unchanged through 2000. By 1860, 
some of the farms and wooded areas had been cleared to make way for a road extending from the river to a residential area in the northeast, 
which had grown to 200 homes. Additionally, a bridge was constructed over the river. By 2000, the number of homes had increased to 500, and all of the farmland and forest had been removed. 
This allowed for the development of two schools, three sports fields, and a series of shops along the southern bank of the river. 
A large lake was also added to the southern end of the river, marking the final significant alteration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The floorplan illustrates the transformation of a building from 1958 to the present day. From a comprehensive viewpoint, it is evident that the building has served both commercial and residential functions, 
with the kitchen being the only area that has remained unchanged. Currently, the flower shop features a more open layout compared to when the building was an apartment and office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1958, the building functioned as an office, with a meeting room occupying the top left corner of the floorplan, and an assistant��s and secretary��s office located beneath it. 
A toilet was positioned in the bottom left corner. By 1985, the meeting room had been expanded and converted into a living room, 
while a large bathroom and shower replaced the previous offices and toilet. The florist shop now features a gift card room in the top left corner, with a large open space for flowers and a play area situated in the bottom left. 
On the right side of the building, the kitchen in the top corner has remained consistent across all versions of the floorplan. In contrast, the manager’s office and reception area, formerly used for bedrooms in the apartment, 
have been repurposed as an office and additional flower display space in the current layout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map illustrates significant changes to the city since 1950, clearly showing its transformation into a more residential and accessible urban area, complemented by the construction of a long lake and an expanded business district.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1950, the city had a population of 20,000, which has since increased tenfold to 200,000. Initially, the residential zone was confined to the area north of the main east-west road. Currently, this zone has expanded in all directions, and additional major roads have been constructed in the southern half of the city. Furthermore, the once narrow river that ran through the town has been dammed, resulting in the creation of an extensive lake that extends from the west to the east of the residential area. The business district, previously limited to the city’s center, now encompasses areas along both the northern and southern shores of the lake. The original bridge over the river now spans the lake, and a new bridge has been erected near the eastern dam. Additionally, a second government building has been established to the south, and the airport to the east has more than doubled its size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map delineates the transformation of the sports courts area at a university from 1990 to the present day. Initially, the area featured fewer courts for tennis and basketball, positioned near a park with trees and grass as well as a car park. By the present day, the park has been replaced by a large basketball court, and the car park has given way to four tennis courts, signifying an increase in sports facilities at the expense of recreational and parking spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, on the right side of the map, a new building has been constructed to house various athletic facilities. Within this structure, the indoor pool and reception area have retained their original locations. However, the changing room located beneath these areas has been extended and shifted slightly to the right, aligning directly above a newly established, large fitness center. This center has taken the place of two former tennis courts, which are now situated outside the main building. These changes reflect a significant enhancement in the variety and capacity of the sports facilities offered by the university.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;delineates&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;transformation
featured
significant changes
it is evident that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leaving  untouched.
remains unaltered.
with the addition of
road that runs from
be flanked by  ~ on both sides
give way to
remain unchanged
cleared to make way for a road
persisted unchanged
were diminished
covered by
occupying
located beneath it
extends from
limited to 
encompasses areas along
shores of the lake
aligning directly above
situated
has taken the place of
terminating
enlarged
established
replaced the grasslands
intersecting roads
By 2007
changes within the town
on the opposite side.
lined with shops
expanded vertically
relocated
along a newly established avenue stretching eastward.
top right corner&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">The maps above depict the current layout of Norbiton and the proposed future developments. From a broad perspective, it is evident that the town is set to transition from an industrial focus to a more residential one, with the addition of housing, educational, commercial, and medical facilities. This development will primarily take place in the western and northern parts of Norbiton, leaving only a small section of farmland untouched.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 15</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w15.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 15" /><published>2024-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-20T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w15</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/20/w15.html">&lt;p&gt;the diagram delinates the steps involved in producing cholete. from the comprehensive perspective, it is evident that process is divided in three primary phases: it is commenced with cacao collection from cultivation plot, followed by refining process, cultimated in chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram delineates the steps involved in producing chocolate. From a comprehensive perspective, it is clear that the process is divided into three primary phases: it begins with the collection of cacao from the cultivation plot, followed by a refining process, and culminates in the production of chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the process is commenced with cultivating the ripe red pods from south america, aferica, and indonesia. following this, we seperate white cocoa beans from pods and fermented. Once fermented, they are dried under the sun and putted in large sacks to be transported to the factory by train or lorry. In the factory, these beans undergo roasting at temperature of 350 celcius degrees. the final step involves removing shell and crush them to be small size, subsequently pressed to be liquid chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process commences with the cultivation of ripe red pods from South America, Africa, and Indonesia. Subsequently, white cocoa beans are separated from the pods and fermented. Once fermented, they are sun-dried and packed into large sacks for transport to the factory by train or lorry. At the factory, the beans undergo roasting at a temperature of 350 degrees Celsius. The final step involves removing the shells, crushing the beans to a small size, and pressing them to produce liquid chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram above illustrates the process by which cocoa beans are harvested and transformed into liquid chocolate. From a comprehensive viewpoint, it is evident that this synthesis of human-engineered and natural methods encompasses three primary stages: initial collection and treatment of the beans, their transportation, and their final processing in a manufacturing facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cacao trees are cultivated in South America, Africa, and Indonesia. The pods are harvested when they mature to a red color. Once harvested, the pods are split open, and the white cocoa beans inside are fermented under leaves, then left to dry in the sun. Following this, the beans are packed into large sacks and transported to factories via train or truck for further processing. In the factory, the beans undergo roasting at a temperature of 350 °C. Post-roasting, the beans are ground, allowing for the separation of the outer shell. The final step in the process involves pressing the inner part of the bean, derived from the previous step, into liquid chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The description outlines the systematic process involved in the production and distribution of pineapples for retail. From a broad perspective, it is evident that pineapple production integrates both artificial and natural processes, starting from the fruit’s ripening, through its preparation and sorting into various sizes for final processing. Smaller pineapples are designated for juice production, medium-sized fruits are canned, and the largest specimens are sold whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process for all pineapple products begins in tropical climates, with temperatures ranging from 28°C to 30°C. Pineapples are harvested at various stages of growth, specifically at heights of 26cm, 28cm, and 30cm, each weighing approximately 2kg. Following harvest, the fruits are cleaned and categorized into three size groups. Both the smallest and medium-sized pineapples have their tops removed and rinds peeled. The smaller fruits are then processed through a juice extractor, while the medium ones are sliced and canned. In contrast, the 30cm pineapples are washed, wax-coated, packed into crates, and then shipped overseas via freight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the diagram delinates the steps involved in production of pineapples.
From the comprehensive perspective, It is evident that process devided in three primary phrases: it begins with growing pineapples, followed by classifying them into three groups, cumulating in having each undergo the corresponding process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram delineates the steps involved in the production of pineapples. From a comprehensive perspective, it is evident that the process is divided into three primary phases: it begins with growing pineapples, followed by classifying them into three groups, culminating in having each undergo the corresponding process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process for all pineapple products begins in tropical climates, with temperatures ranging from 28°C to 30°C. Pineapples are harvested at various stages of growth, specifically at heights of 26cm, 28cm, and 30cm, each weighing approximately 2kg. Following harvest, the fruits are cleaned and categorized into three size groups. Both the smallest and medium-sized pineapples have their tops removed and rinds peeled. The smaller fruits are then processed through a juice extractor, while the medium ones are sliced and canned. In contrast, the 30cm pineapples are washed, wax-coated, packed into crates, and then shipped overseas via freight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process for all pineapple products commences in tropical climates, with temperatures ranging between 28°C and 30°C. Pineapples are harvested at various stages of their growth, specifically at heights of 26cm, 28cm, and 30cm, each weighing approximately 2kg. After harvesting, the fruits are cleaned and sorted into three size categories. Both the smallest and medium-sized pineapples have their tops cut off and their rinds peeled. The smaller fruits are then processed through a juice extractor, while the medium-sized ones are sliced and canned. In contrast, the 30cm pineapples are washed, wax-coated, packed into crates, and subsequently shipped overseas via freight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the above picture delinates the transformation of tools from 1.4 million years ago to 0.8 million years ago. From the comprehensive perspective, the size of tool increased over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the vertical length of tools are still unchanged but horizontal length is widen than before. and both are egg shaped and narrowing as close to the top. the recent one is more sophicated and rounded shaped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above illustration delineates the transformation of tools from 1.4 million years ago to 0.8 million years ago. From a comprehensive perspective, the size of the tools increased over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the vertical length of the tools remains unchanged, the horizontal length has widened compared to earlier forms. Both tools are egg-shaped, tapering towards the top. The more recent tool is more sophisticated and features a rounded shape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram provides a comparative analysis of prehistoric tools dating back to 1.4 million and 0.8 million years ago. Overall, the tool from 1.4 million years ago is less refined, featuring rougher edges, whereas the newer tool appears smoother and better preserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the frontal view, the older tool is slightly narrower with a less distinct shape. In contrast, the newer tool tapers to a sharper point and has clearly rounded sides. The side view shows that the older tool is bulkier and has more jagged indentations compared to the smoother one from 800,000 years ago. Regarding the back view, there is a marked difference; the newer tool has fewer major cracks and more closely resembles its front side. Conversely, the older tool is roughly half the size overall and exhibits significant chipping at the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the diagram delinates the production process of water. From the comprehensive perspective, it is evident that steps are involved in three phases: it begins with cleaning water, followed by carbonation and mixing, cumulate in filtering and packaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it commence with filtering raw water and adding water softener and chemicals, after then undergos electrically heating process and additional carbon dioxide. following this, they add colouring and syrup and flavour and mixing. once mixing process, they are filtered and filling with bottles and cans, subsequently packaging to the supermarket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram delineates the production process of carbonated water. From a comprehensive perspective, it is clear that the process unfolds in three main phases: initial purification, followed by carbonation and mixing, and culminating in filtration and packaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process commences with the filtration of raw water and the addition of water softeners and chemicals. The water then undergoes an electrical heating process before carbon dioxide is added. Subsequent steps include the addition of colorants, syrup, and flavors, followed by thorough mixing. After the mixing process, the mixture is filtered and then filled into bottles and cans. Finally, the products are packaged and shipped to supermarkets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram illustrates the process involved in the production of carbonated drinks, clearly outlining a five-stage, man-made sequence. Initially, this process begins with the filtration of raw water, followed by the addition of water softeners and chemicals. The purified water is subsequently heated and then cooled via a cooling pipe, leading to a critical stage where carbon dioxide is infused to create the effervescent effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following carbonation, the water is blended with colorants, syrup, and flavors, and is filtered once more to ensure quality before it is transferred to the bottling and canning lines. The final product is then packaged, boxed, and distributed to supermarkets for sale. This comprehensive overview highlights the technical steps involved from purification to retail distribution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the diagram delinates the steps involved in producing cholete. from the comprehensive perspective, it is evident that process is divided in three primary phases: it is commenced with cacao collection from cultivation plot, followed by refining process, cultimated in chocolate.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 12</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/19/w13.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 12" /><published>2024-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/19/w13</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/19/w13.html">&lt;p&gt;The diagram outlines the process of olive oil production, which can be categorized into three distinct stages: 
initial harvesting and preparation, oil extraction, and finally, storage for future use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process commences with olives being harvested from trees and placed in a collection vat. 
Following this, the olives are de-leafed and washed with water before being transferred to an olive mill, where they are crushed into a paste. 
The resulting olive paste is then processed in a malaxer at a temperature not exceeding 27��C. After this, the paste undergoes centrifugal pressing, which yields virgin olive oil. 
Subsequently, the oil either goes through a separation process, during which waste water is removed, or is decanted, filtering out solids and water. 
Regardless of the separation method used, the final products are stored in a tank to complete the process as outlined in the diagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram outlines the steps involved in producing smoked fish. From an overall perspective, it is clear that the process can be categorized into three primary stages: 
the initial catching and transportation of the fish, followed by storage and processing, and finally, further storage and transportation to retail fish shops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process begins with the fish being caught in nets and transported by boat to a port. Once at the port, the fish are frozen before being thawed in fresh water. 
In the next stage, the fish are sliced open and immersed in a saltwater solution that contains a small amount of yellow coloring. 
Following this, the fish undergo the actual smoking process. Once smoked, the fish are packed into boxes and frozen at a temperature of zero degrees Celsius in larger containers. 
The final step involves grouping the fish into cold storage bins before they are distributed by truck to retail shops for sale to consumers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram above outlines the production process of both pu’erh raw and ripe tea. From a broad perspective, it is evident that the process consists of three primary stages: 
the initial deactivation and drying of the leaves, followed by either aging or fermentation, and concluding with storage for raw tea or compression for ripe tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process begins similarly for both tea varieties, with the leaves being fried in pans to deactivate specific enzymes. After this, the leaves are rolled and dried under the sun. 
At the subsequent stage, the processes diverge. For ripe tea, the loose raw tea undergoes fermentation with mold before being compressed to form the final product. On the other hand, 
in the production of raw tea, the leaves are compressed first and then aged. Once the aging process is complete, the pu’erh raw tea is ready for consumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram delineates the manufacturing process of leather goods intended for retail sale. An overview reveals that this entirely artificial procedure consists of three primary phases: the initial transport of raw materials to the manufacturing facility, the preparation and processing of these materials, and, finally, the production of consumer goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, the leather skins, derived from various animals, are dried. Following this step, they are transported by truck to a factory, where they undergo a washing process using water and lime. The skins are subsequently immersed in additional lime for a specified duration before being processed through a machine equipped with large rollers to flatten them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The document outlines the procedures for manufacturing cement and subsequently using it to produce concrete. The process commences with the initial blending and chemical alteration of clay and limestone, culminating in the packaging of the final cement product, which is then utilized as a component in concrete production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, limestone and clay are gathered and pulverized into a fine powder. This powder is subsequently placed into a cylindrical mixer. The mixture undergoes transformation in a rotating heater, after which it is pulverized a second time and encapsulated in bags as finished cement.
To create concrete, cement is amalgamated with water, sand, and gravel in a concrete mixer. The specific proportions of the ingredients are 15% cement, 10% water, 25% sand, and 50% gravel, which consists of small stones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;delineates
it is evident that
The process commences with
followed by
culminating in
From a comprehensive perspective,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process begins with 
Following this,
undergoes 
subsequently
After this,
Once
The final step involves
process unfolds in
Regardless of
either&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram delinates the refining process of fur of the sheep.
It is evident that these processes are devided in three primary phases: it is commence with 
collecting, followed by distinguishing two parts which is used for recycling and other one is used for making clothes later one is Cumulated in balls of yarn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diagram delineates the refining process of sheep’s fur. It is evident that this process is divided into three primary phases: it begins with the collection of the fur, followed by a separation into two parts—one for recycling and the other for garment production. The latter is eventually spun into balls of yarn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image illustrates the sequence of procedures involved in processing wool and converting it into various products. From a comprehensive viewpoint, it is clear that wool processing entails initial phases of preparing the raw material, intermediate phases that involve the production of tufts, and final phases that yield yarn and finished consumer goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The procedure initiates with the shearing, cleansing, and drying of sheep wool. Following this, the raw wool is spun into string, some of which may be recycled as a byproduct, or it is processed into wool. This wool is then crafted into tufts and subsequently stored. The concluding stages of the process transform these tufts into balls of yarn, which are then utilized in knitting or the manufacture of retail items such as jackets and carpets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;spun into
as a byproduct
garment
knitting&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">The diagram outlines the process of olive oil production, which can be categorized into three distinct stages: initial harvesting and preparation, oil extraction, and finally, storage for future use.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing 12</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/19/w12.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing 12" /><published>2024-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2024-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/19/w12</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2024/10/19/w12.html">&lt;p&gt;the following map illustrates the transformation of deploiment of instructions in the park. 
from the broad perspective, the loads are more wavy than before and there is more artificial structure than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following map delineates the transformation of the deployment of structures within the park. 
From a comprehensive perspective, the paths are now more sinuous than previously, and the number of artificial structures has increased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in 1980, these are surrounded by fence and two gates are perfomed as enterance and exit at the same time but it is disappeared now. the trees on the northen part are now give way to barbeque setting.
the southen parts of road which is flanked by flowers are now replaced by bursh for the east and play ground for the west. the number of bench surrounding the pond is increased to 4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1980, the area was enclosed by a fence, with two gates serving simultaneously as entrances and exits. However, this feature has since been removed. 
The trees in the northern part have been cleared to make space for a barbecue area. 
The southern section of the road, once lined with flowers, has now been replaced with bushes on the east and a playground on the west. 
Additionally, the number of benches surrounding the pond has increased to four.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/br&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The map illustrates the changes made to a park between 1980 and the present day. 
From an overall perspective, it is clear that the park has been further developed for visitors, with additional recreational spaces for outdoor dining, seating, and play. 
The only significant reduction is the removal of flowerbeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1980, the park featured an entrance on the left side above a pond, which was surrounded by three benches, and a second gate at the southern end. 
Both gates have since been removed, the road has been made less linear, and the pond is now encircled by more benches. 
Additionally, two new roads extend from the top and right sides of the map, creating a section with trees, chairs, desks, and barbecue facilities, where previously only trees stood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the bottom right corner, a flowerbed has been replaced with a playground. Another flowerbed located in the bottom left, beneath the pond, has been replaced by wild bush.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the following map illustrates the transformation of deploiment of instructions in the park. from the broad perspective, the loads are more wavy than before and there is more artificial structure than before.</summary></entry></feed>