<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-06T19:24:06+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/06/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-06T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/06/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/06/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the provided map showcases the changes of farmland over time, from 1936 to 2007. there is cross shaped road ,quartering a map, featured with roundabout. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The map provided illustrates the evolution of the farmland from 1936 to 2007. A distinctive feature of this map is the cross-shaped road that divides the map into quarters, complete with a roundabout at the intersection.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
특별한 distinctive
complete with 
at the intersection
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the centre part of map, which is roundabout was initially featured with post office, sweet shop, butchers, flower shop, bank, library.
the post office which was situated at the northwestern area of roundabout still unchanged and so as bank and library which are situated at the southestern part of roundabout. flower shop which was located at the southwestern part of roundabout transformed as travel agent. sweetshop and butchers, which was located northestern part of the roundabout merged and transformed to be supermarket. there was nothing in the remainder but shopping centre was constructed.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
At the heart of the map, the roundabout was initially encircle a variety of establishments: a post office, a sweet shop, a butcher’s, a flower shop, a bank, and a library. The post office, which was located in the northwestern quadrant of the roundabout, has remained unchanged over the years, as have the bank and the library situated in the southeastern quadrant. The flower shop, once at the southwestern section, has now been replaced by a travel agency. The sweet shop and the butcher’s, which were in the northeastern part of the roundabout, have combined and been replaced by a supermarket. Where there was previously vacant space, a shopping centre has now been constructed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
centre -&amp;gt; heart
many kinds of -&amp;gt; a variety of
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was three trees at the northwestern part of map, but decreased by one tree.
the cycle path at the southwestern part refined to be plain curved road. the residential area was prosperous at the river basin at the northestern part of the map.
the government offices and farm land was at the remainder but transformed as museum and golf course.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To the northwest of the map, there were originally three trees, but this number has since decreased to two. The cycle path in the southwestern quarter has been upgraded to a smooth, curved road. The residential zone, thriving in the northeastern river basin, has expanded over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where government buildings and farmland once stood in the remaining quadrants of the map, they have now given way to a museum and a golf course, reflecting significant changes in land use over the 71-year span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
있던곳 -&amp;gt; where ~ once stood
changed to -&amp;gt; given way to
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the provided map showcases the changes of farmland over time, from 1936 to 2007. there is cross shaped road ,quartering a map, featured with roundabout. The map provided illustrates the evolution of the farmland from 1936 to 2007. A distinctive feature of this map is the cross-shaped road that divides the map into quarters, complete with a roundabout at the intersection. 특별한 distinctive complete with at the intersection the centre part of map, which is roundabout was initially featured with post office, sweet shop, butchers, flower shop, bank, library. the post office which was situated at the northwestern area of roundabout still unchanged and so as bank and library which are situated at the southestern part of roundabout. flower shop which was located at the southwestern part of roundabout transformed as travel agent. sweetshop and butchers, which was located northestern part of the roundabout merged and transformed to be supermarket. there was nothing in the remainder but shopping centre was constructed. At the heart of the map, the roundabout was initially encircle a variety of establishments: a post office, a sweet shop, a butcher’s, a flower shop, a bank, and a library. The post office, which was located in the northwestern quadrant of the roundabout, has remained unchanged over the years, as have the bank and the library situated in the southeastern quadrant. The flower shop, once at the southwestern section, has now been replaced by a travel agency. The sweet shop and the butcher’s, which were in the northeastern part of the roundabout, have combined and been replaced by a supermarket. Where there was previously vacant space, a shopping centre has now been constructed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">colloqual</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/06/colloqual.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="colloqual" /><published>2023-11-06T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/06/colloqual</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/06/colloqual.html">&lt;p&gt;누구가 의도한대로 행동하다
playing right into the hands of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;누구에게 공로가 제겨지다
be outdone by someone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;어느 입장이 되다
take a stand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;결집하다
rally&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;똑똑해야한다
takes a lot of brains&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;화나게만들다
not to tick off&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;돕다
aid&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;속임수
ruse
under the pretext of
pretext가 좀더 정교한 속임수&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;고충
anguish&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;깊은고민
despair&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;직감
hunch&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;비슷하다
more or less&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;긴장되는 순간
cliff hanger&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;미끼
bait&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;걸림돌
hitch&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;너에게 빚을지다
indebted to you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;어떤일을 미루는중
procrastinate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;부탁한다
i’m counting on you&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">누구가 의도한대로 행동하다 playing right into the hands of</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/05/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-05T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/05/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/05/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the provided map showcases changes of swimming pool over times. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided map illustrates the evolution of a swimming pool facility over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the building has been built present days containing every amenity relevent to swimming pool, reception, cafe, changingroom, fitness centre. before that building, there was cafe and reception at the same place as now, the western north part of building, also same as pool, which was initially located northeastern and now situated northen area of building. changing room was initially located beneath reception but it moved little bit eastward, meanwhile tennis court moved westward to outside of building , where car park was located, and fitness centre is constructed at the place which tennis court has been.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the current building, equipped with modern amenities such as a swimming pool, reception area, cafe, changing rooms, and a fitness center, stands as a testament to recent development. Previously, the cafe and reception were situated in the same location as they are today, in the western-northern part of the building. The pool, which was originally in the northeastern section, has since been relocated to the northern part of the building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The changing rooms have also seen a shift; originally placed directly beneath the reception, they have now moved slightly to the east. The tennis court has been relocated to the west, outside of the building, taking over what used to be a car park area. In the tennis court’s former location, a new fitness center has been constructed.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
변한거처럼 보이다 -&amp;gt; have also seen a shift
equipped with
대표하다 -&amp;gt; stands as a testament
as the present days -&amp;gt; as they are today
relocated
occupied where -&amp;gt; taking over
former location
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
basketball court is located at the northwestern part of map where park was originally located
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, there is a basketball court which can be found in the northwestern part of the map. This court is situated where there once was a park.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the provided map showcases changes of swimming pool over times. The provided map illustrates the evolution of a swimming pool facility over time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/04/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-04T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-04T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/04/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/04/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the provided map showcases the changes of secondary school over time, from 1950, 1980, to 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The provided map offers a visual representation of how the secondary school has evolved over time, illustrating changes from 1950 through 1980, and up to 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;offers visual representation
to -&amp;gt; up to
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;initially, the school,beneath the main road, was only occupied eastern half section of map, southen half of which was playground and rest was building.
another side of map was composed of houses and farmland, also southen half of which was farmland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, the school located below the main road occupied only the eastern half of the map. Of this section, the southern half was designated as a playground, while the remainder was occupied by the school building. On the other side of the map, the area was made up of houses and farmland, with the southern half being exclusively farmland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;exclusively
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in 1980, school was extended to the western part to occupying whole part of the map.
western area was made up of car park, science block, sports field. sports field was took place which exactly farmland was situated. carpark occupied western half area of remainder area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1980, the school expanded westward to occupy the entire area of the map. The western portion was developed to include a car park, a science block, and a sports field. The sports field was constructed on the exact spot where the farmland used to be. Additionally, the car park took up the western half of the remaining area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whole part -&amp;gt; entire area&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in 2010, the sports field and play ground was compressed at the right side, with playground being major section of which. and car park is extended to the southward which sports field initially occupied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By 2010, the sports field and playground had been consolidated on the right side of the area, with the playground occupying the larger section. Meanwhile, the car park was extended southward into the space that was initially used by the sports field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in 2010 -&amp;gt; by 2010
at the right side -&amp;gt; on the right side
meanwhile 
extended into the space
used as -&amp;gt; used by(사실 비슷한뜻)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the provided map showcases the changes of secondary school over time, from 1950, 1980, to 2010.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/03/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-03T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-03T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/03/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/03/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the provided map illustrates the transformation occered within the city from 1950 until present days.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided map showcases the city’s transformation from 1950 to the present day.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
–
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there has been initially small buisness district, undergone through by two road, one bisect that region by southen part and northen part and other bisect that  by estern part and western part. the upper part of later road little bit bent to the eastern side. and residential area was only situated above the former road, flank the upper part of business district.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Initially, there was a modestly sized business district intersected by two main roads: one dividing the area into southern and northern sections, and the other cutting through the eastern and western parts. The northern road curved slightly eastward. The residential zone was confined to the area north of this road, hugging the upper boundary of the business district.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
part -&amp;gt; section
divide, cutting through
bent -&amp;gt; curved
eastern side -&amp;gt; eastward
flank -&amp;gt; hugging
upper part -&amp;gt; upper boundary
–
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
now additional road is constructed below the lake which of part small river initially situated. which is parallel to the horizontal road but at the east end, it is connected at the middle part of that road, forming the another bridge cross the lake. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Now, a new road has been laid out beneath the lake, where there used to be a small river. This new thoroughfare runs parallel to the existing east-west road and joins it midway, creating another bridge that spans the lake.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
constructed -&amp;gt; laid out
below -&amp;gt; beneath (beneath는 접촉하다는 뜻도 포함)
–
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the initial bridge cross the river lenghten to connect each side of lake, business district and residential area extended to below part of the lake, residential area get to completely sourrounded business district.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The original bridge over the river has been extended to link both shores of the lake. Meanwhile, the business district and the residential area have both expanded southward beyond the lake. The residential zone now completely encircles the business district.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
connect -&amp;gt; link
southward beyond
surrounded -&amp;gt; encircles
–
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the dam is constructed at the end of lake and airport is augmentated.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, a dam has been erected at the lake’s edge, and the airport has been significantly expanded.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
constructed -&amp;gt; erected
end of lake -&amp;gt; lake’s edge&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the provided map illustrates the transformation occered within the city from 1950 until present days. The provided map showcases the city’s transformation from 1950 to the present day. –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the provided map illustrate the changes of the park over the 40years from 1980 until now. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided map delineates the transformations that have occurred within a park over a span of 40 years, from 1980 to the present day.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
changes -&amp;gt; occered within 
over the -&amp;gt; over a span of
now -&amp;gt; present day
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there was few trees situated at the northen eastern corner triangle part of park. which is transformed into rectangular part, added chairs and desks and barbecue zone.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In 1980, a small cluster of trees was positioned in the northeastern corner of the park, forming a triangular area. This space has since evolved into a rectangular section, now featuring added chairs, tables, and a designated barbecue zone.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;few -&amp;gt; cluster of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;northestern.
part -&amp;gt; section
(바베큐존이 되었다)designated barbecue zone
featuring 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was no road at the northen and estern part of park starts from center. but it appears nowadays. the deployment of bench in the vicinity of pond changed and number increased by 1, 3 to 4. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally, there were no pathways in the northern and eastern sections of the park, starting from the center. However, these have been constructed in recent years. The arrangement and quantity of benches near the pond have also changed, with the number increasing from three to four.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
road -&amp;gt; pathways 인도
appears nowadays -&amp;gt; constructed in recent years
deployment -&amp;gt; arrangment
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was flowers around the southen gate but the left side of it changed to the bush and right side of it changed as play ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Around the southern entrance, there were initially flower beds. These have undergone changes as well; the area to the left has been converted into a bushy zone, while the right side has been transformed into a playground.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
it changed -&amp;gt; it have undergone changes
꽃밭 -&amp;gt; flower beds
—&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the provided map illustrate the changes of the park over the 40years from 1980 until now. The provided map delineates the transformations that have occurred within a park over a span of 40 years, from 1980 to the present day. changes -&amp;gt; occered within over the -&amp;gt; over a span of now -&amp;gt; present day</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/11/02/writing2.html">&lt;p&gt;the depicted map outlines the transformation of region around certain house from 1990 to 2010. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The map provided illustrates the changes in the vicinity of a particular house over a 20-year period, from 1990 to 2010.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
region around -&amp;gt; in the vicinity of
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the garden is located at the upper part of the house. at 1990 and it is later appeared more at the right below part of map, adjacent and above the main road. there was cottage at the left part of road which is changed to the cafe
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In 1990, a garden was situated to the north of the house. Over time, this garden expanded towards the southeastern part of the map, adjacent to and north of the main road. Initially, there was a cottage to the west of the road, which was later transformed into a cafe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the enterance is open to the right part of house and shop is extent to the connected room while mergiing these rooms.
the store room is located at the left right part.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The entrance to the house opened to the east, and over the years, a shop was extended into an adjoining room, effectively merging these spaces. Additionally, a storeroom was located to the northeast of the house.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
right  -&amp;gt; east
extended to the connected room -&amp;gt; extended into adjoining room&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the depicted map outlines the transformation of region around certain house from 1990 to 2010. The map provided illustrates the changes in the vicinity of a particular house over a 20-year period, from 1990 to 2010. region around -&amp;gt; in the vicinity of the garden is located at the upper part of the house. at 1990 and it is later appeared more at the right below part of map, adjacent and above the main road. there was cottage at the left part of road which is changed to the cafe In 1990, a garden was situated to the north of the house. Over time, this garden expanded towards the southeastern part of the map, adjacent to and north of the main road. Initially, there was a cottage to the west of the road, which was later transformed into a cafe.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;depicted map outlines the process of processing olive beginning with harvesting culmulating with storage tank or delivery to the factory for post processing.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The illustrated map vividly depicts the intricate journey of olives, starting from their harvesting and culminating in their eventual storage in tanks or transportation to a factory for further processing.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;복잡한(작은 서로 얽힌) intricate
process -&amp;gt; journey&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
first olive is collected from the tree via collection vat.
once it is collected, it is gone through leafting and washing process before get in olive mill to be crushing.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Initially, olives are meticulously gathered from trees using collection vats. Once harvested, they undergo a thorough cleaning process which includes leaf removal and washing. This prepares them for the next crucial step.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;섬세하게 meticulously
gone through -&amp;gt; undergo through&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
after crushing process, it is pasted through malaxer with -27 degree celcious and send to the centrifugal press machine. the pomace is send to the another factory as aforementioned. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The cleaned olives are then transported to an olive mill, where they are crushed. Following this, the crushed olives are mixed in a malaxer at a controlled temperature of -27 degrees Celsius. This process is essential for enhancing oil extraction.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
after crushing process -&amp;gt; Following this
with -27 degree celcious -&amp;gt; at a controlled temperature of -27 degrees Celsius&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the virgin oils post processed again which is seperation or decantation before store.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Afterwards, the olive paste is directed to a centrifugal press machine. Here, the oil is extracted while the remaining solid residue, known as pomace, is sent to a separate facility for further use.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The extracted virgin oil undergoes additional refinement. This involves processes like separation or decantation to ensure purity and quality. Finally, the refined oil is either carefully stored in tanks or dispatched to factories for additional post-processing stages.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;delivered to -&amp;gt; dispatched to
post-processing stages
—&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">depicted map outlines the process of processing olive beginning with harvesting culmulating with storage tank or delivery to the factory for post processing. The illustrated map vividly depicts the intricate journey of olives, starting from their harvesting and culminating in their eventual storage in tanks or transportation to a factory for further processing.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;the depicted picture shows the delivery process of fish starting with fishing culmulating with fishshop sell.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The provided diagram illustrates the stages involved in the delivery process of fish, from the initial catch to the final sale at a fish shop.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
first we catch fish with net on the sea and deliver that to the port. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process begins at sea, where fish are caught using nets. Once caught, the fish are transported to a port. Upon arrival, they are immediately stored in a freezing environment to preserve their freshness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
we store them freezing and over time, we thaw them in fresh water and cut open.
and then we coloring them as yellow in the saltwater, smoking.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
After some time, these frozen fish are thawed in fresh water and then gutted. The next step involves coloring the fish yellow by immersing them in saltwater and subjecting them to a smoking process. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
and over time -&amp;gt; after some time
손질하다 gutted 
매우 실망하다 gutted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;then we freeze them at the 0 celcius temperature 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Once this is completed, the fish are frozen again, this time at a temperature of 0 degrees Celsius, ensuring they remain in a preserved state. They are then stored accordingly until they are ready for distribution.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
then -&amp;gt; once ~~
remain at ~state -&amp;gt; remain in ~state
and then -&amp;gt; then ~ accordingly
until ready for distribution&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and store them and distribute them to the fish shop sell
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The final step in the process involves delivering these preserved fish to fish shops, where they are ultimately sold to customers. This comprehensive journey from the sea to the shop ensures that the fish remain fresh and high in quality for the end consumer.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
comprehensive journey
remain high in quality
for the end consumer&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the depicted picture shows the delivery process of fish starting with fishing culmulating with fishshop sell. The provided diagram illustrates the stages involved in the delivery process of fish, from the initial catch to the final sale at a fish shop.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing map</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing map" /><published>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/26/writing2.html">&lt;p&gt;depicted map shows the development plan of river basin. 
there is no bridge cross the river but they plan to build that house above the river with constructing the connected bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The illustrated map outlines a development plan for a river basin area. Presently, there is no bridge crossing the river, but there are plans to build one along with houses situated above the river, connected by the proposed bridge.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
shows -&amp;gt; outlines
river basin -&amp;gt; river basin area
now -&amp;gt; presently&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
there was initially the raod featured roundabout and few factories are located around that roundabout and located along the load streached right side of roundabout. 
they are planning to vanish every factory and replace that as housing along the load streach to the right side. 
and construct them adjacent to the road between bridge and roundabout aforementioned. and they will build additional road at the upper left side of roundabout and two housing accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Initially, the area features a road with a roundabout. Several factories are situated around this roundabout and along the road extending from its right side. The plan involves demolishing these factories and replacing them with housing units along the road stretching to the right of the roundabout. These houses will be constructed adjacent to the road, situated between the proposed bridge and the existing roundabout. Additionally, a new road is planned to be built on the upper left side of the roundabout, flanked by two housing units.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
vanishing -&amp;gt; demolishing
replace as -&amp;gt; replace with
flanked by two housing units.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
they are planning to construct few amenities like shops and medical centre located near the roundabout. playground located above the housing which is located at the right side of roundabout. and at the end of that road, there will be school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The development plan also includes the construction of various amenities. Shops and a medical center are planned to be located near the roundabout. Above the housing on the right side of the roundabout, there will be a playground. At the end of this road, a school is proposed to be built.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
and they planning to make new roundabout at the below part of aforementioned roundabout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, there are plans to create a new roundabout below the existing one, enhancing the overall connectivity and accessibility of the area.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">depicted map shows the development plan of river basin. there is no bridge cross the river but they plan to build that house above the river with constructing the connected bridge.</summary></entry></feed>