<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-19T14:23:50+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing1" /><published>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-19T06:23:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/19/writing1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
Some people think that government is wasting money on the arts and that this money could be better spent elsewhere
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To what extent do you agree with this view?
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
Art seems to take up our unconsciousness part which art we were used to express our emotion which cannot expressed in language so it is revealed in various way since the ancient, some is in griving on the wall, some is form of sounds. some people assert art is waste of money and i agree with them on some level and will explain with the following parpgraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
revised -&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Art seems to tap into the unconscious part of ourselves that we struggle to express through language, enabling us to convey our emotions in various ways. Throughout history, art has taken diverse forms, including wall engravings and auditory compositions. While some individuals argue that art is a waste of money, I partially agree with them and will explain my perspective further in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
seems like -&amp;gt; seems to
&lt;br /&gt;
since the ancient -&amp;gt; Throughout history
&lt;br /&gt;
revealed in various way -&amp;gt; has taken diverse forms
&lt;br /&gt;
on some level -&amp;gt; partially
&lt;br /&gt;
with the following paragraph -&amp;gt; in the following paragraph
&lt;br /&gt;
will explain -&amp;gt; will explain my perspective further
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Art has been served as important role in our mental stability. No matter how much we are rich or poor, we like to see beautiful scence and music which seems console and empathy ourselves. so government’s investment to art can improve our lives on some way largly or smally
&lt;br /&gt;
revised -&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Art plays an important role in maintaining our mental stability. Regardless of our wealth or poverty, we all have an innate inclination to appreciate beautiful scenery and music, as they offer solace and evoke empathy within us. Therefore, government investment in art can significantly enhance our lives, whether in significant or subtle ways.
&lt;br /&gt;
has been served -&amp;gt; plays
&lt;br /&gt;
mental stability -&amp;gt; maintaining mental stability
&lt;br /&gt;
no matter how -&amp;gt; regardless of 
&lt;br /&gt;
rich or poor -&amp;gt; wealth or poverty
&lt;br /&gt;
like to see -&amp;gt; have an innate inclination to appreciate
&lt;br /&gt;
console -&amp;gt; solace
&lt;br /&gt;
invest to -&amp;gt; invest in
&lt;br /&gt;
largly or smally -&amp;gt; whether in significant or subtle ways
&lt;br /&gt;
but there is some people who are hard to serve even just themselves so they priority basic tools of life over the art which situation comes from increasing difference between wealth and poverty because of matthew effect but that doesn’t come to conclution that art is lake of meaning
&lt;br /&gt;
However, there are people who struggle to fulfill even their basic needs, prioritizing survival over art. This situation arises from the growing wealth and poverty disparity, known as the Matthew effect. Nevertheless, this does not lead to the conclusion that art lacks meaning.
&lt;br /&gt;
there is some people -&amp;gt; there are people
&lt;br /&gt;
serve even just themselves -&amp;gt; fulfill even their basic needs
&lt;br /&gt;
basic tools of life -&amp;gt; survival
&lt;br /&gt;
comes from -&amp;gt; arises from
&lt;br /&gt;
difference -&amp;gt; disparity(greater level)
&lt;br /&gt;
because of -&amp;gt; known as
&lt;br /&gt;
come to conclution -&amp;gt; lead to the conclution&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q Some people think that government is wasting money on the arts and that this money could be better spent elsewhere To what extent do you agree with this view? A Art seems to take up our unconsciousness part which art we were used to express our emotion which cannot expressed in language so it is revealed in various way since the ancient, some is in griving on the wall, some is form of sounds. some people assert art is waste of money and i agree with them on some level and will explain with the following parpgraph. revised -&amp;gt; Art seems to tap into the unconscious part of ourselves that we struggle to express through language, enabling us to convey our emotions in various ways. Throughout history, art has taken diverse forms, including wall engravings and auditory compositions. While some individuals argue that art is a waste of money, I partially agree with them and will explain my perspective further in the following paragraph. seems like -&amp;gt; seems to since the ancient -&amp;gt; Throughout history revealed in various way -&amp;gt; has taken diverse forms on some level -&amp;gt; partially with the following paragraph -&amp;gt; in the following paragraph will explain -&amp;gt; will explain my perspective further Art has been served as important role in our mental stability. No matter how much we are rich or poor, we like to see beautiful scence and music which seems console and empathy ourselves. so government’s investment to art can improve our lives on some way largly or smally revised -&amp;gt; Art plays an important role in maintaining our mental stability. Regardless of our wealth or poverty, we all have an innate inclination to appreciate beautiful scenery and music, as they offer solace and evoke empathy within us. Therefore, government investment in art can significantly enhance our lives, whether in significant or subtle ways. has been served -&amp;gt; plays mental stability -&amp;gt; maintaining mental stability no matter how -&amp;gt; regardless of rich or poor -&amp;gt; wealth or poverty like to see -&amp;gt; have an innate inclination to appreciate console -&amp;gt; solace invest to -&amp;gt; invest in largly or smally -&amp;gt; whether in significant or subtle ways but there is some people who are hard to serve even just themselves so they priority basic tools of life over the art which situation comes from increasing difference between wealth and poverty because of matthew effect but that doesn’t come to conclution that art is lake of meaning However, there are people who struggle to fulfill even their basic needs, prioritizing survival over art. This situation arises from the growing wealth and poverty disparity, known as the Matthew effect. Nevertheless, this does not lead to the conclusion that art lacks meaning. there is some people -&amp;gt; there are people serve even just themselves -&amp;gt; fulfill even their basic needs basic tools of life -&amp;gt; survival comes from -&amp;gt; arises from difference -&amp;gt; disparity(greater level) because of -&amp;gt; known as come to conclution -&amp;gt; lead to the conclution</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Use chatgpt for free on mac</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/chatgpt.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Use chatgpt for free on mac" /><published>2023-05-17T13:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-17T13:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/chatgpt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/chatgpt.html">&lt;p&gt;Join the membership at openai.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Download chatgpt from the following link.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
https://github.com/vincelwt/chatgpt-mac
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Use.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="tool" /><summary type="html">Join the membership at openai. Download chatgpt from the following link. https://github.com/vincelwt/chatgpt-mac Use.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to create and maintain gitblog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/gitblog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to create and maintain gitblog" /><published>2023-05-17T11:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-17T11:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/gitblog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tool/2023/05/17/gitblog.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;create&quot;&gt;create&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First you should install homebrew.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If you type ruby -v in your own terminal, it will display 2.6.8.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I recommand you to download 2.7.8 because jekyll need &amp;gt;2.7 and there are often many issues after big update. as 2.7.8 is just before version 3.0.0, it provides a more stable option.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Homebrew always download the lastest version which is unstable. by RBM, you can install ruby 2.7.8. i don’t recommand downloading rbenv due to some tricky issues with it in this situation.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Afterward, you should clone a theme from here http://jekyllthemes.org
and type following command in the terminal within the folder where you downloaded theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bundler&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;install&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;gem&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;install&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bundler&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you can see the basic theme running on your local server.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;maintain&quot;&gt;maintain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
To put it simply, you can make your own blog by just typing following command in your terminal after modify your files.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;bundle&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;exec&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;serve&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you can modify your 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;_posts
&lt;br /&gt;
_includes (arrange section on your own homepage)
&lt;br /&gt;
README.md (introduction of homepage)
&lt;br /&gt;
_config.yml (basic information)
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is meaningless to modify _site as it is included in gitignore.
&lt;br /&gt;
Because it will be changed each time by running the command “bundle exec jekyll serve”.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="tool" /><summary type="html">create First you should install homebrew. If you type ruby -v in your own terminal, it will display 2.6.8. I recommand you to download 2.7.8 because jekyll need &amp;gt;2.7 and there are often many issues after big update. as 2.7.8 is just before version 3.0.0, it provides a more stable option. Homebrew always download the lastest version which is unstable. by RBM, you can install ruby 2.7.8. i don’t recommand downloading rbenv due to some tricky issues with it in this situation. Afterward, you should clone a theme from here http://jekyllthemes.org and type following command in the terminal within the folder where you downloaded theme. ```ruby bundler install</summary></entry></feed>