<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-19T20:30:04+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing1-2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing1-2" /><published>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-2.html">&lt;p&gt;there is two proposed region. the first one is located on the  north and second one is located on the south part.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There are two proposed regions. The first region is located to the north, while the second is to the south.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
located on -&amp;gt; located to (두번째 쓸때 located 생략가능)
and -&amp;gt; while
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
the first one is located upper side of rail, left of river, right of housing estate.
both city is located far from golf course. city centre is surrounded by road, traversed by river.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The northern region is situated above the railway, to the left of the river, and to the right of a housing estate. Both cities are distant from the golf course, with the city center being encircled by roads and bisected by a river.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
located -&amp;gt; situated
upper side -&amp;gt; above
far from -&amp;gt; are distant from
surrounded -&amp;gt; being encircled
are traversed -&amp;gt; bisected
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
railway is connect between north region and south region industrial estate is near south region 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A railway connects the northern and southern regions, and an industrial estate is situated near the southern region.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
north, south -&amp;gt; northern region, southern region
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
traversed =  goes through&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">there is two proposed region. the first one is located on the north and second one is located on the south part. There are two proposed regions. The first region is located to the north, while the second is to the south. located on -&amp;gt; located to (두번째 쓸때 located 생략가능) and -&amp;gt; while the first one is located upper side of rail, left of river, right of housing estate. both city is located far from golf course. city centre is surrounded by road, traversed by river. The northern region is situated above the railway, to the left of the river, and to the right of a housing estate. Both cities are distant from the golf course, with the city center being encircled by roads and bisected by a river. located -&amp;gt; situated upper side -&amp;gt; above far from -&amp;gt; are distant from surrounded -&amp;gt; being encircled are traversed -&amp;gt; bisected railway is connect between north region and south region industrial estate is near south region A railway connects the northern and southern regions, and an industrial estate is situated near the southern region. north, south -&amp;gt; northern region, southern region traversed = goes through</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing1" /><published>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/10/19/writing1-1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
that diagram illustrates making and delivery process of rock. 
there are totally 7 process starting with digging cumulating with delivery
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The diagram illustrates the creation and delivery process of bricks.
In total, there are seven processes, beginning with digging and culminating in delivery.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;make -&amp;gt; create
start from -&amp;gt; beginning with
&lt;br /&gt;
first digger is employed for dig the clay and digged clay is put on the metal grid, filtering to smaller one on the roller.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
First, a digger is employed to excavate the clay. The excavated clay is then placed on a metal grid, where it is filtered into smaller pieces via a roller.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;be employed for -&amp;gt; be employed to
smaller one -&amp;gt; smaller pieces
on the roller -&amp;gt; via a roller
&lt;br /&gt;
then sand and water is added to that smaller one. that is formed as brick by cutting them or moulding.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Next, sand and water are added to these smaller pieces. These are then formed into bricks either by cutting or molding.
&lt;br /&gt;
formed as  -&amp;gt; formed into
or -&amp;gt; either or
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;after formed as brick, they are dried for more than 24 hours and then heated in the kiln, first heated in moderate temperature and high temperature and finally cooled for 2 to 3days. following packaging and delivery
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Once shaped into bricks, they are dried for more than 24 hours. Subsequently, they are heated in a kiln, initially at a moderate temperature, followed by a high temperature. They are then cooled for 2 to 3 days. The process concludes with packaging and delivery.
&lt;br /&gt;
formed as -&amp;gt; shaped into
followed by -&amp;gt; concludes with&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">that diagram illustrates making and delivery process of rock. there are totally 7 process starting with digging cumulating with delivery The diagram illustrates the creation and delivery process of bricks. In total, there are seven processes, beginning with digging and culminating in delivery.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/20/writing1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing1" /><published>2023-07-20T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-20T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/20/writing1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/20/writing1.html">&lt;p&gt;the graph illustrated on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;respondents
(시작부)turning to 2010
with regard to the
over the period
차지하다 accounted for
the percentage is forcast to reach
expenditure, types of
지출 outlay
어디에 대해서 in terms of&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">the graph illustrated on</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/20/writing-n.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing" /><published>2023-07-20T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-20T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/20/writing%20n</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/20/writing-n.html">&lt;p&gt;Although we are capable of discerning meaningful content, distorted or unnecessary information can still influence our future learning path. For example, when we come across news about a new fast-food chain, our exposure to fast food increases, leading to a higher likelihood of choosing it. Similarly, when we encounter reports of gun violence in America, we may mistakenly assume that such incidents occur frequently, despite their infrequent nature. This also applies to fake news, which grabs our attention, prompts further investigation, and expands our knowledge in areas that may not hold significant value, ultimately having the same effect as providing unnecessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though we have the ability to recognize meaningful information, distorted or irrelevant content can still impact our future learning journey. For instance, when we come across news about a new fast-food chain, our exposure to fast food increases, making us more likely to choose it. Similarly, encountering reports of gun violence in America might lead us to believe such incidents occur frequently, even if they are relatively rare. This also holds true for fake news, which captures our attention, prompts further investigation, and expands our knowledge in areas that may not hold much value, ultimately resembling the impact of unnecessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;expands our knowledge in areas
simillar effect -&amp;gt; resembling&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way to manage attendants is recommended to vary depending on the characteristics of each department. I believe one of the most prominent personality traits in human beings is being active. Active individuals tend to follow their curiosity, leading to improved intelligence compared to others, as well as greater independence because they challenge traditional practices by asking questions. When active individuals are placed in departments that require continuous change and experimentation, they thrive in such environments. However, if they are placed in departments that do not offer such opportunities, they may experience significant stress. Wearing a costume can create a sense of unity and conformity, but it can also constrain divergent thinking, limiting the possibility of questioning and stifling creativity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The approach to managing attendants should be adapted to suit the specific characteristics of each department. In my view, one of the most prominent personality traits in human beings is being active. Active individuals tend to follow their curiosity, which results in improved intelligence compared to others, and they also exhibit greater independence by questioning conventional practices. When active individuals are assigned to departments that embrace continuous change and experimentation, they thrive in such dynamic environments. However, if they are placed in departments that lack such opportunities, they may experience considerable stress. While wearing a uniform can foster a sense of unity and conformity, it can also limit divergent thinking, restricting the potential for questioning and hindering creativity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;보인다 exhibit
placed to -&amp;gt; assigned to
dynamic environments
considerable stress
장려하다 복돋우다 foster
divergent thinking&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference between men and women lies in their levels of activity. However, being active has its pros and cons. Active individuals are usually good at math, as it requires curiosity to acquire knowledge that is used to refine existing knowledge by distinguishing between different concepts. On the other hand, they may face challenges when learning languages, as language knowledge is often not directly interconnected. The process of selecting a learning approach itself can be perceived as a waste of time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distinction between men and women lies in their levels of activity. However, being active comes with its advantages and disadvantages. Active individuals typically excel in math, as it demands curiosity to acquire knowledge and refine existing understanding by differentiating between various concepts. Conversely, they may encounter difficulties in language learning, as language knowledge is often not directly connected. Moreover, the process of choosing a learning approach itself can be perceived as time-consuming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;usually -&amp;gt; typically
good at -&amp;gt; excel in
distinguishing -&amp;gt; differentiating
seems as -&amp;gt; preceived as&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most prominent reason for crime lies in the disparity between wealth and poverty. According to game theory, when individuals fail to secure enough resources, they resort to competing with and depriving one another, creating a zero-sum game scenario. Resources can take various forms, and their deficiency not only signifies a lack of money but also a lack of self-esteem. Many people resort to robbery or theft to alleviate their financial struggles, while others engage in online crime and sexual offenses due to a sense of inadequacy. Drug-related problems also arise from the wealth-poverty gap, as pharmaceutical companies illegally sell drugs and simultaneously market medicines that mitigate the drugs’ side effects. Such practices are made possible through lobbying efforts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main reason for crime often stems from the disparity between wealth and poverty. Drawing on game theory, when individuals lack sufficient resources, they may resort to competing and depriving one another, leading to a zero-sum game scenario. These resources can take various forms, and their deficiency not only represents a lack of financial means but also a deficiency in self-esteem. Some people turn to robbery or theft to cope with financial difficulties, while others engage in online crime and sexual offenses driven by feelings of inadequacy. Drug-related issues also arise from the wealth-poverty gap, with pharmaceutical companies involved in illegal drug sales while simultaneously marketing medicines that mitigate the drugs’ side effects through lobbying efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;according to -&amp;gt; drawing on
lobbying efforts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the government sends criminals to jail, they often find alternative ways to engage in criminal activities rather than becoming deterred or reforming. This is because the government fails to address the underlying deficiencies that contribute to their criminal behavior. Simply incarcerating individuals and increasing police presence on the streets does not solve the root problem; it is cost-effective but not a comprehensive solution. The key to eliminating crime lies in education. We have a responsibility to guide individuals in the right direction and we can achieve this by incentivizing learning, such as providing financial rewards when we observe significant progress in their knowledge acquisition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the government may send criminals to jail, many of them still find alternative ways to continue their criminal activities rather than being deterred or reformed. This is because the government often overlooks the underlying issues that contribute to their criminal behavior. Simply putting individuals behind bars and increasing police presence on the streets might offer short-term solutions, but it doesn’t address the root cause comprehensively. The ultimate solution to reducing crime lies in education. We have a responsibility to guide individuals toward the right path, and we can achieve this by incentivizing learning. For instance, providing financial rewards when we observe significant progress in their knowledge acquisition can encourage positive change and transformation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role of teachers and parents is to support students in navigating their path towards pursuing happiness. There are numerous ways to pursue happiness, but students often get stuck in just one way because they may not be aware of other options or simply follow what is in front of them. The main role of advisors is to help them broaden their perspective and explore different paths that lead to happiness. Sometimes, you need to encourage them to keep going, and other times, you need to guide them towards better alternatives. If they struggle to adapt to a particular teaching method, you should search for alternative ways to teach. However, it is important not to force them to pursue the path you believe is best, as everyone has different experiences and different ways of finding happiness. There is no one-size-fits-all approach to happiness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role of teachers and parents is to provide support and guidance to students as they embark on their journey to pursue happiness. While there are various paths to achieve happiness, students often get stuck in one direction due to limited exposure or simply following the familiar. As advisors, it is essential to help them expand their horizons and explore different avenues leading to happiness. At times, encouragement is necessary to keep them motivated, while other times, gentle guidance can lead them to better alternatives. If a particular teaching method proves challenging for them, it’s crucial to seek alternative approaches to facilitate their learning. However, it’s important not to impose our own beliefs about the best path to happiness, as each individual’s experiences and preferences are unique. There is no one-size-fits-all formula for achieving happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;start -&amp;gt; embark
expand their horizons
explore different avenues leading to happiness
강요하다 impose
모두 다르다 간단하게 unique
no one-size-fits-all formula&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone has their own unique way of learning. Men often excel in questioning their existing knowledge, while women tend to adapt quickly to newly acquired knowledge. Older people usually focus on organizing their existing knowledge rather than acquiring new knowledge, leveraging their wealth of experience to learn with precision but at a slower pace. On the other hand, young people are often adept at fast-paced learning, although their accuracy may sometimes lag behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each individual has their own distinct approach to learning. Men often excel in their ability to question and challenge their existing knowledge, while women demonstrate a talent for quickly adapting to new information. Older individuals typically prioritize organizing and consolidating their existing knowledge, drawing from their wealth of experience to learn with precision, albeit at a slower pace. Conversely, young people are often proficient at absorbing knowledge rapidly, even though their accuracy may occasionally be compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;everyone -&amp;gt; each
exel in ~ to ~
통합하다 consolidate
정확하게 배우다 learn with precision
부족해지다 accuracy may occasionally be compromised&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Environmental destruction exists in various forms, such as damaged plants and animals. The underlying problems contributing to this destruction include reckless hunting, the transformation of nature to suit human interests, and the indiscriminate discharge of harmful waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Environmental destruction manifests in various forms, including damaged plants and animals. The root causes of this issue encompass reckless hunting, altering nature to align with human interests, and the indiscriminate disposal of harmful waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;현상이 나타나다 manifest
“in various form”
transformation -&amp;gt; altering
to suit -&amp;gt; to align with&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To effectively tackle this issue, it is imperative to address it at an international or governmental level, as opposed to individual efforts. Caring for the environment yields collective benefits for all of humanity, extending beyond the interests of any single individual. The true significance of the rewards derived from such behavior is best realized when we unite in our collective commitment towards environmental preservation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to effectively tackle this issue, it is crucial to address it at an international or governmental level, rather than relying solely on individual efforts. Caring for the environment has far-reaching benefits that extend beyond the interests of any single individual. The true significance of the rewards from such behavior is fully realized when we come together as a collective to commit to environmental preservation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at ~ level
far-reaching benefits&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When considering a job, there are several factors to take into account. Apart from the salary, elements such as the location, colleagues, and the nature of the work play a vital role in achieving a work-life balance. Location matters because it affects our commute time and the weather we encounter. The relationships we build with colleagues can significantly impact our stress levels. And, of course, finding fulfillment and satisfaction in our work stems from the content of the tasks we undertake. All these aspects are crucial in making a well-informed decision when selecting the right job for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When contemplating a job, there are several factors to consider. Besides the salary, elements like the location, colleagues, and the nature of the work play a crucial role in achieving a healthy work-life balance. The location is important as it influences our commute time and exposes us to different weather conditions. The relationships we forge with our colleagues can greatly impact our stress levels. Moreover, finding fulfillment and satisfaction in our work depends on the content of the tasks we undertake. Taking all these aspects into account is essential in making a well-informed decision when selecting the right job for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;consider -&amp;gt; contemplate
build -&amp;gt; forge 
essential to make -&amp;gt; essential in make&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When companies hire employees from other countries, some citizens in their home country may oppose this practice, fearing a reduction in local job opportunities. However, it’s important to recognize that the underlying issue stems from global wealth disparities, which have been exacerbated historically through colonization and dominance by certain regions, particularly Europe. When a country hires individuals from less affluent nations, they indirectly contribute to reducing the wealth disparity between countries. By providing resources and opportunities to people in other parts of the world, it can lead to positive outcomes and foster a more equitable global environment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When companies decide to hire employees from other countries, there might be opposition from some citizens in their home country who fear it could lead to a reduction in local job opportunities. However, it is crucial to understand that the root of this issue lies in the global wealth disparities, which have been historically exacerbated by colonization and dominance from certain regions, notably Europe. When a country chooses to employ individuals from less affluent nations, it indirectly contributes to narrowing the wealth gap between countries. By offering resources and opportunities to people in other parts of the world, it can lead to positive outcomes and foster a more equitable global environment. This approach encourages a collaborative effort towards addressing the underlying issue of wealth disparity on an international scale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at level -&amp;gt; on scale&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the changing nature of industries and the diminishing need for uniting in our collective effort, nuclear families are becoming more prevalent, contrasting with the traditional extended families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the evolving nature of industries and the decreasing necessity for living in close-knit communities, nuclear families are becoming more common, in contrast to the traditional extended families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;contrast to -&amp;gt; contrasting with
close-knit communities
decreasing necessity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the healthcare system continues to advance, our life expectancy increases, resulting in a progressively aging society. Over time, we have proposed numerous solutions to cope with this phenomenon. One of the most prominent suggestions is extending the retirement age, allowing the elderly to contribute their still robust capabilities, thanks to the benefits of modern healthcare, to society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the continuous advancement of the healthcare system, our life expectancy is increasing, leading to a progressively aging society. As a result, we have explored numerous solutions to address this phenomenon. One of the most notable suggestions is extending the retirement age, enabling the elderly to contribute their valuable skills and capabilities, which have been enhanced by modern healthcare, to society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;prominent, notable&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To tackle the issue of increasing obesity rates, there are several approaches we can take. The government can initiate a public nonprofit agency to promote the consumption of low-fat foods. Additionally, individuals can take action by engaging in regular exercise to reduce body fat. However, one of the most crucial behaviors to address is curbing our desire for excessive carbohydrate consumption. This is because consuming too many carbohydrates can have more detrimental effects than not being as active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To address the issue of increasing obesity rates, we can adopt various approaches. The government can establish a public nonprofit agency to encourage the consumption of low-fat foods. On an individual level, regular exercise can help reduce body fat. However, one of the most critical behaviors to address is controlling our excessive carbohydrate intake. Consuming too many carbohydrates can have more detrimental effects on our health compared to not being as physically active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;initiate, establish&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;on an individual level, ~
consumption -&amp;gt; intake&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some attempts to revert to traditional healthcare methods, which contrasts with modern medical technology. This has created some controversy within the healthcare system, as both approaches have historically been enhanced through experimental results. Traditional methods often involve researching the correlation of organs that may not seem directly related, focusing on the neuro system. On the other hand, modern methods concentrate on directly alleviating abnormal symptoms of specific organs and utilize modern analysis technology to explore peripheral areas known to be correlated with those organs.
While modern technology can address most problems, when faced with unprecedented issues, there is a possibility that traditional methods could prove effective. This highlights the ongoing debate between the existing and new approaches in healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an ongoing debate between traditional healthcare methods and modern medical technology. While modern methods have proven effective in addressing most health issues, there are some attempts to revert to traditional practices. Both approaches have been enhanced through experimental results, but they differ in their focus. Traditional methods often research the correlation of seemingly unrelated organs, with a focus on the neuro system. In contrast, modern methods concentrate on directly alleviating specific organ symptoms, utilizing advanced analysis technology to explore related peripheral areas. While modern technology can address most problems, there is a possibility that traditional methods could be effective in handling unprecedented issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;지금 논쟁이 있다 There is an “ongoing” debate
어떤점에서 다르다 they differ in their focus
증상 organ symptoms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As society evolves, there are concerns about losing our traditional customs. However, I firmly believe that embracing transformation and progress is an essential process for improvement. We can let go of corrupted and toxic customs by comparing them with others and adopting well-functioning practices from different cultures. Our customs shouldn’t simply be a mix of various elements but rather a process of referencing and refining practices from different cultures. By doing so, we can preserve the essence of our traditions while incorporating positive changes to adapt to the changing times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As society continues to evolve, there is a growing concern about losing our traditional customs. However, I firmly believe that embracing transformation and progress is crucial for improvement. We can let go of corrupted and toxic customs by comparing them with practices from other cultures and adopting well-functioning elements. Our customs shouldn’t be a mere mix of various elements; instead, we should reference and refine practices from different cultures. By doing so, we can preserve the essence of our traditions while incorporating positive changes that allow us to adapt to the changing times. This way, we can maintain our cultural heritage while also embracing beneficial advancements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;버리다 let go of
그렇게 함으로써, by doing so
유산 heritage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art holds significant importance in society because it serves as a reflection of our culture and values. When we admire and appreciate the culture of other countries through art, we gain insight into their aspirations and ideals. Moreover, art offers a unique medium for us to express our unexplainable emotions and feelings, allowing us to connect with the material on a deeper level. However, since these emotions are difficult to articulate, they become challenging to remember. Consequently, when we lose our art, we risk forgetting some of our distinctive characteristics as a society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art plays a crucial role in society as it acts as a reflection of our culture and values. When we admire and appreciate the art and culture of other countries, we gain valuable insights into their aspirations and ideals. Furthermore, art provides us with a unique way to express our unexplainable emotions and feelings, allowing us to connect with the artwork on a deeper level. However, since these emotions are often challenging to articulate, they become difficult to remember over time. As a result, losing our art could lead to forgetting some of our distinctive characteristics as a society. Therefore, preserving and appreciating art is vital in maintaining our cultural identity and heritage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;명료하다 articulate
cultural heritage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people believe that building a sky train will help ease traffic congestion. However, the construction of a sky train could potentially lead to environmental pollution, including blocking sunlight with its structures. Additionally, if the increased accessibility to the city accelerates population growth, the issue of traffic jams may not improve, and the disparity between wealth and poverty could result in a lifestyle that fails to enjoy the benefits of sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many people believe that constructing a sky train will alleviate traffic congestion, there are potential drawbacks to consider. For instance, the sky train’s structures could cause environmental pollution and obstruct sunlight. Furthermore, if the improved accessibility to the city leads to a surge in population, the traffic congestion issue may persist, and some individuals may not have the opportunity to enjoy the benefits of sunlight due to socioeconomic disparities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;block -&amp;gt; obstruct
may persist
socioeconomic disparities&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">Although we are capable of discerning meaningful content, distorted or unnecessary information can still influence our future learning path. For example, when we come across news about a new fast-food chain, our exposure to fast food increases, leading to a higher likelihood of choosing it. Similarly, when we encounter reports of gun violence in America, we may mistakenly assume that such incidents occur frequently, despite their infrequent nature. This also applies to fake news, which grabs our attention, prompts further investigation, and expands our knowledge in areas that may not hold significant value, ultimately having the same effect as providing unnecessary information.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/19/writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing" /><published>2023-07-19T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-19T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/19/writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/19/writing.html">&lt;p&gt;even though are reasonable enough to descern meaningful information, the problem of providing distorted or unnecessary information is that affect our furture learning direction. for example, when we get to know about new fast food, our knowledge fool of food extended on the direction of fast food which incur increasing probability for us to choose fast food. when we come to reach the news of gun murder in america, we easily think there are lots of gun accident eventhough that is not occer often. this also happened in fake news, which bring our attention and make us to investigate about it also resulting our knowledge to extend to that area, same effect as provided unnescessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although we are capable of discerning meaningful content, distorted or unnecessary information can still influence our future learning path. For example, when we come across news about a new fast-food chain, our exposure to fast food increases, leading to a higher likelihood of choosing it. Similarly, when we encounter reports of gun violence in America, we may mistakenly assume that such incidents occur frequently, despite their infrequent nature. This also applies to fake news, which grabs our attention, prompts further investigation, and expands our knowledge in areas that may not hold significant value, ultimately having the same effect as providing unnecessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the way to manage attendent is recommanded to be different depends on the characteristics of department. i believe the most apparent feature of personality within human beings is active. when someone is active person, they used to choose following their curiousity enabling them to be improved as more intelligent than others. and more independent because they always throw questions to the traditional practice. when they are allocated in department which needs continuous change and everyday try new things, they are fitted in that department but if not, they will be get substantial stress. when we got to wear costum, we can feel united mood and at the same time but that can constrain our deviated way of thinking, so resulting in restrictness of posibility of throwing question, creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way to manage attendants is recommended to vary depending on the characteristics of each department. I believe one of the most prominent personality traits in human beings is being active. Active individuals tend to follow their curiosity, leading to improved intelligence compared to others, as well as greater independence because they challenge traditional practices by asking questions. When active individuals are placed in departments that require continuous change and experimentation, they thrive in such environments. However, if they are placed in departments that do not offer such opportunities, they may experience significant stress. Wearing a costume can create a sense of unity and conformity, but it can also constrain divergent thinking, limiting the possibility of questioning and stifling creativity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;회사의 “성향” -&amp;gt; characteristics
feature of personality -&amp;gt; personality traits
active -&amp;gt; being active
than -&amp;gt; compare to
throw question -&amp;gt; challenge
allocated -&amp;gt; placed
they are fitted -&amp;gt; they thrive in
get stress -&amp;gt; experience stress
united mood -&amp;gt; sense of unity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the disadvantage of communicate on online compare to meet offline is our behavior doesn’t seems to be sincere. if we meet on offline, we should go long to the appointment place on foot to meet friends and this also means we came here even though there is the possibility of meet weild person. and if we meet online, we can’t fully utilize our sensory system. we can’t smell aroma. our image and sound is little bit distorted whilst conveying through internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The disadvantage of online communication compared to meeting offline is that our behavior may not seem as sincere. When meeting offline, we make an effort to physically travel to the meeting place, demonstrating our commitment to meeting friends even in the presence of the possibility of encountering unfamiliar individuals. However, when communicating online, we are unable to fully utilize our sensory system. We cannot experience smells or fully perceive unaltered images and sounds as they may be distorted during transmission over the internet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;seem to be -&amp;gt; seem as
should go -&amp;gt; make an effort (노력해서 가다 의미 포함해야함)
altered 바뀐
conveying -&amp;gt; transmission
communite on online -&amp;gt; communicate online
with -&amp;gt; in the presence of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the difference between man and woman is being active. there is still pros and cons. active person usually good at math which require curiosity to acquire the knowledge which needs to trim the already known knowledge within the effort to tell the difference. but not good at studing language every knowledge composed in language usually not related each other, the process of choosing the way to learn itself is already waste of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference between men and women lies in their levels of activity. However, being active has its pros and cons. Active individuals are usually good at math, as it requires curiosity to acquire knowledge that is used to refine existing knowledge by distinguishing between different concepts. On the other hand, they may face challenges when learning languages, as language knowledge is often not directly interconnected. The process of selecting a learning approach itself can be perceived as a waste of time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;already known -&amp;gt; existing
tell -&amp;gt; distinguishing
is -&amp;gt; can be preceived
trim -&amp;gt; refine&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the most prominent reason of crime lies in the disparity between wealthy and poverty. According to game theory, when they fail to secure enough resource, they begin to compete and deprive each other which curcimstance is referred as zero sum game. the resource appears as various form. dificient of resource not only means lack of money but also lake of self esteem. numerous people commit rob or steal to fill their insufficient of money, they also commit online crime and sexual crime because of insufficient of self esteem. drug problem also occured due to gab between wealthy and poverty. medicine company illegarly sell drug and sell the medicine simultainously which cure the side effect of drug. this become possible because of their lobby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most prominent reason for crime lies in the disparity between wealth and poverty. According to game theory, when individuals fail to secure enough resources, they resort to competing with and depriving one another, creating a zero-sum game scenario. Resources can take various forms, and their deficiency not only signifies a lack of money but also a lack of self-esteem. Many people resort to robbery or theft to alleviate their financial struggles, while others engage in online crime and sexual offenses due to a sense of inadequacy. Drug-related problems also arise from the wealth-poverty gap, as pharmaceutical companies illegally sell drugs and simultaneously market medicines that mitigate the drugs’ side effects. Such practices are made possible through lobbying efforts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;means -&amp;gt; signifies
시나리오 scenario
appears -&amp;gt; can take various form
insufficient of money -&amp;gt; financial struggle
due to a sense of inadequacy 불만때문에
lobbying efforts
sell -&amp;gt; market
cure -&amp;gt; mitigate
pharmaceutical&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;even though governemnt sent them to the jail, they even learn another way to crime rather than scared and be better. because government did’t do anything for mitigate their deficiency. sending to jail and deploying more police on the street doesn’t address underlying problem but cost effective. the root solution to eliminate criminal is emerged from education. we have responsibility to nevigate them to the right direction and we can achieve that through encourage them to learn such like giving money when we check they achieved certain extention of knowledge acquirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the government sends criminals to jail, they often find alternative ways to engage in criminal activities rather than becoming deterred or reforming. This is because the government fails to address the underlying deficiencies that contribute to their criminal behavior. Simply incarcerating individuals and increasing police presence on the streets does not solve the root problem; it is cost-effective but not a comprehensive solution. The key to eliminating crime lies in education. We have a responsibility to guide individuals in the right direction and we can achieve this by incentivizing learning, such as providing financial rewards when we observe significant progress in their knowledge acquisition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;단념하다 deterred
개선되다 be better -&amp;gt; reforming
comprehensive solution
incentivizing -&amp;gt; 보상을 주면서 행동을 유도
encourage -&amp;gt; 그냥 행동을 유도
achieved certain extention -&amp;gt; significant progress&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the role of teacher and parents is support students to nevigate their way to pursuing happiness. there is numerous way to pursuing hapiness but students often stuck in a some just one way because they don’t know any better and Just follow what’s in front of you. so the main role of adviser is to help them to look as far as they need to be happy. sometimes you need to encourage them to keep going, sometimes you need to you need to tell them there is another more good way. if they fail to adapt to class, you should search another way to teach. but you cannot force them to persuing the way you want because no one knows your way is best to pursuing happiness, moreover, everyone have different experience and different way to feel happiness so there is no chance to know the best way to be happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role of teachers and parents is to support students in navigating their path towards pursuing happiness. There are numerous ways to pursue happiness, but students often get stuck in just one way because they may not be aware of other options or simply follow what is in front of them. The main role of advisors is to help them broaden their perspective and explore different paths that lead to happiness. Sometimes, you need to encourage them to keep going, and other times, you need to guide them towards better alternatives. If they struggle to adapt to a particular teaching method, you should search for alternative ways to teach. However, it is important not to force them to pursue the path you believe is best, as everyone has different experiences and different ways of finding happiness. There is no one-size-fits-all approach to happiness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;support in nevigating
don’t know -&amp;gt; not be aware of
멀리보게 만들다 broaden their perspective
or sometimes -&amp;gt; and other times
모두를 만족시키는 -&amp;gt; one-size-fits-all&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;everyone has their own way to learn. the man usually like to questioning their excisting knowledge whereas woman is good at fastly adapt themselves to newly learned knowledge. old people usually try to organize their knowledge rather than aquire more knowledge because they already experienced a lot so they are good at learn accurately but not fast. young people are good at learn fastly but not accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone has their own unique way of learning. Men often excel in questioning their existing knowledge, while women tend to adapt quickly to newly acquired knowledge. Older people usually focus on organizing their existing knowledge rather than acquiring new knowledge, leveraging their wealth of experience to learn with precision but at a slower pace. On the other hand, young people are often adept at fast-paced learning, although their accuracy may sometimes lag behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;뒤쳐지다 lag behind
느린 속도 slower pace
빠른 속도 fast-paced
많은 경험 wealth of experience
정확하게 학습하다 learn with precision
try to -&amp;gt; focus on
leveraging their wealth of experience to learn with precision
get shortsighted
For what it’s worth…
그건 그렇다 치고&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;environmental distruction is existing in various form we can see that as demaged plant and demaged animal the underlying problem of this is Reckless hunting, transformation of nature in the favor of human, indiscriminate discharge of detrimental waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Environmental destruction exists in various forms, such as damaged plants and animals. The underlying problems contributing to this destruction include reckless hunting, the transformation of nature to suit human interests, and the indiscriminate discharge of harmful waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;누구의 입맛에 맞게 -&amp;gt; to suit ~ interests
무분별하게 reckless indiscriminate (전자는 결과를 생각하지 않는 행동, 후자는 선택을 잘 못함)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we have to address with that problem as internation or government level not individually because behavior of caring environment itself benefit every human species not meaningful for just one person who take care of it. so, the reward from this behavior has meaning when we doing this altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To effectively tackle this issue, it is imperative to address it at an international or governmental level, as opposed to individual efforts. Caring for the environment yields collective benefits for all of humanity, extending beyond the interests of any single individual. The true significance of the rewards derived from such behavior is best realized when we unite in our collective commitment towards environmental preservation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it is imperative to address
rather than -&amp;gt; as opposed to
this behavior -&amp;gt; such behavior
is meaningful -&amp;gt; is best realized
doing altogether -&amp;gt; unite in our collective commitment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there is numerous component to take into account for choosing the job. representitively, except for salary, there are location, colleagues, the content of work which of things are the part of work and life balance,. the reason why location is important is it impact on commute time and weather. the stress came from relationship is mostly lies on colleagues, when our content of work is best realized, we feel the satisfaction and fulfillment through the work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When considering a job, there are several factors to take into account. Apart from the salary, elements such as the location, colleagues, and the nature of the work play a vital role in achieving a work-life balance. Location matters because it affects our commute time and the weather we encounter. The relationships we build with colleagues can significantly impact our stress levels. And, of course, finding fulfillment and satisfaction in our work stems from the content of the tasks we undertake. All these aspects are crucial in making a well-informed decision when selecting the right job for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;choosing the job -&amp;gt; considering a job
except for -&amp;gt; apart from
play a vital role “in”
work-life balance
일의 필수요소, 특징 the nature of the work
the reason why location is important -&amp;gt; location matters
tasks we undertake&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when company consider a employee, some company collect them from another country so the citizen of own country opposed to their behavior in the excuse of their decreasing workplace. the most problem underlying numerous worldwide issue arise from disparity between wealth and poverty esepcially excerbated through colonization and domination over another country led by europe. when country hire people from another country which country is not wealthy as their country, they indirectly alleviate the disparity across countries by giving resource to people who live in another country which is good phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When companies hire employees from other countries, some citizens in their home country may oppose this practice, fearing a reduction in local job opportunities. However, it’s important to recognize that the underlying issue stems from global wealth disparities, which have been exacerbated historically through colonization and dominance by certain regions, particularly Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a country hires individuals from less affluent nations, they indirectly contribute to reducing the wealth disparity between countries. By providing resources and opportunities to people in other parts of the world, it can lead to positive outcomes and foster a more equitable global environment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;behavior -&amp;gt; practive
어떤걸 두려워해서 fearing a 
과거의 일을 언급할때 historically
colonization and dominance by certain regions
affluent nations
foster a more equitable global environment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With transformation in the nature of industry, disappearing necessarity of cowork, the share of nuclear family is increasing as opposed to grand family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the changing nature of industries and the diminishing need for uniting in our collective effort, nuclear families are becoming more prevalent, contrasting with the traditional extended families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;share of ~ high -&amp;gt; prevalent
as opposed to -&amp;gt; contrasting with
grand family -&amp;gt; traditional extended families&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the improvement of healthcare system, since we become to live longer, society is aging more and more. we suggested numerous solution to address such phenomenon so far. the most prominent suggestion is we can prolong the retirement age so as to leverage elderly’s still vigorous power ,which is due to modernized healthcare system, to the society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the healthcare system continues to advance, our life expectancy increases, resulting in a progressively aging society. Over time, we have proposed numerous solutions to cope with this phenomenon. One of the most prominent suggestions is extending the retirement age, allowing the elderly to contribute their still robust capabilities, thanks to the benefits of modern healthcare, to society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;의료 -&amp;gt; healthcare
life expectancy
increasingly -&amp;gt; progressively
proposed 제안받다
extending, postpone
여전히 건장한 능력 still robust capabilities
due to -&amp;gt; thanks to benefits of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;individual and government plays different role each other. individual watch governemnt to not corrupt but government watch individual to not commit crime and hram each other. the good government usually commit to address socialwide problem such as environmental preservation, economic crisis, conflict between nation. and also they can start governmental agency which spesically deals with social problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Individuals and the government each have distinct roles to play in society. While individuals keep an eye on the government to prevent corruption, the government, in turn, monitors individuals to deter crime and harm to others. A well-functioning government takes responsibility for tackling issues that affect society as a whole, such as environmental preservation, economic crises, and international conflicts. Moreover, they have the ability to establish specialized governmental agencies that address these social challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;감시하다 keep an eye on , monitor
반면에 in turn
좋은 well functioning
사회 전반적으로 society as a whole&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we can apply numerous approach to address increasing fat rate. government can start public profit agency to encourage consuming low-fat food. we can decrease our inner fat by regulary training our body. the most important behavior is deter our willing of consuming carbohydrate. because consuming excessive carbohydrate is more detrimental than lazy training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To tackle the issue of increasing obesity rates, there are several approaches we can take. The government can initiate a public nonprofit agency to promote the consumption of low-fat foods. Additionally, individuals can take action by engaging in regular exercise to reduce body fat. However, one of the most crucial behaviors to address is curbing our desire for excessive carbohydrate consumption. This is because consuming too many carbohydrates can have more detrimental effects than not being as active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fat -&amp;gt; obesity
기업을 창조하다 -&amp;gt; initiate
공공기관 -&amp;gt; public nonprofit agency
운동하다 -&amp;gt; regular exercise
body fat
willing -&amp;gt; desire
lazy training -&amp;gt; not being as active&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;some attempt to revert to traditional healthcare method contrast to modern medical technology, there is some contraversary in healthcare system between existing approach and new approach. even though both methods ,historically, are enhanced through experimental results, traditional method is usually researched about correlation of organs which seems not correlated each other so their methods are related to neuro system. modern method is usually focus on directly alleviate the abnormal symtom of that organ and start searching pheriperal area which is known as correlated with that organ with aid of modern analysis techonology. so most problem can be solved with modern technology but when we encounter unprecedented problem, there is presence of probability that traditional method will work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some attempts to revert to traditional healthcare methods, which contrasts with modern medical technology. This has created some controversy within the healthcare system, as both approaches have historically been enhanced through experimental results. Traditional methods often involve researching the correlation of organs that may not seem directly related, focusing on the neuro system. On the other hand, modern methods concentrate on directly alleviating abnormal symptoms of specific organs and utilize modern analysis technology to explore peripheral areas known to be correlated with those organs.
While modern technology can address most problems, when faced with unprecedented issues, there is a possibility that traditional methods could prove effective. This highlights the ongoing debate between the existing and new approaches in healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;controversy within
contrast with
pheriperal -&amp;gt; peripheral
traditional methods could prove effective
결론에 쓸만한 문장 “This highlights” the ongoing debate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With changing socitey over time, people worry about losing our traditional custom. but i believe pursuing transformation of practice is imperative process to be improved. we can abandon our corrupted and toxical custom by compare with another one and accept their well-functioning practice. our custom doesn’t merely developing to the mixing together but reference another culture and refine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As society evolves, there are concerns about losing our traditional customs. However, I firmly believe that embracing transformation and progress is an essential process for improvement. We can let go of corrupted and toxic customs by comparing them with others and adopting well-functioning practices from different cultures. Our customs shouldn’t simply be a mix of various elements but rather a process of referencing and refining practices from different cultures. By doing so, we can preserve the essence of our traditions while incorporating positive changes to adapt to the changing times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;develope -&amp;gt; evolve
worry -&amp;gt; concern
trim -&amp;gt; refine
abandon -&amp;gt; let go of 
toxical -&amp;gt; toxic
accept -&amp;gt; adopt
by doing so
important thing -&amp;gt; essence
변화하는 시간에 적응하다 adapt to the changing times&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the reason why art is important to the society is they reflect our society. when we appreciate another countries culture, we can find out what they are pursuing. especially, when it comes to art, we can put our unexplainable emotion and feelings on that meterial. but as they are hard to explain so hard to remember, when we lose our art, it is easy to forgot few of our own feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art holds significant importance in society because it serves as a reflection of our culture and values. When we admire and appreciate the culture of other countries through art, we gain insight into their aspirations and ideals. Moreover, art offers a unique medium for us to express our unexplainable emotions and feelings, allowing us to connect with the material on a deeper level. However, since these emotions are difficult to articulate, they become challenging to remember. Consequently, when we lose our art, we risk forgetting some of our distinctive characteristics as a society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;find out what they are pursuing -&amp;gt; gain insight into their aspirations and ideals
is only methods -&amp;gt; offers a unique medium
명료하다 articulate
few of our -&amp;gt; some of our
own feature -&amp;gt; distinctive characteristics
we risk forgetting&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;many people think build sky train will alleviate the traffic cog. but sky train pose potentional posibility of environmental pollution including shade sunlight. moreover, if they accerlate the increasing population to the city, the the problem of traffic jam doesn’t getting better and the disparity between wealth and poverty result in lifestyle which fail to reach to the sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people believe that building a sky train will help ease traffic congestion. However, the construction of a sky train could potentially lead to environmental pollution, including blocking sunlight with its structures. Additionally, if the increased accessibility to the city accelerates population growth, the issue of traffic jams may not improve, and the disparity between wealth and poverty could result in a lifestyle that fails to enjoy the benefits of sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;build -&amp;gt; construction
cog -&amp;gt; congestion
blocking sunlight with its structures
fails to enjoy the benefits of sunlight&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">even though are reasonable enough to descern meaningful information, the problem of providing distorted or unnecessary information is that affect our furture learning direction. for example, when we get to know about new fast food, our knowledge fool of food extended on the direction of fast food which incur increasing probability for us to choose fast food. when we come to reach the news of gun murder in america, we easily think there are lots of gun accident eventhough that is not occer often. this also happened in fake news, which bring our attention and make us to investigate about it also resulting our knowledge to extend to that area, same effect as provided unnescessary information.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing technology</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/17/writing-technology.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing technology" /><published>2023-07-17T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-17T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/17/writing%20technology</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/17/writing-technology.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
Modern technology is now very common in most work places
how do you think this has changed the ways we work?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With modernization of technology over the world, our life style has changed over time. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my discussion regarding this transformation of our life style alongside work places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the modernization of technology worldwide, our lifestyle has undergone significant changes over time. In the following paragraph, I will discuss this transformation of our lifestyle in relation to work environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the modernization of technology worldwide, our lifestyle has changed over time. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on the discussion of this transformation of our lifestyle alongside the evolution of work environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;over the world -&amp;gt; worldwide
changed -&amp;gt; undergone changes
my discusstion -&amp;gt; the discussion
alongside 는 and 느낌으로 
and 대신에 in relation to 써도됨&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was the time human used to work as primary industry such as peasantry, fisher, woodsman and more. However, since human’s resources accumulated over time, the effort they have to put for sustaining basic lives decreases. they start to work as secondary industry and third industry which had been enabled as human can commute far from home. According to investigation conducted in Callifornia, United States, in 1950, More than 50% of working population engage in primary industry but in 1990, Less than 20% of working population still serve for primary industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a time when humans used to work in the primary industry, which included agriculture, fishing, forestry, and more. However, as human resources accumulated over time, the effort required to sustain basic livelihoods decreased. This led people to shift towards the secondary and tertiary industries, enabled by the ability to commute farther from home. According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, in 1950, over 50% of the working population was engaged in the primary industry. However, by 1990, less than 20% of the working population remained in the primary industry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;살림 livelihoods
일거리가 이동하다 shift 
의해서 가능하게 되다 enabled by
more than -&amp;gt; over&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In these days, consequently, with the emerging of fourth industry, numerous people don’t even commute but work at home. people begin to know the power of computer is significant alongside to utilize internet. for example, they start advertising, make movie, share information, communicate each other immediately by chatting and calling. and also they can analysis data with AI(artificial intelligence) even though which doesn’t need internet. which also enabling us to work numerous things at the same time and allow us to yield profit as long as our ability can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent times, with the emergence of the fourth industrial revolution, many people no longer need to commute but instead work from home. People have come to recognize the significant power of computers and the utilization of the internet. For example, they engage in activities such as advertising, movie-making, information sharing, and immediate communication through chat and calls. Additionally, they can analyze data with artificial intelligence (AI) even without internet connectivity. This enables individuals to multitask and pursue profit based on their abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus far, we scrutinized affect of the modernization of technology on our work place. As times goes on, our work style transform to require less commute distance and enabling us to work depends on our personal ability rather than where we born.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus far, we have examined the impact of technological modernization on our workplaces. As time passes, our work style is evolving to require less commuting distance and allowing us to work based on our personal abilities rather than being constrained by our birthplace&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;scrutinized -&amp;gt; have examined
time goes on -&amp;gt; time passes
birthplace&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">Q Modern technology is now very common in most work places how do you think this has changed the ways we work? A</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing space 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/16/writing-space.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing space 1" /><published>2023-07-16T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-16T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/16/writing%20space</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/16/writing-space.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
Some people think that space exploration is a waste of resources while others think that it is essential for mankind to continue to explore the universe in which we live
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
With the advancement of techonology over time, we are getting to explore more dangerous region. some argue exploring universe pose hazard so we have to restrain the area to explore. in the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
With the advancement of technology over time, we have been able to explore increasingly dangerous regions. Some argue that exploring the universe poses hazards, and thus we should limit the areas we explore. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
We have to overcome numerous danger whenever we challenge new area. For example, when we try to dive water, we have to overcome danger of shark, water pressure, toxic creature, even swift flow of water. however, now we can travel with submarine and many kinds of robots. We also available to overcome the obstacle of unknown hazard in the universe through our techonology.
&lt;br /&gt;
We encounter numerous dangers whenever we venture into new areas. For instance, when diving into water, we must overcome the risks of encountering sharks, dealing with water pressure, encountering toxic creatures, and navigating swift water currents. However, thanks to advancements in technology, we now have submarines and various types of robots that aid in exploration. Furthermore, our technological capabilities enable us to overcome the obstacles posed by unknown hazards in the universe
&lt;br /&gt;
explore -&amp;gt; venture
water flow -&amp;gt; water currents
because of -&amp;gt; thanks to
many kinds of -&amp;gt; various types of
that helps exploration -&amp;gt; that aid in exploration
techonological level -&amp;gt; technological capabilities
&lt;br /&gt;
the importance of exploring is based on learning which itself is worthwhile as long as we pursuing happiness through this anyway so it is not a waste of resourse. According to AI research conducted at MIT university, the performance of agent increased when they make agent to explore following their own curiosity ,which eventually result in agent to maximize IG(information gain). As we can see through research, explore is correlated with intelligence. In above example, we get to learn about sea more deeper and we got to know new creature and their skills to adapt their environment, when we explore universe, we can obtain substantial knowledge which ultimately advantageous to human life. 
&lt;br /&gt;
The importance of exploration lies in the process of learning, which in itself is valuable, especially when pursued for the sake of happiness. Therefore, it is not a waste of resources. According to AI research conducted at MIT University, agent performance increases when agents are allowed to explore based on their own curiosity, ultimately resulting in maximizing information gain (IG). As observed through research, exploration is strongly correlated with intelligence. In the aforementioned example, deep-sea exploration enables us to acquire a deeper understanding of the ocean, discover new creatures, and learn about their adaptations to their environment. Similarly, exploring the universe provides us with substantial knowledge that ultimately benefits human life.
&lt;br /&gt;
어디에서 나오다 -&amp;gt; lies
그거자체는 -&amp;gt; which in itself
for -&amp;gt; for the sake of
above -&amp;gt; aforementioned
learn -&amp;gt; acquire understanding
&lt;br /&gt;
In conclusion, explore itself is safe when we explore in the range of our coverage of technological capabilities. Moreover, we also can acquire our understanding of nature so can learning. As we consider aforementioned factors, exploring universe is highly recommanded and not waste of resorce&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, exploration itself is safe when conducted within the range of our technological capabilities. Furthermore, it allows us to enhance our understanding of nature and facilitates learning. Considering these factors, exploring the universe is highly recommended and not a waste of resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;resorce -&amp;gt; resources&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">Q Some people think that space exploration is a waste of resources while others think that it is essential for mankind to continue to explore the universe in which we live A With the advancement of techonology over time, we are getting to explore more dangerous region. some argue exploring universe pose hazard so we have to restrain the area to explore. in the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. With the advancement of technology over time, we have been able to explore increasingly dangerous regions. Some argue that exploring the universe poses hazards, and thus we should limit the areas we explore. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. We have to overcome numerous danger whenever we challenge new area. For example, when we try to dive water, we have to overcome danger of shark, water pressure, toxic creature, even swift flow of water. however, now we can travel with submarine and many kinds of robots. We also available to overcome the obstacle of unknown hazard in the universe through our techonology. We encounter numerous dangers whenever we venture into new areas. For instance, when diving into water, we must overcome the risks of encountering sharks, dealing with water pressure, encountering toxic creatures, and navigating swift water currents. However, thanks to advancements in technology, we now have submarines and various types of robots that aid in exploration. Furthermore, our technological capabilities enable us to overcome the obstacles posed by unknown hazards in the universe explore -&amp;gt; venture water flow -&amp;gt; water currents because of -&amp;gt; thanks to many kinds of -&amp;gt; various types of that helps exploration -&amp;gt; that aid in exploration techonological level -&amp;gt; technological capabilities the importance of exploring is based on learning which itself is worthwhile as long as we pursuing happiness through this anyway so it is not a waste of resourse. According to AI research conducted at MIT university, the performance of agent increased when they make agent to explore following their own curiosity ,which eventually result in agent to maximize IG(information gain). As we can see through research, explore is correlated with intelligence. In above example, we get to learn about sea more deeper and we got to know new creature and their skills to adapt their environment, when we explore universe, we can obtain substantial knowledge which ultimately advantageous to human life. The importance of exploration lies in the process of learning, which in itself is valuable, especially when pursued for the sake of happiness. Therefore, it is not a waste of resources. According to AI research conducted at MIT University, agent performance increases when agents are allowed to explore based on their own curiosity, ultimately resulting in maximizing information gain (IG). As observed through research, exploration is strongly correlated with intelligence. In the aforementioned example, deep-sea exploration enables us to acquire a deeper understanding of the ocean, discover new creatures, and learn about their adaptations to their environment. Similarly, exploring the universe provides us with substantial knowledge that ultimately benefits human life. 어디에서 나오다 -&amp;gt; lies 그거자체는 -&amp;gt; which in itself for -&amp;gt; for the sake of above -&amp;gt; aforementioned learn -&amp;gt; acquire understanding In conclusion, explore itself is safe when we explore in the range of our coverage of technological capabilities. Moreover, we also can acquire our understanding of nature so can learning. As we consider aforementioned factors, exploring universe is highly recommanded and not waste of resorce</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing food 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/15/writing-food-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing food 2" /><published>2023-07-15T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-15T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/15/writing%20food%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/15/writing-food-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
with a fast pace of modern life more and more people are turning towards fast food for their main meals.
&lt;br /&gt;
do you think the advantages outweigh the disadvantages?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
With modernization over the world, people are becomming more and more busy. According to this situation, consumption of fast food increasing. some argue that we should restrict consumption of fast food. in the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument through explaining about pros and cons of consumption of fast food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With modernization taking place worldwide, people are becoming increasingly busy. As a result, the consumption of fast food is also increasing. Some argue that we should restrict the consumption of fast food. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument by discussing the pros and cons of consuming fast food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;through explaining -&amp;gt; by discussing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As diversity of job increase over time, propertion of people who serve in first industry such like present decreasing. which undoubtedly result in increasing food miles so make us hard to consume various food. Nowadays we come to choose fast food which doesn’t need lots of time or resource. According to research conducted in California, United States, in 2017, on twenties, the rate of daily consumption of fastfood on average on upper 20% wealthy is 30% less than opposite group which means people who can afford healthy food don’t choose fast food because that is unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the diversity of job opportunities increases over time, the proportion of people serving in traditional industries, such as the present, is decreasing. This undoubtedly results in an increase in food miles, making it harder for us to consume a variety of foods. Nowadays, we tend to choose fast food because it requires less time and resources. According to research conducted in California, United States, in 2017, among individuals in their twenties, the average daily consumption rate of fast food in the upper 20% wealthier group was 30% lower than the opposite group. This suggests that people who can afford healthy food often avoid fast food due to its unhealthy nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;first industry -&amp;gt; primary industry
serve -&amp;gt; working
on twenties -&amp;gt; among individuals in their twenties&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However consuming fast food doesn’t absolutely result in losing our health condition. As increasing number of people who worry about their health, lots of healty food company borned which make suppliment for a cheap price which is useful for modern people who spend hard time to consuming necessary nutrition. even though we normaly consume limited and cheap nutrition through fast food, we can consume another essentional nutrition by simply consuming cheap and small suppliment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, consuming fast food doesn’t necessarily lead to a decline in our health condition. With an increasing number of people concerned about their health, numerous healthy food companies have emerged, offering affordable supplements that are beneficial for modern individuals who struggle to obtain necessary nutrition. Even though fast food often provides limited and inexpensive nutrition, we can easily supplement our diet with essential nutrients by incorporating affordable and compact supplements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;losing health condition -&amp;gt; decline health condition
회사가 생겨났다 born -&amp;gt; emerged
suppliment -&amp;gt; supplement&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclution, even though it is hard to consume healthy food and someone have to consume fast food to fit their economic situation, they also can consume important nutrition which they don’t have chance to consume in normal days through consuming suppliment. given these facts, i believe that advantage of leverage fast food overweight the disadvantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, despite the challenges of consuming healthy food and the necessity for some individuals to rely on fast food due to their economic circumstances, they can still obtain essential nutrients they might not have access to on a regular basis through the use of supplements. Considering these factors, I believe that the advantages of leveraging fast food outweigh the disadvantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;because of -&amp;gt; due to
economic situation -&amp;gt; economic circumstances
given these facts -&amp;gt; considering these factors
평소에 on a regular basis
활용하다 leveraging&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">Q with a fast pace of modern life more and more people are turning towards fast food for their main meals. do you think the advantages outweigh the disadvantages? A With modernization over the world, people are becomming more and more busy. According to this situation, consumption of fast food increasing. some argue that we should restrict consumption of fast food. in the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument through explaining about pros and cons of consumption of fast food.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing house 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/15/writing-house.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing house 1" /><published>2023-07-15T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-15T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/15/writing%20house</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/15/writing-house.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
Many countries are experiencing population growth and need more homes
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With prosperation of mankind over the world, The population have increased over time. As our space to live limited, we start try to decide whether to build house in country side or city side. in the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding discussion of advantage and disadvantage to choose one of each side.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With the prosperity of mankind worldwide, the population has steadily increased over time. As available living space becomes limited, we are faced with the decision of whether to build houses in the countryside or in urban areas. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding the advantages and disadvantages of choosing either side
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
prosperation -&amp;gt; prosperity
over the world -&amp;gt; worldwide
try to decide -&amp;gt; faced with decision
one of each side -&amp;gt; either side
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As we have lots of workplace in the cityside, the price of house and rent fee at the city side is higher than country side. according to the principle of law of supply and demand,
If we build lots of house at the cityside, we can expect the price of house in the city side decrease. But the problem is, that is failed to applied in the real life. According to the investigation conducted in the California, United States, the number of house in the city side was around 3times more than country side at 1990 and prices was around 2times higher in average. However in 2010, the price of house in cityside is 3times higher than country side but the number of house in the city side was even 5times higher than country side.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As there are numerous workplaces in the city, housing prices and rental fees there are higher compared to the countryside. This is due to the law of supply and demand. One might expect that building more houses in the city would decrease housing prices. However, in reality, this principle doesn’t always apply. According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, in 1990, the number of houses in the city was roughly three times greater than in the countryside, and the average prices were about twice as high. However, by 2010, housing prices in the city were three times higher than in the countryside, despite the number of houses in the city being five times higher than in the countryside
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;lots of -&amp;gt; numerous
than -&amp;gt; compared to
we can expect -&amp;gt; one might expect
rent fee -&amp;gt; rental fee
around -&amp;gt; roughly
more -&amp;gt; greater
around -&amp;gt; about
two times -&amp;gt; twice as
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The unexpected Matthew effect as you can see in the above investigation is derived from Regional development, the variable of which we had to account for and ruled out but overlooked. Since population density ,which undoubtedly correlated to development of local society, in the city side increases over time unlike from rural side, the city side increasingly developed over time. This curcimstance correspondingly resulted in another increasing demand.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The unexpected Matthew effect, as you can see in the above investigation, is derived from regional development, a variable that we had to account for and rule out but overlooked. Due to the increase in population density over time, which is undoubtedly correlated with the development of the local society, the city side experiences continuous growth. Consequently, this circumstance leads to an increasing demand
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
came -&amp;gt; stems, derived
over time -&amp;gt; continuous ~
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
but which phenomenon ,which is about only few local society is developing, is dangerous even though that probably yeilds siginificent profit on the society. for example, when war is occering, whole country is subseptive to few misile attack to some city. Additionally we also valnurable to the situation whether some people, who manage the region the most power is concentrated in, change their mind to be extremely selfish.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
However, there is a phenomenon that is specific to only a few developing local societies, yet it is dangerous despite its potential to yield significant profits for society. For example, during times of war, the entire country becomes susceptible to missile attacks targeted at specific cities. Additionally, we are also vulnerable to situations where the people who hold the most power in a region change their mindset to become extremely selfish
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
is dangerous -&amp;gt; poses danger
subjective -&amp;gt; susceptible
valnurable -&amp;gt; vulnerable
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In conclution, building new house in the city side can relieve temporary problem and enabling us to yield substantial profit right away. However, in the long way, it will excerbate permement imparity between rural and urban which ultimately bring us loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, building new houses in the city can temporarily alleviate problems and enable us to immediately generate substantial profits. However, in the long run, it can exacerbate the permanent disparity between rural and urban areas, ultimately resulting in losses&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;right away -&amp;gt; immediately
in the long way -&amp;gt; in the long run (길게보면)
excerbate -&amp;gt; exacerbate
imparity -&amp;gt; disparity
side -&amp;gt; area&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">Q Many countries are experiencing population growth and need more homes A With prosperation of mankind over the world, The population have increased over time. As our space to live limited, we start try to decide whether to build house in country side or city side. in the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding discussion of advantage and disadvantage to choose one of each side. With the prosperity of mankind worldwide, the population has steadily increased over time. As available living space becomes limited, we are faced with the decision of whether to build houses in the countryside or in urban areas. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding the advantages and disadvantages of choosing either side prosperation -&amp;gt; prosperity over the world -&amp;gt; worldwide try to decide -&amp;gt; faced with decision one of each side -&amp;gt; either side As we have lots of workplace in the cityside, the price of house and rent fee at the city side is higher than country side. according to the principle of law of supply and demand, If we build lots of house at the cityside, we can expect the price of house in the city side decrease. But the problem is, that is failed to applied in the real life. According to the investigation conducted in the California, United States, the number of house in the city side was around 3times more than country side at 1990 and prices was around 2times higher in average. However in 2010, the price of house in cityside is 3times higher than country side but the number of house in the city side was even 5times higher than country side. As there are numerous workplaces in the city, housing prices and rental fees there are higher compared to the countryside. This is due to the law of supply and demand. One might expect that building more houses in the city would decrease housing prices. However, in reality, this principle doesn’t always apply. According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, in 1990, the number of houses in the city was roughly three times greater than in the countryside, and the average prices were about twice as high. However, by 2010, housing prices in the city were three times higher than in the countryside, despite the number of houses in the city being five times higher than in the countryside</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing food 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/14/writing-food-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing food 1" /><published>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/14/writing%20food%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english/2023/07/14/writing-food-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
with a growing world population one of the most pressing issues is that of feeding such a large number of people. some people think that gm foods offer a viable solution to this problem to what extent do you agree
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As population over the world increase, Some argue that genetic modified foods will be good alternative of real food to sort out depletion of food problem. In the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As the global population continues to increase, some argue that genetically modified foods could be a viable alternative to address the issue of food depletion. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
sort out -&amp;gt; address
&lt;br /&gt;
The development of gene over the time was based on “proper survive” principle which means they should provide good nutrition for animal to survive and also they should be optimized to prospering. But if they don’t have to worry about breed, there is no point to modify their behavior to prospering by decreasing efficiency of providing nutrition. so there are still many ways to make plant improve in our favor without any side effect. Additionally,According to the investigation conducted in California, United States, on the residents about cancer rate between who continue to consuming genetic modified food regularly and who didn’t, surprisingly the ratio of occurence of cancer in formar group was rather more lower than later group by 0.0003%. even though they didn’t account for another varience to rule out such as wealthyness, gender, workplace, at least we don’t have any proper reason to deduce GM food are harm for our health. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The development of genes over time has been based on the principle of ‘proper survival,’ which means they should provide good nutrition for animals to survive and optimize their chances of prospering. However, if there is no concern about breeding, there is no point in modifying their behavior to prioritize prospering at the expense of decreased nutritional efficiency. Therefore, there are still many ways to improve plants in our favor without any adverse side effects. Additionally, according to an investigation conducted in California, United States, comparing the cancer rates between residents who regularly consume genetically modified food and those who don’t, the occurrence of cancer in the former group was surprisingly lower by 0.0003% compared to the latter group. Although this study did not account for other variables such as wealth, gender, or workplace, it provides no substantial reason to deduce that GM foods are harmful to our health.
&lt;br /&gt;
survival of the fittest
at the cost of
later -&amp;gt; latter
&lt;br /&gt;
However, we have to think about if GM foods are only one solution to takle with deplation of food problem. Some people just grown their own plant or animal to eat so it doesn’t seems make sense that food depletion can be problem. i think the root of problem is inconsistent density of population which brings city side people to feel the price of food as expensive which is result of additional transportation and maintainence fee. so if we just make food more, this can simply suffocate local farmar without solving root problem.
&lt;br /&gt;
However, we must consider whether GM foods are the only solution to tackle the issue of food depletion. Some people choose to grow their own plants or raise animals for consumption, making the concept of food depletion seem less relevant. I believe the root problem lies in the uneven distribution of population density, which leads urban dwellers to perceive food prices as expensive due to additional transportation and maintenance costs. Simply increasing food production could potentially suffocate local farmers without addressing the underlying problem.”
&lt;br /&gt;
if -&amp;gt; whether
inconsistent -&amp;gt; uneven
root problem -&amp;gt; underlying problem
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, we can conclude GM is good way to make food because development process of food is not optimized to good for human so it can be improved more without any side effect. However the problem with the food can be not necessairy came from food depletation so it is possible that we cannot solve that problem by making more food easily.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, we can conclude that genetic modification is a good approach to improving food production as the development process of food is not optimized solely for human benefit. It can be further improved without significant side effects. However, it is important to note that the problem with food may not necessarily arise solely from food depletion. Therefore, simply increasing food production may not be the easy solution to address the underlying problem.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
way -&amp;gt; approach
came from -&amp;gt; arise from
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="english" /><summary type="html">Q with a growing world population one of the most pressing issues is that of feeding such a large number of people. some people think that gm foods offer a viable solution to this problem to what extent do you agree A As population over the world increase, Some argue that genetic modified foods will be good alternative of real food to sort out depletion of food problem. In the following paragraph, i will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. As the global population continues to increase, some argue that genetically modified foods could be a viable alternative to address the issue of food depletion. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. sort out -&amp;gt; address The development of gene over the time was based on “proper survive” principle which means they should provide good nutrition for animal to survive and also they should be optimized to prospering. But if they don’t have to worry about breed, there is no point to modify their behavior to prospering by decreasing efficiency of providing nutrition. so there are still many ways to make plant improve in our favor without any side effect. Additionally,According to the investigation conducted in California, United States, on the residents about cancer rate between who continue to consuming genetic modified food regularly and who didn’t, surprisingly the ratio of occurence of cancer in formar group was rather more lower than later group by 0.0003%. even though they didn’t account for another varience to rule out such as wealthyness, gender, workplace, at least we don’t have any proper reason to deduce GM food are harm for our health. The development of genes over time has been based on the principle of ‘proper survival,’ which means they should provide good nutrition for animals to survive and optimize their chances of prospering. However, if there is no concern about breeding, there is no point in modifying their behavior to prioritize prospering at the expense of decreased nutritional efficiency. Therefore, there are still many ways to improve plants in our favor without any adverse side effects. Additionally, according to an investigation conducted in California, United States, comparing the cancer rates between residents who regularly consume genetically modified food and those who don’t, the occurrence of cancer in the former group was surprisingly lower by 0.0003% compared to the latter group. Although this study did not account for other variables such as wealth, gender, or workplace, it provides no substantial reason to deduce that GM foods are harmful to our health. survival of the fittest at the cost of later -&amp;gt; latter However, we have to think about if GM foods are only one solution to takle with deplation of food problem. Some people just grown their own plant or animal to eat so it doesn’t seems make sense that food depletion can be problem. i think the root of problem is inconsistent density of population which brings city side people to feel the price of food as expensive which is result of additional transportation and maintainence fee. so if we just make food more, this can simply suffocate local farmar without solving root problem. However, we must consider whether GM foods are the only solution to tackle the issue of food depletion. Some people choose to grow their own plants or raise animals for consumption, making the concept of food depletion seem less relevant. I believe the root problem lies in the uneven distribution of population density, which leads urban dwellers to perceive food prices as expensive due to additional transportation and maintenance costs. Simply increasing food production could potentially suffocate local farmers without addressing the underlying problem.” if -&amp;gt; whether inconsistent -&amp;gt; uneven root problem -&amp;gt; underlying problem In summary, we can conclude GM is good way to make food because development process of food is not optimized to good for human so it can be improved more without any side effect. However the problem with the food can be not necessairy came from food depletation so it is possible that we cannot solve that problem by making more food easily. In summary, we can conclude that genetic modification is a good approach to improving food production as the development process of food is not optimized solely for human benefit. It can be further improved without significant side effects. However, it is important to note that the problem with food may not necessarily arise solely from food depletion. Therefore, simply increasing food production may not be the easy solution to address the underlying problem. way -&amp;gt; approach came from -&amp;gt; arise from</summary></entry></feed>