<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-06-02T15:06:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Voca 5</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/06/02/voca-5.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Voca 5" /><published>2023-06-02T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-06-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/06/02/voca%205</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/06/02/voca-5.html"></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca 4</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/01/voca-4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca 4" /><published>2023-06-01T08:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-06-01T08:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/01/voca%204</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/01/voca-4.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
therapeutic
&lt;br /&gt;
culture vulture
&lt;br /&gt;
dabbler
&lt;br /&gt;
shopaholic
&lt;br /&gt;
hooked on
&lt;br /&gt;
get up to
&lt;br /&gt;
full diary
&lt;br /&gt;
keen participant
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
cloaked
&lt;br /&gt;
scruffy
&lt;br /&gt;
dress codes
&lt;br /&gt;
attire
&lt;br /&gt;
cleavage
&lt;br /&gt;
midriff
&lt;br /&gt;
frumpy
&lt;br /&gt;
dress- down days
&lt;br /&gt;
overalls
&lt;br /&gt;
skimpy
&lt;br /&gt;
baggy
&lt;br /&gt;
clingy
&lt;br /&gt;
chic
&lt;br /&gt;
done up to the nines
&lt;br /&gt;
High Street
&lt;br /&gt;
made-to-measure
&lt;br /&gt;
off the peg/rack
&lt;br /&gt;
all the rage
&lt;br /&gt;
the height of fashion
&lt;br /&gt;
up-to-the-minute
&lt;br /&gt;
catches on
&lt;br /&gt;
off the cuff
&lt;br /&gt;
to be hand in glove with someone
&lt;br /&gt;
on a shoestring
&lt;br /&gt;
no frills
&lt;br /&gt;
to put someone in a straitjacket
&lt;br /&gt;
to draw a veil over
&lt;br /&gt;
to have something up your sleeve 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
squat
&lt;br /&gt;
hovel
&lt;br /&gt;
penthouse
&lt;br /&gt;
Council or social housing
&lt;br /&gt;
tower blocks
&lt;br /&gt;
granny flat
&lt;br /&gt;
household word/ name
&lt;br /&gt;
on the house
&lt;br /&gt;
home truths
&lt;br /&gt;
nothing to write home about
&lt;br /&gt;
hit home
&lt;br /&gt;
make yourself at home
&lt;br /&gt;
have the time of your life
&lt;br /&gt;
get a new lease of life
&lt;br /&gt;
a dog’s life
&lt;br /&gt;
be a matter of life and death
&lt;br /&gt;
take your life in your hands
&lt;br /&gt;
breathe new life into
&lt;br /&gt;
house of cards
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
housewarming
&lt;br /&gt;
stag party
&lt;br /&gt;
hen night
&lt;br /&gt;
reception
&lt;br /&gt;
black-tie
&lt;br /&gt;
leaving do
&lt;br /&gt;
hobnob with
&lt;br /&gt;
knocks around with
&lt;br /&gt;
outstaying my welcome
&lt;br /&gt;
cliquey
&lt;br /&gt;
his crowd
&lt;br /&gt;
stood him up
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
hackneyed
&lt;br /&gt;
far-fetched
&lt;br /&gt;
risqué
&lt;br /&gt;
gripping
&lt;br /&gt;
harrowing
&lt;br /&gt;
moving
&lt;br /&gt;
understated
&lt;br /&gt;
tedious
&lt;br /&gt;
applause(어플라우즈)
&lt;br /&gt;
glowing reviews
&lt;br /&gt;
encores
&lt;br /&gt;
standing ovation
&lt;br /&gt;
up-and-coming
&lt;br /&gt;
typecast
&lt;br /&gt;
panned/slated
&lt;br /&gt;
booed
&lt;br /&gt;
total flop
&lt;br /&gt;
miscast
&lt;br /&gt;
covers 
&lt;br /&gt;
portrayal
&lt;br /&gt;
tender&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">therapeutic culture vulture dabbler shopaholic hooked on get up to full diary keen participant cloaked scruffy dress codes attire cleavage midriff frumpy dress- down days overalls skimpy baggy clingy chic done up to the nines High Street made-to-measure off the peg/rack all the rage the height of fashion up-to-the-minute catches on off the cuff to be hand in glove with someone on a shoestring no frills to put someone in a straitjacket to draw a veil over to have something up your sleeve squat hovel penthouse Council or social housing tower blocks granny flat household word/ name on the house home truths nothing to write home about hit home make yourself at home have the time of your life get a new lease of life a dog’s life be a matter of life and death take your life in your hands breathe new life into house of cards housewarming stag party hen night reception black-tie leaving do hobnob with knocks around with outstaying my welcome cliquey his crowd stood him up hackneyed far-fetched risqué gripping harrowing moving understated tedious applause(어플라우즈) glowing reviews encores standing ovation up-and-coming typecast panned/slated booed total flop miscast covers portrayal tender</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/01/voca-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca 3" /><published>2023-06-01T04:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-06-01T04:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/01/voca%203</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/01/voca-3.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
infatuated with
&lt;br /&gt;
besotted with
&lt;br /&gt;
hit it off
&lt;br /&gt;
a man after my own heart
&lt;br /&gt;
get on like a house on fire
&lt;br /&gt;
bosom friends/buddies/pals (버슴)
&lt;br /&gt;
family ties
&lt;br /&gt;
holds her in high regard
&lt;br /&gt;
as thick as thieves
&lt;br /&gt;
fond
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
casual acquaintances
&lt;br /&gt;
two-faced towards
&lt;br /&gt;
bitter/arch rivals
&lt;br /&gt;
sworn enemies
&lt;br /&gt;
scrupulously honest (스크류풀러슬리)
&lt;br /&gt;
unswerving
&lt;br /&gt;
staunchest ally
&lt;br /&gt;
rift can develop
&lt;br /&gt;
don’t see eye to eye
&lt;br /&gt;
been on bad terms
&lt;br /&gt;
turned sour
&lt;br /&gt;
broken home
&lt;br /&gt;
family feud
&lt;br /&gt;
quarrel
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
yearns to/ yearn for
&lt;br /&gt;
coveted
&lt;br /&gt;
defuse
&lt;br /&gt;
placate
&lt;br /&gt;
conciliate
&lt;br /&gt;
appeasing (주요한건 처리하지않음)
&lt;br /&gt;
exultant
&lt;br /&gt;
ecstatic
&lt;br /&gt;
rejoiced
&lt;br /&gt;
jubilant (주벌런트)
&lt;br /&gt;
bliss
&lt;br /&gt;
utter
&lt;br /&gt;
sheer
&lt;br /&gt;
thrilled to bits
&lt;br /&gt;
floating on air
&lt;br /&gt;
over the moon
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Antipathy
&lt;br /&gt;
Aversion
&lt;br /&gt;
loathing
&lt;br /&gt;
alarm
&lt;br /&gt;
offhand
&lt;br /&gt;
officious
&lt;br /&gt;
ostentatious
&lt;br /&gt;
pompous
&lt;br /&gt;
puerile (퓨어리얼)
&lt;br /&gt;
fickle
&lt;br /&gt;
nit-picking
&lt;br /&gt;
obnoxious
&lt;br /&gt;
forlorn
&lt;br /&gt;
distraught
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
conception
&lt;br /&gt;
embryo (엠브리오)
&lt;br /&gt;
implants
&lt;br /&gt;
foetus (피더스)
&lt;br /&gt;
placenta
&lt;br /&gt;
goes into labour
&lt;br /&gt;
midwife
&lt;br /&gt;
ripe old age
&lt;br /&gt;
late
&lt;br /&gt;
pensioner
&lt;br /&gt;
sheltered accommodation
&lt;br /&gt;
doddery
&lt;br /&gt;
gaga
&lt;br /&gt;
have all her wits about her
&lt;br /&gt;
dementia
&lt;br /&gt;
coffin
&lt;br /&gt;
cremation
&lt;br /&gt;
condolences
&lt;br /&gt;
to pass away, to pass on, to pass over
&lt;br /&gt;
to be on your last legs
&lt;br /&gt;
fatalities/ perished/ slaughtered/ the deceased
&lt;br /&gt;
to bequeath
&lt;br /&gt;
intestate&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">infatuated with besotted with hit it off a man after my own heart get on like a house on fire bosom friends/buddies/pals (버슴) family ties holds her in high regard as thick as thieves fond casual acquaintances two-faced towards bitter/arch rivals sworn enemies scrupulously honest (스크류풀러슬리) unswerving staunchest ally rift can develop don’t see eye to eye been on bad terms turned sour broken home family feud quarrel yearns to/ yearn for coveted defuse placate conciliate appeasing (주요한건 처리하지않음) exultant ecstatic rejoiced jubilant (주벌런트) bliss utter sheer thrilled to bits floating on air over the moon Antipathy Aversion loathing alarm offhand officious ostentatious pompous puerile (퓨어리얼) fickle nit-picking obnoxious forlorn distraught conception embryo (엠브리오) implants foetus (피더스) placenta goes into labour midwife ripe old age late pensioner sheltered accommodation doddery gaga have all her wits about her dementia coffin cremation condolences to pass away, to pass on, to pass over to be on your last legs fatalities/ perished/ slaughtered/ the deceased to bequeath intestate</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/30/voca-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca 2" /><published>2023-05-30T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-30T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/30/voca%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/30/voca-2.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
morale
&lt;br /&gt;
seeking a career in
&lt;br /&gt;
paternity leave
&lt;br /&gt;
perks/ benefits
&lt;br /&gt;
holiday entitlement
&lt;br /&gt;
voluntary/ compulsory redundancies
&lt;br /&gt;
skeleton staff
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
telesales
&lt;br /&gt;
cold calling
&lt;br /&gt;
hard sell
&lt;br /&gt;
purchasing power
&lt;br /&gt;
shop around
&lt;br /&gt;
trade something up
&lt;br /&gt;
brand loyalty
&lt;br /&gt;
niche market
&lt;br /&gt;
come/go under the hammer
&lt;br /&gt;
increasing bids 
&lt;br /&gt;
red tape
&lt;br /&gt;
hammer out a deal
&lt;br /&gt;
capital assets - the property company have
&lt;br /&gt;
holiday property letting agency
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
obliging
&lt;br /&gt;
tactless
&lt;br /&gt;
diligent
&lt;br /&gt;
shrewd - good judgemet
&lt;br /&gt;
extravagant
&lt;br /&gt;
altruistic
&lt;br /&gt;
frugal
&lt;br /&gt;
dogmatic
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
obese
&lt;br /&gt;
stout
&lt;br /&gt;
stocky
&lt;br /&gt;
unkempt - not tidy
&lt;br /&gt;
immaculate - smart perfect
&lt;br /&gt;
swarthy - dark appearance
&lt;br /&gt;
haggard - looks ill and tired
&lt;br /&gt;
pouting - position their lips in attractive way
&lt;br /&gt;
grimace - strong dislike expression
&lt;br /&gt;
scowled -  bad-tempered, angry look
&lt;br /&gt;
leering - looking in an unpleasant, sexually interested way
&lt;br /&gt;
clenched her fist
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
impetuous - doing without thinking first
&lt;br /&gt;
effusive
&lt;br /&gt;
self-conscious
&lt;br /&gt;
taciturn - save words
&lt;br /&gt;
diffident
&lt;br /&gt;
haughty - think themselves better than others
&lt;br /&gt;
conceited - think themselves wonderful
&lt;br /&gt;
gullible
&lt;br /&gt;
obstinate
&lt;br /&gt;
pig-headed&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">morale seeking a career in paternity leave perks/ benefits holiday entitlement voluntary/ compulsory redundancies skeleton staff telesales cold calling hard sell purchasing power shop around trade something up brand loyalty niche market come/go under the hammer increasing bids red tape hammer out a deal capital assets - the property company have holiday property letting agency obliging tactless diligent shrewd - good judgemet extravagant altruistic frugal dogmatic obese stout stocky unkempt - not tidy immaculate - smart perfect swarthy - dark appearance haggard - looks ill and tired pouting - position their lips in attractive way grimace - strong dislike expression scowled - bad-tempered, angry look leering - looking in an unpleasant, sexually interested way clenched her fist impetuous - doing without thinking first effusive self-conscious taciturn - save words diffident haughty - think themselves better than others conceited - think themselves wonderful gullible obstinate pig-headed</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing environment 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/30/writing-envirnmont-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing environment 1" /><published>2023-05-30T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-30T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/30/writing%20envirnmont%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/30/writing-envirnmont-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
human activity has had a negative impact on plants and animals around the world. some people think that this cannot be changed, while others believe actions can be taken to bring about a change
&lt;br /&gt;
discuss both and give your opinion
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q human activity has had a negative impact on plants and animals around the world. some people think that this cannot be changed, while others believe actions can be taken to bring about a change discuss both and give your opinion A</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/29/voca-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca 1" /><published>2023-05-29T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-29T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/29/voca%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/29/voca-1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
dissertation
&lt;br /&gt;
first draft
&lt;br /&gt;
carry out research
&lt;br /&gt;
bursaries
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Curriculum reform
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Reporting to
&lt;br /&gt;
subsidised
&lt;br /&gt;
cover letter
&lt;br /&gt;
in support of
&lt;br /&gt;
hands-on
&lt;br /&gt;
Yours faithfully
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
panel
&lt;br /&gt;
line manager
&lt;br /&gt;
speak up
&lt;br /&gt;
talk us through
&lt;br /&gt;
fill the post
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
opposite number
&lt;br /&gt;
rapport
&lt;br /&gt;
take the initiative
&lt;br /&gt;
pecking order
&lt;br /&gt;
talk shop
&lt;br /&gt;
day shift
&lt;br /&gt;
knocking off
&lt;br /&gt;
mind-numbing
&lt;br /&gt;
stuck in a rut
&lt;br /&gt;
went in with
&lt;br /&gt;
differentiated point -&amp;gt; distinguishing factor
serieze -&amp;gt; series
simplifized -&amp;gt; simplified&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">dissertation first draft carry out research bursaries Curriculum reform Reporting to subsidised cover letter in support of hands-on Yours faithfully panel line manager speak up talk us through fill the post opposite number rapport take the initiative pecking order talk shop day shift knocking off mind-numbing stuck in a rut went in with differentiated point -&amp;gt; distinguishing factor serieze -&amp;gt; series simplifized -&amp;gt; simplified</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">About RL</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/theory/2023/05/29/About-RL.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About RL" /><published>2023-05-29T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-29T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/theory/2023/05/29/About%20RL</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/theory/2023/05/29/About-RL.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
What i suppose to write about today is reinforcement learning which is one of the kinds of active learning. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The term “active” in “active learning” simply refers to the ability to choose the way we learn. and there have been numerous method which is included in active learning especially many branch of generative models such as RL and GAN. And due to their learning style, we can embody curiosity through these algorithms. You can see the implementation of many different uncertainty estimation methods through Bayesian neural networks.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There have been various valuable attempts to construct plausible AI models that not only mimic human intelligence but also pursue the ultimate goal of true intelligence. While neural networks appear to effectively learn various patterns, we cannot guarantee that what they have learned represents optimized knowledge.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As I mentioned in my previous post, the optimization of their learned knowledge depends on the PAC-Bayes bound. 
Additionally, although I haven’t mentioned it yet, we can also simply utilize optimization methods to ensure if the knowledge they have learned is optimized or not.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The distinguishing factor of reinforcement learning (RL) from other active learning methods is its ability to effectively lower the PAC-Bayes bound by reducing the hypothesis space through the Markov assumption.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The model which has Markov assumption refers to they have decision-making process being dependent only on the present state and not the previous states. Many machine learning algorithms utilize the Markov assumption by incorporating memory structures, particularly RNN, LSTM, HMM, CRF ..in the analysis of time series data.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
these strong assumption allows these technique to inference fastly with simplified structure, which eventually enabling them to learn even one pattern fastly without any help of contradictory patterns which can prevent them from having unnesscery knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="theory" /><summary type="html">What i suppose to write about today is reinforcement learning which is one of the kinds of active learning. The term “active” in “active learning” simply refers to the ability to choose the way we learn. and there have been numerous method which is included in active learning especially many branch of generative models such as RL and GAN. And due to their learning style, we can embody curiosity through these algorithms. You can see the implementation of many different uncertainty estimation methods through Bayesian neural networks. There have been various valuable attempts to construct plausible AI models that not only mimic human intelligence but also pursue the ultimate goal of true intelligence. While neural networks appear to effectively learn various patterns, we cannot guarantee that what they have learned represents optimized knowledge. As I mentioned in my previous post, the optimization of their learned knowledge depends on the PAC-Bayes bound. Additionally, although I haven’t mentioned it yet, we can also simply utilize optimization methods to ensure if the knowledge they have learned is optimized or not. The distinguishing factor of reinforcement learning (RL) from other active learning methods is its ability to effectively lower the PAC-Bayes bound by reducing the hypothesis space through the Markov assumption. The model which has Markov assumption refers to they have decision-making process being dependent only on the present state and not the previous states. Many machine learning algorithms utilize the Markov assumption by incorporating memory structures, particularly RNN, LSTM, HMM, CRF ..in the analysis of time series data. these strong assumption allows these technique to inference fastly with simplified structure, which eventually enabling them to learn even one pattern fastly without any help of contradictory patterns which can prevent them from having unnesscery knowledge.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing work 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/28/writing-work-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing work 2" /><published>2023-05-28T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-28T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/28/writing%20work%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/28/writing-work-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
more and more people are moving away from an agriculture background to relocate to cities in order to look for work
&lt;br /&gt;
what will be the consequences of this? what solutions can you offer?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
These days, as society is getting encountering the globalization, we also becomming face to disparity of density of population by immigration to city center for most people. i will elaborate further on my perspective in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
These days, as society is encountering globalization, we are also facing a disparity in population density due to immigration to city centers for most people. I will elaborate further on my perspective in the following paragraph
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;by -&amp;gt; due to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The most substantial reason believing is people usually anticipate they can get the benefit as modernized culture from the city resulting in their life more comfortable and clear.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The most substantial reason is that people usually anticipate they can benefit from the modernized culture of the city, making their lives more comfortable and fulfilling.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
for instance, when they try to fix their gadget such as laptop, it must be hard to find skillful company to sort out the problem. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
For instance, when they try to fix their gadgets, such as laptops, it can be difficult to find a skilled company to resolve the problem.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe the plausable solution for this matter is advocating government to hinder matthew effect and releive the disparity between poverty and wealthy. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;revised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I believe the plausible solution for this matter is to advocate for government intervention to mitigate the Matthew effect and alleviate the disparity between poverty and wealth&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;advocate -&amp;gt; advocate for
hinder -&amp;gt; intervention to mitigate
relieve -&amp;gt; alleviate
relieve 는 얕은 경감
alleviate는 오래가는 경감&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Q more and more people are moving away from an agriculture background to relocate to cities in order to look for work what will be the consequences of this? what solutions can you offer? A These days, as society is getting encountering the globalization, we also becomming face to disparity of density of population by immigration to city center for most people. i will elaborate further on my perspective in the following paragraph. revised</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">useful expression 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/28/useful-expression.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="useful expression 1" /><published>2023-05-28T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-28T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/28/useful%20expression</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/05/28/useful-expression.html">&lt;p&gt;save it
&lt;br /&gt;
그말 안해도돼
&lt;br /&gt;
be that as it may
&lt;br /&gt;
in a tight spot
&lt;br /&gt;
give ~ a hand
&lt;br /&gt;
take advantage of
&lt;br /&gt;
glare at
&lt;br /&gt;
self-control
&lt;br /&gt;
cut ties with
&lt;br /&gt;
stuck up
&lt;br /&gt;
stand
&lt;br /&gt;
you are out of her league
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;spend about
&lt;br /&gt; 
look me good
&lt;br /&gt;
mistaken a for b
&lt;br /&gt;
why aren’t you do that
&lt;br /&gt;
absent for
&lt;br /&gt;
absent from
&lt;br /&gt;
whoarder
&lt;br /&gt;
right, qualification
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m fooled 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;during that time
&lt;br /&gt;
call by just looking
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;once upon a time
&lt;br /&gt;
in the old days
&lt;br /&gt;
the number one thing
&lt;br /&gt;
be supported
&lt;br /&gt;
you must be worn out
&lt;br /&gt;
you are probably tired
&lt;br /&gt;
free in a way of thinking
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;government agency
&lt;br /&gt;
absent of alternatives
&lt;br /&gt;
once at a time
&lt;br /&gt;
at the time
&lt;br /&gt;
competing for the first place
&lt;br /&gt;
unmatched once and only
&lt;br /&gt;
its for your own sake
&lt;br /&gt;
brain washing
&lt;br /&gt;
waste water
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;launch the airplain
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;take off the airplain
&lt;br /&gt;
as if
&lt;br /&gt;
turn ~ in
&lt;br /&gt;
turn oneself in
&lt;br /&gt;
do down redicule
&lt;br /&gt;
speak badly of
&lt;br /&gt;
punting
&lt;br /&gt;
temporary metropolis
&lt;br /&gt;
fireworks
&lt;br /&gt;
timing
&lt;br /&gt;
it is not long before
&lt;br /&gt;
it have to go without saying
&lt;br /&gt;
to state the obvious
&lt;br /&gt;
rule consistency
&lt;br /&gt;
at cheap price
&lt;br /&gt;
dispense
&lt;br /&gt;
tuberance
&lt;br /&gt;
fluctuate
&lt;br /&gt;
desease spread
&lt;br /&gt;
discernment
&lt;br /&gt;
have a good stomatch
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;on and off
&lt;br /&gt;
pyramid scheme
&lt;br /&gt;
esponage
&lt;br /&gt;
set fire
&lt;br /&gt;
vandalism
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tyrant
&lt;br /&gt;
muscles in tense
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;public servants
&lt;br /&gt;
send over
&lt;br /&gt;
accomplice
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in many ways
&lt;br /&gt;
in some ways
&lt;br /&gt;
as the saying goes
&lt;br /&gt;
rules are made to benefit the rich
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at this rate
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">save it 그말 안해도돼 be that as it may in a tight spot give ~ a hand take advantage of glare at self-control cut ties with stuck up stand you are out of her league</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">About AI</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/theory/2023/05/28/About-AI.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About AI" /><published>2023-05-28T16:10:33+01:00</published><updated>2023-05-28T16:10:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/theory/2023/05/28/About%20AI</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/theory/2023/05/28/About-AI.html">&lt;p&gt;With advancement of ai, we can see plenty of conspicuous model these days which is usually comes from GAN and RL both of which are active learning model.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There has been numerous elaboration to find out like “what is ai”, “how can we build most plausable ai” and “what is intelligence” and lots of paper successfully gave us deep inspiration about fundamental implementation of ai. Even though there has been enourmous pregress in AI, we still can’t explain why we have curiousity and still failed to make how to make model to learn maximizing PAC-bayes bound.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I wanna write about the most fundamental and important concepts we encounter when we first learn about AI which are namely bias and variance.
actually these two concept imply opposite things. Bias means assumption and variance means non-assumption which is like even though we learn something which works simillar as preliminary learned, we should not assume that will works simillary.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The matter at hand is, we have to strike a balance between two concept. For example, when you take the ramen and their color was red, you can think every red food is spicy if you are really biasd. However you have to be more specific in the real life and take that as depending on the context. In the other hand, you should have bias to some extent. when you learned something from specific situation, you should be able to adapt that principle for another situation as well.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The representative theory which discuss about this is called PAC and we usually employ PAC-bayes bounds in academic paper. As a matter of course, there has been attempts which aim to make model to autonomously strike a balance by themselves which is called autoML.
There are many different kinds of techniques which is included in autoML framework called HPO(hyper parameter optimization), NAS(neural architecture search), meta learning and more.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There are many kinds of PAC-Bayes bounds, and a common characteristic among them is that the bound decreases as 1. estimated risk discreases, 2. the Kullback-Leibler divergence (KLD) between the posterior and prior distributions decreases or 3. the number of data for learning increases.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
HPO and NAS is method of finding appropriate hypothetical space which is corresponding to 2 and meta learning is method of increasing number of data for learning which is corresponding to 3.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="theory" /><summary type="html">With advancement of ai, we can see plenty of conspicuous model these days which is usually comes from GAN and RL both of which are active learning model. There has been numerous elaboration to find out like “what is ai”, “how can we build most plausable ai” and “what is intelligence” and lots of paper successfully gave us deep inspiration about fundamental implementation of ai. Even though there has been enourmous pregress in AI, we still can’t explain why we have curiousity and still failed to make how to make model to learn maximizing PAC-bayes bound. I wanna write about the most fundamental and important concepts we encounter when we first learn about AI which are namely bias and variance. actually these two concept imply opposite things. Bias means assumption and variance means non-assumption which is like even though we learn something which works simillar as preliminary learned, we should not assume that will works simillary. The matter at hand is, we have to strike a balance between two concept. For example, when you take the ramen and their color was red, you can think every red food is spicy if you are really biasd. However you have to be more specific in the real life and take that as depending on the context. In the other hand, you should have bias to some extent. when you learned something from specific situation, you should be able to adapt that principle for another situation as well. The representative theory which discuss about this is called PAC and we usually employ PAC-bayes bounds in academic paper. As a matter of course, there has been attempts which aim to make model to autonomously strike a balance by themselves which is called autoML. There are many different kinds of techniques which is included in autoML framework called HPO(hyper parameter optimization), NAS(neural architecture search), meta learning and more. There are many kinds of PAC-Bayes bounds, and a common characteristic among them is that the bound decreases as 1. estimated risk discreases, 2. the Kullback-Leibler divergence (KLD) between the posterior and prior distributions decreases or 3. the number of data for learning increases. HPO and NAS is method of finding appropriate hypothetical space which is corresponding to 2 and meta learning is method of increasing number of data for learning which is corresponding to 3.</summary></entry></feed>