<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-07-14T10:29:51+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Emmett</title><subtitle>Themed by ejjoo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">writing tourism 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing-tourism-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing tourism 1" /><published>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-14T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing%20tourism%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/14/writing-tourism-1.html"></content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing sports 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/13/writing-sports-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing sports 1" /><published>2023-07-13T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-13T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/13/writing%20sports%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/13/writing-sports-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
&lt;br /&gt;
some people think dangerous sports should be banned while others think people should be free to choose.
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
with modernization of the world, the techonology used to support sports improved, so enabling us to challenge more and more dangerous sports. Some argue we should forbid dangerous sports so as to prevent occerance of decreased. I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With the modernization of the world, the technology used to support sports has improved, enabling us to engage in increasingly challenging and potentially dangerous activities. Some argue that we should prohibit dangerous sports to prevent occurrences of harm. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument.
&lt;br /&gt;
more and more -&amp;gt; increasingly
forbid -&amp;gt; prohibit
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
sports have plenty of beneficial aspect. we can improve our socialization skill by communicate each other in multi player sports, we can relieve stress and improve our health by enjoying physical activity, we even improve our motor skill by e-sports which doesn’t require stemina. But i belive the most rewarding aspect of sports is experience. as our equipment are enhanced over the time, we can try many kinds of activitys didn’t abled to before. nowadays we eventually learn various skills through mordanized sports which situation allow us to improve ability dealing with many different problems by different skills.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sports have plenty of beneficial aspects. We can improve our socialization skills by communicating with each other in multiplayer sports. We can relieve stress and enhance our health by engaging in physical activities. Additionally, even in e-sports, which do not require stamina, we can improve our motor skills. However, I believe the most rewarding aspect of sports is the experience itself. As our equipment continues to advance over time, we can explore and participate in various activities that were previously inaccessible. Nowadays, modernized sports allow us to learn a wide range of skills, enabling us to enhance our ability to tackle different problems using different approaches.
&lt;br /&gt;
try -&amp;gt; explore participate
deal -&amp;gt; tackle
different approaches
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
According to one investigation conducted at california states of US on twenty generation, the decreased by sports are decreasing as their proficiency increasing. For example, the people dead rate while scuba diving is totally 0.01% but 80% of that portion was occupied by people who’s experience of diving is less than 50times even though average experience time of diving was 200times. the lesson we can learn with this experience is dangerous sports itself doesn’t affect the possibility of critical injury but insufficient understanding of sports itself.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, spanning twenty generations, the occurrence of accidents in sports is decreasing as proficiency levels increase. For instance, the fatality rate while scuba diving is only 0.01%. However, 80% of these incidents involve individuals with less than 50 diving experiences, despite the average diving experience being 200 times. The lesson we can learn from this is that the inherent danger in sports does not necessarily determine the likelihood of critical injuries; rather, it is often attributed to a lack of understanding and knowledge about the sport itself
&lt;br /&gt;
California, United States,
twenties
proficiency level
fatality
inherent
attributed to
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, what i would like to state is the riskness of sports are not based on defficulty but understanding of that sports. moreover, since benefit of experiencing new sports are invaluable we can’t restrict the range of available sports. In conclution, I think we have to be care of education of security than just ban the sports. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, what I would like to emphasize is that the level of risk in sports is not solely determined by their difficulty but rather by our understanding of those sports. Furthermore, considering the invaluable benefits of experiencing new sports, we should not restrict the range of available activities. In conclusion, I believe it is essential to prioritize education on safety measures rather than simply banning certain sports.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
based on -&amp;gt; solely determined by
education on safety measure
just -&amp;gt; simply
then
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q some people think dangerous sports should be banned while others think people should be free to choose. A with modernization of the world, the techonology used to support sports improved, so enabling us to challenge more and more dangerous sports. Some argue we should forbid dangerous sports so as to prevent occerance of decreased. I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument in the following paragraph. With the modernization of the world, the technology used to support sports has improved, enabling us to engage in increasingly challenging and potentially dangerous activities. Some argue that we should prohibit dangerous sports to prevent occurrences of harm. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument. more and more -&amp;gt; increasingly forbid -&amp;gt; prohibit sports have plenty of beneficial aspect. we can improve our socialization skill by communicate each other in multi player sports, we can relieve stress and improve our health by enjoying physical activity, we even improve our motor skill by e-sports which doesn’t require stemina. But i belive the most rewarding aspect of sports is experience. as our equipment are enhanced over the time, we can try many kinds of activitys didn’t abled to before. nowadays we eventually learn various skills through mordanized sports which situation allow us to improve ability dealing with many different problems by different skills. Sports have plenty of beneficial aspects. We can improve our socialization skills by communicating with each other in multiplayer sports. We can relieve stress and enhance our health by engaging in physical activities. Additionally, even in e-sports, which do not require stamina, we can improve our motor skills. However, I believe the most rewarding aspect of sports is the experience itself. As our equipment continues to advance over time, we can explore and participate in various activities that were previously inaccessible. Nowadays, modernized sports allow us to learn a wide range of skills, enabling us to enhance our ability to tackle different problems using different approaches. try -&amp;gt; explore participate deal -&amp;gt; tackle different approaches According to one investigation conducted at california states of US on twenty generation, the decreased by sports are decreasing as their proficiency increasing. For example, the people dead rate while scuba diving is totally 0.01% but 80% of that portion was occupied by people who’s experience of diving is less than 50times even though average experience time of diving was 200times. the lesson we can learn with this experience is dangerous sports itself doesn’t affect the possibility of critical injury but insufficient understanding of sports itself. According to an investigation conducted in California, United States, spanning twenty generations, the occurrence of accidents in sports is decreasing as proficiency levels increase. For instance, the fatality rate while scuba diving is only 0.01%. However, 80% of these incidents involve individuals with less than 50 diving experiences, despite the average diving experience being 200 times. The lesson we can learn from this is that the inherent danger in sports does not necessarily determine the likelihood of critical injuries; rather, it is often attributed to a lack of understanding and knowledge about the sport itself California, United States, twenties proficiency level fatality inherent attributed to In summary, what i would like to state is the riskness of sports are not based on defficulty but understanding of that sports. moreover, since benefit of experiencing new sports are invaluable we can’t restrict the range of available sports. In conclution, I think we have to be care of education of security than just ban the sports. In summary, what I would like to emphasize is that the level of risk in sports is not solely determined by their difficulty but rather by our understanding of those sports. Furthermore, considering the invaluable benefits of experiencing new sports, we should not restrict the range of available activities. In conclusion, I believe it is essential to prioritize education on safety measures rather than simply banning certain sports. based on -&amp;gt; solely determined by education on safety measure just -&amp;gt; simply then</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">writing reading 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/12/writing-reading-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="writing reading 1" /><published>2023-07-12T00:10:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-12T00:10:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/12/writing%20reading%201</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/writing/2023/07/12/writing-reading-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Q
Some people think books are losing importance as a source of information and entertainment. to what extent do you agree?
&lt;br /&gt;
A
&lt;br /&gt;
with globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to get the information on the internet. some argue books are not important anymore as online website have cumulated immornouse information. i will elaborate on my perspective of this argument further in the following paragraph.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With the globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to access information on the internet. Some argue that books are no longer important since online websites have accumulated enormous amounts of information. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
when we read the book with paper, we can protect our eyesight from various dexitorious lights such as microwave and bluelight. morever, we can utilize our aother sensory motor system to appreciate reading mood entirely which eventually award us on some extent of satisfaction and enjoyness.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
When we read a book on paper, we can protect our eyesight from various detrimental lights, such as microwaves and blue light. Moreover, we can engage our other sensory and motor systems to fully appreciate the reading experience, which ultimately rewards us with a certain level of satisfaction and enjoyment.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
however, when it comes to learning, according to one of artificial intelligence researches conducted on agent simulated in the computer from MIT university, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately when we learn following curiousity by maximizing information gain. but when we learn with the book, the information they produce to be obsorved restricted in some aspect besides hard to find which aspect hinder us to learn actively with having curiousity. but when we learn something on the internet, we can search what we used to want to know whenever we want enabling us to learn actively resulting our knowledge optimized.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
However, when it comes to learning, according to one of the artificial intelligence research studies conducted at MIT University on computer-simulated agents, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately by following curiosity and maximizing information gain. On the other hand, learning with books may restrict the information they provide in some aspects, making it difficult to identify the specific areas that hinder active learning and curiosity. In contrast, learning something on the internet allows us to search for the information we want to know whenever we want, enabling us to learn actively and resulting in optimized knowledge
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summerize, I believe the significance of reading the book stay still at the aspect of giving us the sufficient opportunity of feeling fulfillment and enjoy. But they are not most useful means anymore as internet come to us as secondary unlimited and handy resourse of information.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In summary, I believe that the significance of reading books remains in providing us with ample opportunities for fulfillment and enjoyment. However, they are no longer the most useful means, as the internet has emerged as a primary, limitless, and convenient resource of information.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Q Some people think books are losing importance as a source of information and entertainment. to what extent do you agree? A with globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to get the information on the internet. some argue books are not important anymore as online website have cumulated immornouse information. i will elaborate on my perspective of this argument further in the following paragraph. With the globalization of the world, it is becoming easier to access information on the internet. Some argue that books are no longer important since online websites have accumulated enormous amounts of information. In the following paragraph, I will elaborate on my perspective regarding this argument when we read the book with paper, we can protect our eyesight from various dexitorious lights such as microwave and bluelight. morever, we can utilize our aother sensory motor system to appreciate reading mood entirely which eventually award us on some extent of satisfaction and enjoyness. When we read a book on paper, we can protect our eyesight from various detrimental lights, such as microwaves and blue light. Moreover, we can engage our other sensory and motor systems to fully appreciate the reading experience, which ultimately rewards us with a certain level of satisfaction and enjoyment. however, when it comes to learning, according to one of artificial intelligence researches conducted on agent simulated in the computer from MIT university, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately when we learn following curiousity by maximizing information gain. but when we learn with the book, the information they produce to be obsorved restricted in some aspect besides hard to find which aspect hinder us to learn actively with having curiousity. but when we learn something on the internet, we can search what we used to want to know whenever we want enabling us to learn actively resulting our knowledge optimized. However, when it comes to learning, according to one of the artificial intelligence research studies conducted at MIT University on computer-simulated agents, we can optimize our knowledge more accurately by following curiosity and maximizing information gain. On the other hand, learning with books may restrict the information they provide in some aspects, making it difficult to identify the specific areas that hinder active learning and curiosity. In contrast, learning something on the internet allows us to search for the information we want to know whenever we want, enabling us to learn actively and resulting in optimized knowledge In summerize, I believe the significance of reading the book stay still at the aspect of giving us the sufficient opportunity of feeling fulfillment and enjoy. But they are not most useful means anymore as internet come to us as secondary unlimited and handy resourse of information. In summary, I believe that the significance of reading books remains in providing us with ample opportunities for fulfillment and enjoyment. However, they are no longer the most useful means, as the internet has emerged as a primary, limitless, and convenient resource of information.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (metaphore)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(metaphore).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (metaphore)" /><published>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca%20(metaphore)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(metaphore).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; metaphore &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;formidable
&lt;br /&gt;
dismal
&lt;br /&gt;
ludicrous
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
be on the ball
&lt;br /&gt;
rule of thumb
&lt;br /&gt;
dim
&lt;br /&gt;
trickling
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
threw me completely
&lt;br /&gt;
got our wires crossed
&lt;br /&gt;
I’m not with you. / You’ve lost me there
&lt;br /&gt;
to be fed up to the back teeth
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Come over
&lt;br /&gt;
put forward
&lt;br /&gt;
come off
&lt;br /&gt;
come under
&lt;br /&gt;
stay on
&lt;br /&gt;
dwell on
&lt;br /&gt;
catch on
&lt;br /&gt;
going on
&lt;br /&gt;
brush up on
&lt;br /&gt;
laid off 
&lt;br /&gt;
thrown himself into&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">metaphore formidable dismal ludicrous be on the ball rule of thumb dim trickling threw me completely got our wires crossed I’m not with you. / You’ve lost me there to be fed up to the back teeth Come over put forward come off come under stay on dwell on catch on going on brush up on laid off thrown himself into</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (colloqual, words)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(colloqual,-words).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (colloqual, words)" /><published>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca%20(colloqual,%20words)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(colloqual,-words).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; colloqual &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a mass of
&lt;br /&gt;
dozens of
&lt;br /&gt;
tons of
&lt;br /&gt;
umpteen
&lt;br /&gt;
a scrap of
&lt;br /&gt;
I gather
&lt;br /&gt;
Incidentally
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
in excess of
&lt;br /&gt;
somewhere in the region of 
&lt;br /&gt;
or so
&lt;br /&gt;
dash
&lt;br /&gt;
stacks of
&lt;br /&gt;
or whatever
&lt;br /&gt;
and things like that / and that kind of thing.
&lt;br /&gt;
something along those lines
&lt;br /&gt;
or words to that effect
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Mumble
&lt;br /&gt;
mutter
&lt;br /&gt;
slagging off
&lt;br /&gt;
whining
&lt;br /&gt;
chatting away
&lt;br /&gt;
winding him up
&lt;br /&gt;
get tongue-tied
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; words &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;86
&lt;br /&gt;
overhang
&lt;br /&gt;
overshadowed
&lt;br /&gt;
undermine
&lt;br /&gt;
proliferate
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
guilt-ridden
&lt;br /&gt;
crime-ridden
&lt;br /&gt;
bedridden
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
upend
&lt;br /&gt;
end up
&lt;br /&gt;
uphold
&lt;br /&gt;
hold up
&lt;br /&gt;
outdo
&lt;br /&gt;
do out
&lt;br /&gt;
outrun
&lt;br /&gt;
run out
&lt;br /&gt;
upset
&lt;br /&gt;
set up&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">colloqual a mass of dozens of tons of umpteen a scrap of I gather Incidentally in excess of somewhere in the region of or so dash stacks of or whatever and things like that / and that kind of thing. something along those lines or words to that effect Mumble mutter slagging off whining chatting away winding him up get tongue-tied words 86 overhang overshadowed undermine proliferate guilt-ridden crime-ridden bedridden upend end up uphold hold up outdo do out outrun run out upset set up</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (variation)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(variation).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (variation)" /><published>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca%20(variation)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/23/voca-(variation).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; variation &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">variation</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (communication)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(communication).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (communication)" /><published>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca%20(communication)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(communication).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; agree &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;assent
countenance
endorse
clamp down
veto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; complain &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve just about had enough of
this is just not on
I’m not at all satisfied with
I wish to complain about
I take great exception to
I really must object to
grouse *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; apology &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;phoney *
alibi
flimsy pretext
remorse
acquitted
armistice
accord
ceasefire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; compliment &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;back-handed compliment
double-edged compliment
pay tribute to
ovation
extol
plaudit
laud&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; promise &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;promise someone the earth/moon
oath / to swear
swears by
pledge
vowed
wager&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">agree assent countenance endorse clamp down veto</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (regret, academy, agree)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(regret,-academy,-agree).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (regret, academy, agree)" /><published>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-22T09:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca%20(regret,%20academy,%20agree)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/22/voca-(regret,-academy,-agree).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; regret &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;out of touch
&lt;br /&gt;
what became of
&lt;br /&gt;
if I recall
&lt;br /&gt;
think back
&lt;br /&gt;
hear anything of
&lt;br /&gt;
what stands out in my mind
&lt;br /&gt;
reminiscing about
&lt;br /&gt;
through rose-tinted spectacles
&lt;br /&gt;
pangs
&lt;br /&gt;
rue
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; agree &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tally
&lt;br /&gt;
dissent
&lt;br /&gt;
concessions
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; academy &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;authoritative
&lt;br /&gt;
incidence
&lt;br /&gt;
negate
&lt;br /&gt;
thereby
&lt;br /&gt;
whereby
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;expounded
&lt;br /&gt;
posited
&lt;br /&gt;
subsumed
&lt;br /&gt;
allude
&lt;br /&gt;
touch upon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
scribble
&lt;br /&gt;
jot down
&lt;br /&gt;
doodling
&lt;br /&gt;
writing up
&lt;br /&gt;
touch-type
&lt;br /&gt;
run you off&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">regret out of touch what became of if I recall think back hear anything of what stands out in my mind reminiscing about through rose-tinted spectacles pangs rue</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (cause, compare, difficulty, opinions, statistics)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/09/voca-(cause,-compare,-difficulty,-opinions,-statistics).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (cause, compare, difficulty, opinions, statistics)" /><published>2023-06-09T17:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-09T17:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/09/voca%20(cause,%20compare,%20difficulty,%20opinions,%20statistics)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/09/voca-(cause,-compare,-difficulty,-opinions,-statistics).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; cause &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;precipitated *
&lt;br /&gt;
brought about
&lt;br /&gt;
has implications for&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; compare &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;affinity *
&lt;br /&gt;
akin to
&lt;br /&gt;
To use a sporting analogy *
&lt;br /&gt;
to equate 
&lt;br /&gt;
tantamount to *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; difficulty &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a snag, a hitch, a glitch. Glitch *
&lt;br /&gt;
pitfall *
&lt;br /&gt;
ordeal *
&lt;br /&gt;
abstruse *
&lt;br /&gt;
arduous *
&lt;br /&gt;
convoluted *
&lt;br /&gt;
gruelling *
&lt;br /&gt;
insufferable *
&lt;br /&gt;
wayward *
&lt;br /&gt;
What’s eating him
&lt;br /&gt;
What’s bugging him
&lt;br /&gt;
to slog *
&lt;br /&gt;
to grind *
&lt;br /&gt;
to graft *
&lt;br /&gt;
to flog yourself to death *
&lt;br /&gt;
in a fix * / in a spot * / in a hole / up against it * / up to your neck
&lt;br /&gt;
out of the wood(s) *
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; opinions &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The odds are
&lt;br /&gt;
The odds are against
&lt;br /&gt;
are bound to
&lt;br /&gt;
There’s every likelihood
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; statustics &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;twofold
&lt;br /&gt;
quadrupled
&lt;br /&gt;
by a factor of
&lt;br /&gt;
revised upwards *
&lt;br /&gt;
deviated from the norm *
&lt;br /&gt;
seesawed
&lt;br /&gt;
erratic
&lt;br /&gt;
blip
&lt;br /&gt;
flawed
&lt;br /&gt;
cautious *&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">cause precipitated * brought about has implications for</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">voca (Manner, Sense)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/08/voca-(Manner,-Sense).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="voca (Manner, Sense)" /><published>2023-06-08T16:48:33+09:00</published><updated>2023-06-08T16:48:33+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/08/voca%20(Manner,%20Sense)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hobby/2023/06/08/voca-(Manner,-Sense).html">&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; Motion &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
limp
&lt;br /&gt;
stagger
&lt;br /&gt;
lurch *
&lt;br /&gt;
tiptoe
&lt;br /&gt;
stride
&lt;br /&gt;
tramp
&lt;br /&gt;
trample
&lt;br /&gt;
trudge
&lt;br /&gt;
limped to a conclusion
&lt;br /&gt;
staggered
&lt;br /&gt;
Maria takes everything that life throws at her in her stride. [takes … 
calmly]
&lt;br /&gt;
unprecedented
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; Manner &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;insolent *
&lt;br /&gt;
etiquette
&lt;br /&gt;
stand on ceremony
&lt;br /&gt;
straitlaced
&lt;br /&gt;
the done thing
&lt;br /&gt;
netiquette
&lt;br /&gt;
twitch
&lt;br /&gt;
flinch *
&lt;br /&gt;
squirm *
&lt;br /&gt;
smirk *
&lt;br /&gt;
beam
&lt;br /&gt;
sniff at something
&lt;br /&gt;
snort
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; Sounds &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;squeaking *
&lt;br /&gt;
pounding
&lt;br /&gt;
creaked
&lt;br /&gt;
sizzled
&lt;br /&gt;
rang out
&lt;br /&gt;
eerie
&lt;br /&gt;
deafening *
&lt;br /&gt;
you could have heard a pin drop
&lt;br /&gt;
I can’t hear myself think
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; Weight &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;weighed down
&lt;br /&gt;
weigh up
&lt;br /&gt;
weighed out
&lt;br /&gt;
weighing on me
&lt;br /&gt;
weighed in
&lt;br /&gt;
sift * 체로 걸러내다
&lt;br /&gt;
dilute
&lt;br /&gt;
impervious *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size:30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt; speed &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;nip
&lt;br /&gt;
dart
&lt;br /&gt;
whizz
&lt;br /&gt;
zip
&lt;br /&gt;
bolt
&lt;br /&gt;
scamper, scurry, scuttle
&lt;br /&gt;
tumble (finantial)
&lt;br /&gt;
crawl, creep
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="hobby" /><summary type="html">Motion limp stagger lurch * tiptoe stride tramp trample trudge limped to a conclusion staggered Maria takes everything that life throws at her in her stride. [takes … calmly] unprecedented Manner insolent * etiquette stand on ceremony straitlaced the done thing netiquette twitch flinch * squirm * smirk * beam sniff at something snort Sounds squeaking * pounding creaked sizzled rang out eerie deafening * you could have heard a pin drop I can’t hear myself think Weight weighed down weigh up weighed out weighing on me weighed in sift * 체로 걸러내다 dilute impervious *</summary></entry></feed>